<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<codeList xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://apps.gs1.org/GDD/Documents/GDDCodeListSchema.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <urn>urn:gs1:gdd:cl:PackagingMarkedLabelAccreditationCode</urn>
  <name></name>
  <version>9</version>
  <domain>gdsn</domain>
  <code><value>3PMSF</value><name>Three-peak mountain snowflake (3PMSF)</name><description>"A three-peak mountain snowflake (3PMSF) symbol branded on a tire's sidewall indicates the tire meets required performance criteria in snow testing to be considered severe snow service-rated. Originally used as a designation for winter tires, the 3PMSF symbol is now featured on some all-season and all-terrain tires with snow performance that meets the testing criteria. (UNECE Regulation 117, (EC) 661/2009)

"</description></code>
  <code><value>AGRICULTURE_BIOLOGIQUE</value><name>Agriculture Biologique</name><description>France's national logo for organic products since 1985. Organic products carrying the logo must contain more than 95 percent organic components and be produced or processed within the EU, and were certified by one of the inspection bodies accredited according to EN 45011.</description></code>
  <code><value>AISE_2020_BRAND</value><name>The A.I.S.E. 2020 mark for brands</name><description>The new mark certifies that your brand meets all Charter product sustainability standards, in addition to the manufacturing requirements (ISO 14025 standard for Type III environmental labels and declarations).</description></code>
  <code><value>AISE_2020_COMPANY</value><name>The A.I.S.E. 2020 mark for companies</name><description>This new mark certifies that your organisation meets the Charter company sustainability standards in their manufacturing facilities (ISO 14025 standard for Type III environmental labels and declarations).</description></code>
  <code><value>ALENTEJO_SUSTAINABILITY_PROGRAMME</value><name>Wines of Alentejo Sustainability Programme</name><description>The purpose of the WASP (Wines of Alentejo Sustainability Programme) is to align the sector's competitiveness with environmental, economic and social objectives, thus creating opportunities based on an integrated and sustainably oriented strategy. The certification of sustainable wine production is the guarantee that an independent evaluation, by a third party credentialed according to the Portuguese Quality System, confirms that good sustainability practices have been implemented. It is an important source of information to assess, guarantee and improve the environmental and socio-economic conditions of the industry.</description></code>
  <code><value>BEE_FRIENDLY</value><name>Bee friendly</name><description>The goal of the bee friendly label is to promote the agricultural  technics which are not harmful to bee and other pollinators.</description></code>
  <code><value>100_PERCENT_CANADIAN_MILK</value><name></name><description>The use of a "100% Canadian Milk" or "100% Canadian Dairy" claim, with or without logos, vignettes etc., when used on dairy products, indicates all of the dairy ingredients in the product are derived from Canadian sources.</description></code>
  <code><value>100_PERCENT_VEGANSKT</value><name>100% Veganskt</name><description>100% Veganskt (Vegan) is certified by Djurens rätt (Animal rights) and shows that the product does not contain animal ingredients.</description></code>
  <code><value>ACMI</value><name>Art And Creative Materials Institute, Inc.</name><description>Art And Creative Materials Institute, Inc.</description></code>
  <code><value>ADCCPA</value><name>ADCCPA</name><description>The ADCCPA is a non-profit association established in 1995, for the development of food product conformity certification. It manages the "CQ - Certified Product" logo, identifying the Product Conformance Certification (CCP) approach.</description></code>
  <code><value>AFIA_PET_FOOD_FACILITY</value><name>AFIA Pet Food Facility </name><description>AFIA Pet Food Ingredient Facility Certification Program is launched by the American Feed Industry Association and administered by the Safe Quality Food Institute (SQFI). The program builds upon the domestic Safe Feed/Safe Food program, but is designed to meet the safety issues specifically related to the manufacturing of pet food. </description></code>
  <code><value>AGENCE_BIO</value><name></name><description>The BIO Agency is a public interest group whose mission is to develop and promote organic agriculture.</description></code>
  <code><value>AGRI_CONFIANCE</value><name>AGRI Confiance</name><description>Where do the food products come from? How and by whom are they produced? Are they respectful of the environment?
It is to answer all these questions that Agri Confiance® was created in 1992. A collective approach of the producers organized in cooperative, engaged for a sustainable agriculture and for each one of us. A controlled engagement. An ambition. A movement. For there to be trust between us.</description></code>
  <code><value>AGRI_NATURA</value><name>Agri Natura</name><description>Certification for meat out of integrated production based on principles of IP-Suisse. Label owned by Ernst Sutter AG.</description></code>
  <code><value>AGRICULTURE_BIOLIGIQUE</value><name>Agriculture Bioligique</name><description>France's national logo for organic products since 1985. Organic products carrying the logo must contain more than 95 percent organic components and be produced or processed within the EU, and were certified by one of the inspection bodies accredited according to EN 45011.</description></code>
  <code><value>AHAM</value><name>Air cleaner performance standard
e.g., humidifiers</name><description>The Association of Home Appliance Manufacturers (AHAM) is an organization that verifies the volume, energy and in some cases, performance, of many common household appliances. Since 1967, we've used outside laboratories to test products, and today you'll find the AHAM Verified Mark on all products included in our program – making comparing products easier for you</description></code>
  <code><value>AISE</value><name></name><description>A.I.S.E., the international Association for Soaps, Detergents and Maintenance Products is the official representative body of this industry in Europe.</description></code>
  <code><value>AISE_2005</value><name>The International Association for Soaps, Detergents and Maintenance Products</name><description>The International Association for Soaps, Detergents and Maintenance Products: This Charter logo on a product means that the company placing this product on the market is committed to the industry Charter for Sustainable Cleaning, and that the company has successfully complied with the Charter Sustainability Procedures. Consumers and professional users who see this logo on a product can be assured that the company making this product is voluntarily committed to delivering continual improvements in safety, environmental friendliness and other key aspects of sustainability. Only those companies that have signed up to the Charter, and meet the licensing conditions, are permitted to use it.</description></code>
  <code><value>AISE_2010</value><name></name><description>The International Association for Soaps, Detergents and Maintenance Products This logo will certify that the company which manufactured the product is following Charter update 2010 sustainability principles.</description></code>
  <code><value>AKC_PEACH_KOSHER</value><name>Atlanta Kashrus Commission Certification  </name><description>Atlanta Kashrus Commission Certification  </description></code>
  <code><value>ALIMENTATION_DU_TOUT_PETIT</value><name>Alimentation du tout petit</name><description>"The ""childhood food"" symbol guarantees that the product complies with French and European regulatory requirements. In addition to perfectly meeting the special nutritional needs of children from birth to 3 years old, the product meets very strict safety standards.



Ingredient quality, strict monitoring of contaminants and microbiological risks, packaging composition... my child's meal is combed through to make sure everything is fine."</description></code>
  <code><value>ALIMENTS_BIO_PREPARES_AU_QUEBEC</value><name>Aliments BIO Prepares au Quebec </name><description>The presence of Quebec Bio Food prepared on a product means that it is composed of minimally 85% of Quebec organic products. The processing and packaging of these foods must also be made in Québec</description></code>
  <code><value>ALIMENTS_DU_QUEBEC</value><name>Aliments du Quebec</name><description>Aliments du Québec is an organization whose mission is to promote Quebec agri-food products.  Promotional activities, brand identification at the points-of-sale and special events are all ways to inform consumers about the availability of Quebec food products
Aliments du Québec is the holder of the unique label of origin for Quebec food products, recognized by the whole agri-food industry, we manage two certifications: Aliments du Québec and Aliments préparés au Québec.</description></code>
  <code><value>ALIMENTS_DU_QUEBEC_BIO</value><name>Aliments du Quebec BIO</name><description>The presence of Quebec organic Food on a product means that it is entirely made from ingredients sourced in Quebec and composed of minimally 85% of Quebec organic products.</description></code>
  <code><value>ALIMENTS_PREPARES_AU_QUEBEC</value><name>Aliments Prepares au Quebec</name><description>Any product processed and packaged entirely in Quebec can be considered an "Aliments préparés au Québec .  When the main ingredients are available in Quebec in sufficient quantities, they must be used. </description></code>
  <code><value>ALUMINIUM_GESAMTVERBAND_DER_ALUMINIUMINDUSTRIE</value><name></name><description>The packaging is recyclable aluminium by Gesamtverband der Aluminiumindustrie.</description></code>
  <code><value>AMA_GENUSSREGION</value><name>AMA Delight region (Austria)</name><description>AMA GENUSSREGION is a protected umbrella brand from the Austrian Federal Ministry of Agriculture, Regions and Tourism and the Agrarmarkt Austria Marketing GesmbH which certifies the regional provenance and quality of Austrian food products. www.genussregionen.at</description></code>
  <code><value>AMA_ORGANIC_SEAL</value><name></name><description>Austria Ministry of Agriculture Organic Label, AMA Marketing licenses the AMA organic logo. Red, white and black indicates the majority of ingredients are of Austrian origin.</description></code>
  <code><value>AMA_ORGANIC_SEAL_BLACK</value><name></name><description>AMA Assurance Organic products with a national origin are uniformly marked with the black AMA organic label without indication of origin.</description></code>
  <code><value>AMA_SEAL_OF_APPROVAL</value><name></name><description>The AMA quality label ensures independent controls and stands for conventionally produced foods that meet exceptional quality criteria and whose origin is traceable.</description></code>
  <code><value>AMERICAN_DENTAL_ASSOCIATION</value><name>American Dental Association</name><description>The American Dental Association's (ADA) Seal of Acceptance is a trusted symbol of a dental product's safety and effectiveness. In order to earn the Seal, manufacturers must supply objective data from clinical and/or laboratory studies that support the product's safety, effectiveness, and promotional claims. </description></code>
  <code><value>AMERICAN_HEART_ASSOCIATION_CERTIFIED</value><name>American Heart Association Certified</name><description>The American Heart Association Certified attribute includes all products that have published the symbol by Heart-Check Food Certification Program on their packaging. </description></code>
  <code><value>ANIMAL_WELFARE_APPROVED_GRASSFED</value><name></name><description>Guarantees the meat comes from an animal raised entirely outdoors on pasture, and fed a 100-per-cent grass and forage diet.</description></code>
  <code><value>APPELLATION_ORIGINE_CONTROLEE</value><name>Appellation Origine Controlee</name><description>The registered designation of origin (AOC) is a label allowing to identify a product whose manufacturing stages (production and processing) are carried out in the same geographical area and according to recognized know-how. It is the combination of a physical and biological environment with a traditional human community which bases the specificity of an AOC product, with definition in a specification.

The French AOC is an official French label that meets the criteria of the European Protected Designation of Origin (PDO). In France, since 2012, for products other than wine, the term AOC is replaced by AOP as soon as the product is registered at the European level.</description></code>
  <code><value>AQUACULTURE_STEWARDSHIP_COUNCIL</value><name></name><description>The Aquaculture Stewardship Council ASC certification and labelling programme for responsibly farmed seafood.  A global organisation working with aquaculture producers, seafood processors, retail and foodservice companies, scientists, conservation groups and the public to promote the best environmental and social choice in seafood. The ASC's aquaculture certification programme and seafood label will recognise and reward responsible aquaculture.</description></code>
  <code><value>ARGE_GENTECHNIK_FREI</value><name></name><description>ARGE logo stands for the production of food without genetically modified additives.</description></code>
  <code><value>ARGENCERT</value><name>Argencert</name><description>Argencert guarantees the organic quality of a product from its origin to the final result, certifying both raw and processed products and the compatibility assessment of inputs.</description></code>
  <code><value>ARLA_FARMER_OWNED</value><name>Arla Farmer Owned</name><description>The FARMER OWNED marque has been develop to use on pack on all Arla branded products. FARMER OWNED represents the fact that Arla Foods is 100% owned by farmers. The FARMER OWNED marque is implemented on Arla branded assortment across all markets. The Farmer Owned marque is owned and administered by Arla Foods.</description></code>
  <code><value>ASCO</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Agricultural Services Certified Organic (ASCO)</name><description>Agricultural Services Certified Organic, LLC provides quality, express and economical organic certification services as established by the National Organic Program that meets the individualized needs of our clients in the global market place</description></code>
  <code><value>ASMI</value><name>The Alaska Seafood Marketing Institute</name><description>ASMI The Alaska Seafood Marketing Institute is a marketing organization with the mission of increasing the economic value of the Alaska seafood resource through:
• Increasing the positive awareness of the Alaska Seafood brand;
• Quality assurance, technical industry analysis, education, advocacy and research;
http://www.alaskaseafood.org/.</description></code>
  <code><value>ATG</value><name></name><description>If there is no BENOR-mark for a specific material, then the manufacturers can ask for a technical approval by BUtgb (Belgian Union for technical approval in the construction). This technical approval (ATG) provides a technical advice, including a description and the technical characteristics. An ATG is a favourable review of one particular building product of one manufacturer for a particular application. It's all about systems, innovative products and products that contain multiple components.</description></code>
  <code><value>AUS_KAUP_ESTONIA</value><name></name><description>Used to specify Estonia Meat in their product. Eesti Lihatöötlejate Assotsiatsioon www.ela.ee</description></code>
  <code><value>AUSTRALIAN_CERTIFIED_ORGANIC</value><name>Australian Certified Organic</name><description>Australian Certified Organic (ACO) is Australia’s largest certifier for organic and biodynamic produce and has over 1500 operators within its certification system.
ACO provides certification services to operators from all sectors of the organic industry. Certification ensures compliance with national production standards and allows trace back of all products to their origin.</description></code>
  <code><value>AUSTRIA_BIO_GARANTIE</value><name></name><description>Austria Bio Garantie GMBH (ABG)  is Austria's leading inspection body. It conducts inspections throughout Austria at all levels of the organic production chain (farmers-processors-traders-import/export) as well as in different foreign countries.</description></code>
  <code><value>AUSTRIAN_ECO_LABEL</value><name></name><description>The Austrian Eco Label guarantees environment-friendly products and services.</description></code>
  <code><value>BCARA_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Province of British Columbia Certified Organic, British Columbia Association for Regenerative Agriculture (BCARA), Canada</name><description>BCARA is accredited by the Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) as a certification body that certifies organic products under the Canada Organic Regime. Products certified under the Canada Organic Regime can be sold inter-provincially and internationally to countries that have equivalency agreements with Canada. The Organic Products Regulations require mandatory certification to the current National Organic Standard for agricultural products represented as organic in international and inter-provincial trade, or that bear the federal organic agricultural product legend (or federal logo).</description></code>
  <code><value>BDIH_LOGO</value><name></name><description>BDIH Germany guidelines for Certified Natural Cosmetics</description></code>
  <code><value>BEBAT</value><name></name><description>BEBAT is a non-profit organization, founded in 1995 under a Belgian law on environmental taxes. BEBAT gives a new life to batteries and flashlights! We do that by sorting and recycling. The federal government and the regional authorities are working with us.</description></code>
  <code><value>BEDRE_DYREVELFAERD_1HEART</value><name>Bedre Dyrevelfaerd 1Heart</name><description>The government animal-welfare label will initially be for pork, but it will later be expanded to cover meat from other animals. Examples of animal welfare for this marking include free-range sows, curly tail/undocked tail, more straw, more space, max. 8 hours’ transport.</description></code>
  <code><value>BEDRE_DYREVELFAERD_2HEART</value><name>Bedre Dyrevelfaerd 2Heart</name><description>The government animal-welfare label will initially be for pork, but it will later be expanded to cover meat from other animals. Examples of animal welfare include free-range sows, curly tail/undocked tail, even more straw, even more space, max. 8 hours’ transport.</description></code>
  <code><value>BEDRE_DYREVELFAERD_3HEART</value><name>Bedre Dyrevelfaerd 3Heart</name><description>The government animal-welfare label will initially be for pork, but it will later be expanded to cover meat from other animals. Examples of animal welfare for this marking include free-range sows, curly tail/undocked tail, much more straw, much more Space, max. 8 hours’ transport, outdoor space,
access to open fields. </description></code>
  <code><value>BELGAQUA</value><name></name><description>Belgaqua is the Belgian Federation for the Water Sector, and verifies the conformity of devices connected to the water supply at the request of the manufacturer or the importer, and is responsible for the inspection of protections against back blends.</description></code>
  <code><value>BENOR</value><name></name><description>BENOR stands for BElgian NORm and points out that a product is according to Belgian standards. Is mainly used for traditional building materials such as steel, concrete, tile, brick, floor tiles and other concrete products, indicated by the abbreviation NBN. Mainly for building materials in road construction.</description></code>
  <code><value>BERCHTESGADENER_LAND</value><name></name><description>The regional seal "Berchtesgadener Land" approved regional origin and quality of organically and conventionally produced agricultural products and services in the region of Berchtesgaden. The award criteria go in terms of the origin and support of genetic engineering ban partially beyond legal requirements. </description></code>
  <code><value>BEST_AQUACULTURE_PRACTICES</value><name></name><description>The Best Aquaculture Practices Certified (BAP Certified) mark on retail packaging tells consumers that seafood came from BAP certified aquaculture facilities.
The Best Aquaculture Practices standards, developed by the Global Aquaculture Alliance, form the basis for BAP certification. The standards specifically protect biodiversity and worker rights within a program that addresses environmental, social, food safety and traceability issues throughout producers' operations.</description></code>
  <code><value>BEST_AQUACULTURE_PRACTICES_2_STARS</value><name></name><description>2 Star BAP accreditation. The BAP program is the world’s most comprehensive third-party certification system for aquaculture facilities, addressing every key element of responsible aquaculture, including environmental responsibility, social responsibility, food safety, animal welfare, traceability and more. BAP standards encompassing the entire aquaculture production chain, including farms, processing plants, hatcheries and feed mills. </description></code>
  <code><value>BEST_AQUACULTURE_PRACTICES_3_STARS</value><name></name><description>3 Star BAP accreditation. The BAP program is the world’s most comprehensive third-party certification system for aquaculture facilities, addressing every key element of responsible aquaculture, including environmental responsibility, social responsibility, food safety, animal welfare, traceability and more. BAP standards encompassing the entire aquaculture production chain, including farms, processing plants, hatcheries and feed mills. </description></code>
  <code><value>BEST_AQUACULTURE_PRACTICES_4_STARS</value><name></name><description>4 Star BAP accreditation. The BAP program is the world’s most comprehensive third-party certification system for aquaculture facilities, addressing every key element of responsible aquaculture, including environmental responsibility, social responsibility, food safety, animal welfare, traceability and more. BAP standards encompassing the entire aquaculture production chain, including farms, processing plants, hatcheries and feed mills. </description></code>
  <code><value>BETER_LEVEN_1_STER</value><name></name><description>The one-star Beter Leven (better life) mark indicates that the product comes from a company that cares that animals are kept according to the minimal requirements for sanitation and wel-being for the cattle industry. See: http://beterleven.dierenbescherming.nl/1-ster</description></code>
  <code><value>BETER_LEVEN_2_STER</value><name></name><description>The two-star Beter Leven (better life) mark indicates that the product comes from a company that provides for a higher wel-being of animals than that established by the minimal requirements for sanitation and wel-being for the cattle industry, yet the conditions are inferior to those of Biological-class products. See: http://beterleven.dierenbescherming.nl/2-sterren-</description></code>
  <code><value>BETER_LEVEN_3_STER</value><name></name><description>The three-star Beter Leven (better life) mark is awarded to products that come from companies that excel in keeping animals according to top guidelines for Biological-class products. In some cases this mark is accompanied by an EKO indication. See: http://beterleven.dierenbescherming.nl/3-sterren-</description></code>
  <code><value>BETTER_BUSINESS_BUREAU_ACCREDITED</value><name>Better Business Bureau Accredited</name><description>If a business has been accredited by the BBB, it means BBB has determined that the business meets accreditation standards, which include a commitment to make a good faith effort to resolve any consumer complaints. BBB accredited businesses pay a fee for accreditation review and monitoring for continued compliance and for support of BBB services to the public. BBB Code of Business Practices represents standards for business accreditation by BBB. Businesses based in the United States and Canada that meet these standards and complete all application procedures will be accredited by BBB.  The Code is built on the BBB Standards for Trust, eight principles that summarize important elements of creating and maintaining trust in business. </description></code>
  <code><value>BETTER_COTTON_INITIATIVE</value><name>Better Cotton Initiative</name><description>The Better Cotton Initiative (BCI) is a not-for-profit organisation stewarding the global standards for Better Cotton, and bringing together cotton’s complex supply chain, from the farmers to the retailers. BCI exists to make global cotton production better for the people who produce it, better for the environment it grows in and better for the sector’s future, by developing Better Cotton as a sustainable mainstream commodity.</description></code>
  <code><value>BEVEG</value><name>BeVeg</name><description>"BeVeg is a global vegan network that brings legal credibility to vegan claims, which inherently raises the standard of consumer transparency. BeVeg is ISO accredited and recognized by the world accreditation forum for its internationally accredited vegan standard. BeVeg is accredited under ISO 17065 as a published vegan standard for vegan conformity assessment. https://www.beveg.com/

"</description></code>
  <code><value>BEWUSST_TIROL</value><name>Bewusst Tirol</name><description>Bewusst Tirol is a seal of quality marking food from the Tyrol. The "Awareness Tyrol" project promotes the use of local food in the hotel industry and gastronomy and thus strengthens the cooperation between tourism and agriculture. The participating companies are honoured for their high use of domestic products. http://amtirol.at/projekte/bewusst-tirol</description></code>
  <code><value>BEWUSTE_KEUZE</value><name></name><description>Identifies non-staple or non-essential products (e.g. soup, candy, desserts, etc.) that offer more nutritional value or less contain less of potentially harmful ingredients (such as sugar, salt, fat) in comparison to similar items according to the guidelines of the Dutch Wetenschappelijke Commissie. See: http://www.ikkiesbewust.nl/</description></code>
  <code><value>BIKO_TIROL</value><name></name><description>BIKo TYROL covers Genetically Modified-free milk production, AMA seal, quality Tyrol and beef labelling are controlled and certified. The Biko Tyrol operates in accordance with EN 45011 and is an accredited certification body.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_AUSTRIA_LABEL</value><name></name><description>Bio Austria is the Austrian Bio-network of Eastern organic farmers. Created from the former Association Harvest for Life</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_BAYERN_WITH_CERTIFICATE_PROVENANCE</value><name>Bio-Bayern with Certificate of Provenance</name><description>In cases in which the products of a certain provenance (e.g. Bavaria) made according to the higher quality criteria can be tracked along the whole path from their production, via their processing, all the way to the shop counter, they can be given a biolabel stating the corresponding indication of geographical origin. In this case the origin is presented both in the form of a corresponding logo as well as the colours of the state of origin in the inner oval. The biolabel with the certificate of origin awarded by the Free State of Bavaria stands for products and services over and beyond the statutory standards a three-tier control system a full certificate of origin

</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_BAYERN_WITHOUT_CERTIFICATE_PROVENANCE</value><name>Bio-Bayern without Certificate of Provenance</name><description>The biolabel awarded by the Free State of Bavaria offers companies in the farming and food sector in the European Union the opportunity to label goods produced in compliance with the terms of the EU-Eco Regulation in combination with higher quality criteria.
The precisely defined regulations are a guarantee for the consumers of an economic system in harmony with nature and provide them with guidance when making their purchases. Both the farmers of organic products as well as the producers must fulfil the demanding inspection criteria and allow their products to be checked by state-approved and monitored inspection boards. The defined control system ensures a complete traceability of the products over the entire lifecycle. The biolabel awarded by the Free State of Bavaria stands for products and services over and beyond the statutory standards a three-tier control system
</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_CZECH_LABEL</value><name>Bio Czech Label</name><description>National BIO mark of the Czech Republic. More information is available on the website of Czech Ministry of Agriculture. </description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_FISCH</value><name></name><description>ARGE Biofisch stands for criteria in rearing of fish according to agreed quality standards of organic fish farming in Austria.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_LABEL_BADEN_WURTTENBERG</value><name>Bio-LABEL Baden-Württemberg</name><description>The products marked with the Bio-Zeichen Baden-Württemberg are regional organic foods with a traceable origin. The use or labelling is based on the ecological standards of the EC Organic Regulation supplemented with the requirement that the products must be produced in fully converted farms and, in part, on the more stringent requirements of the organic farming associations. The regional origin of the products ensures an additional ecological advantage of the products. The rationality promotes short transport and marketing channels. The independent checks of food by authorized inspection bodies and the additional supervision by the sign holder ensure a high degree of credibility of the sign. The control number printed on the products makes the controls comprehensible.
The seal clearly shows the consumer that the agricultural products and products come from Baden-Württemberg. This ensures not only that the processing takes place in the region, but also that the sourcing of raw materials is 100% regional. In the production and processing of food, the guidelines of the EU Organic Regulation are used as the basis. Many products that are labelled with the Baden-Württemberg organic label are also produced according to the stricter guidelines of an organic farming association. The farms participating in the Bio-Zeichen Baden-Württemberg must be 100% organic. A partial conversion is - with the exception of products from the orchard - not permitted. Neutral controls ensure compliance with the guidelines.
</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_LABEL_GERMAN</value><name></name><description>German national organic certification label (Bio-Siegel), see www.bio-siegel.de</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_LABEL_HESSEN</value><name>Bio-LABEL Hessen</name><description>The organic Label - HESSEN shows the consumer that an organically produced product originates from the region. For this, the nationwide used organic seal was supplemented with a reference to the origin. Since 2006, there is this sign for Hesse.
In 2010, the organic Label - HESSEN was supplemented by another appendix: the European Union logo for organically produced products.
This allows companies to use only one logo on the packaging of their products instead of three different logos, because the European organic label is required.
Behind the Bio-Seal - HESSEN, similar to the quality mark "Tested Quality - HESSEN", there are special requirements for producers, processors and marketers regarding the quality and traceable origin of their products.
</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_PARTENAIRE</value><name>Bio Partenaire</name><description>Bio Partenaire guarantees that the product meets the European requirements for organic agriculture and a fair price is paid to farmers in developing countries.
Previously, the label was known under the name Bio Equitable.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_RING_ALLGAEU</value><name></name><description> The logo of Bio-Ring Allgäu e.V. is issued by an association of consumers and organic farmers since 1987 with the aim to strengthen the organic farming in the region of Allgäu. Their focus is on the involvement of an independent, public welfare-oriented regional development processes in connection with the marketing of high quality regional agricultural products. The association represents the interests of producers, whose production in excess of the statutory requirements and their quality criteria based on a wide range of areas basic criteria (eco-certifications) and are the life cycle (raw materials, production and processing, disposal) take into account the products.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIO_SUISSE_BUD_SEAL</value><name></name><description>Represents interests of Swiss organic farmers www.bio-suisse.ch</description></code>
  <code><value>BIOCHECKED_NON_GLYPHOSATE_CERTIFIED</value><name>BioChecked Non-Glyphosate certified</name><description>BioChecked™ Agrees to provide third party certification for Non Glyphosate Certified™ (Zero Tolerance*) by reviewing and holding producer’s individual copy of laboratory test results of Glyphosate testing in house in secure and confidential manner for 1 year and as renewed. </description></code>
  <code><value>BIOCHECKED_NON_GMO_VERIFIED</value><name>BioChecked Non GMO verified</name><description>BioChecked™ offers Non GMO Certification for single input (mono ingredient) Non GMO Certified™ and multiple input (multi-ingredient) Non GMO Verified™  foods.  It is certified multiple countries; </description></code>
  <code><value>BIODEGRADABLE</value><name>Biodegradable</name><description>The product is biodegradable. There can be different variations of the logo.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIODEGRADABLE_PRODUCTS_INSTITUTE</value><name>Biodegradable Products Institute </name><description>The Biodegradable Products Institute (BPI) is a not-for-profit association of key individuals and groups from government, industry and academia. Through our innovative compostable label program, we educate manufacturers, legislators and consumers about the importance of scientifically based standards for compostable materials which biodegrade in large composting facilities. 
</description></code>
  <code><value>BIODYNAMIC_CERTIFICATION</value><name>Biodynamic Certification</name><description>The Biodynamic Certified includes all products that have published the Demeter USA Certified Biodynamic Certification on their package. </description></code>
  <code><value>BIODYNAMISCH</value><name>Biodynamisch</name><description>The "Biodynamisch" indicates that products contain at least 95 percent organic and 90 percent demeter ingredients. The Label is issued by the association Demeter e.V. and is used for food and cosmetic products.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIOKREIS</value><name>Biokreis</name><description>The Biokreis Association for Organic Farming and Healthy Food e. V. forgives the label.
The label promotes cooperation between organic farmers and processing companies. They should comply with environmental and social principles. It also aims to make peasant agriculture in the sense of a circular economy.
The criteria presuppose compliance with the EU organic regulation for the EU organic label, but go beyond this with its own requirements.
</description></code>
  <code><value>BIOLAND</value><name></name><description>The Bioland-Label (organic label) identifies products from organic farming. The production method based on a circular economy - without synthetic pesticides and synthetic chemical nitrogen fertilizer. The animals are kept humanely and the food will be processed carefully. The guidelines go beyond the EU criteria. The organic label is assigned by the Bioland association.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIOLAND_ENNSTAL</value><name></name><description>The "organic farming Ennstal" was founded in 1989 as a regional initiative - today one in three farmers cultivated in Styria Liezen region its operation under the strict rules of organic farming.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIOPARK</value><name>Biopark</name><description>The biopark e. V. was founded in 1991 by farmers and scientists as an organic farming association. Biopark companies are represented throughout Germany. At the initiative of Biopark, the first GMO-free region was founded in Germany.
The objective of the Biopark label, which has been awarded since 1991, is to promote organic farming. The aim is a closed loop as far as possible. It is about the protection of the environment, landscape management and animal welfare.
Biopark certifies farms that have decided to convert their work to organic farming. The Biopark label can be found on meat and cereal products as well as on potatoes. The criteria presuppose compliance with the EU organic regulation for the EU organic label, but go beyond this with its own requirements.
</description></code>
  <code><value>BIOS_KONTROLLE</value><name></name><description>The BIOS label ensures organic food that is not genetically modified and produced in accordance with environmental standards. The BIOS logo may be used for the labelling of certified organic products exclusively.</description></code>
  <code><value>BIRD_FRIENDLY_COFFEE_SMITHSONIAN_CERTIFICATION</value><name>Bird Friendly Coffee Smithsonian Certification </name><description>The Smithsonian Migratory Bird Centre Bird Friendly logo guarantees that every bean is produced organically, under high-quality shade, that tropical "agroforests" are preserved and migratory birds find a healthy haven.</description></code>
  <code><value>BK_CHECK_VAAD_HAKASHRUS_OF_BUFFALO</value><name>Bk Check Vaad Hakashrus Of Buffalo</name><description>Vaad HaKashrus of Buffalo Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>BLEU_BLANC_COEUR</value><name>Bleu Blanc Coeur</name><description>The Blue-White-Heart approach was born between 1993 and 2000, from a simple observation made by a dairy farmer, Jean Pierre Pasquet to an agricultural engineer, Pierre Weill. He explained to him that he noticed that in the spring, when his cows were in pasture grass, they were in better shape, and the butter he made was softer and more spreadable than in winter.

From this observation, Jean-Pierre Pasquet and Pierre Weill began their reflection on the importance of preserving the food chain and valuing plants and seeds of nutritional interest. Together, they created an agriculture committed to a sustainable and social approach with breeders eager to feed their fellow citizens.</description></code>
  <code><value>BLUE_ANGEL</value><name></name><description>The Blue Angel is awarded to companies as kind of a reward for their commitment to environmental protection. They use it to professionally promote their eco-friendly products in the market. The Blue Angel is an ecological beacon showing the consumer the way to the ecologically superior product and promotes environmentally conscious consumption. See: http://www.blauer-engel.de/en/index.php</description></code>
  <code><value>BLUE_RIBBON_KOSHER</value><name>Blue Ribbon Kosher</name><description>Blue Ribbon Kosher Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>BLUESIGN</value><name>Bluesign Technologies AG Approved e.g., footwear insoles</name><description>The quality label bluesign® approved fabrics certifies that at least 90 per cent of the used fabrics comply with the strict safety and environmental requirements of the bluesign® criteria. Their suppliers and manufacturers have been verified as bluesign® system partners.</description></code>
  <code><value>BORD_BIA_APPROVED</value><name></name><description>The Bord Bia Approved logo is awarded to a company which has been audited by Bord Bia to verify that processes, from farm to fork, comply with the highest Quality Assurance Standards. These standards include: animal welfare, traceability, environment, safety, feed, water, testing, inspection, hygiene and good manufacturing practice. "Bord Bia Approved" is awarded to a company where all the ingredients including meat content satisfy the Bord Bia requirements. www.bordbia.ie</description></code>
  <code><value>BORD_BIA_APPROVED_MEAT</value><name></name><description>Bord Bia Approved - Meat Content Only applies to companies where only the meat content satisfies certain conditions detailed in the Bord Bia requirements document. see http://www.bordbia.ie/industryservices/quality/Documents/Quality-Assurance-Scheme-Logo-GuidelinesV7.pdf for more details.</description></code>
  <code><value>BRA_MILJOVAL_LABEL_SWEDISH</value><name></name><description>Bra Miljöval Bra Miljöval is the ecolabel of SSNC. It is referred to as "Good Environmental Choice" in English. SSNC started ecolabelling ecolabelling</description></code>
  <code><value>BRC_GLOBAL_STANDARDS</value><name></name><description>BRC Global Standards is a leading safety and quality certification programme, used by over 22,000 certificated suppliers in 123 countries, with certification issued through a worldwide network of accredited certification bodies.</description></code>
  <code><value>BREATHEWAY</value><name>BreatheWay</name><description>BreatheWay® membranes are designed to naturally extend the shelf life of virtually any fresh product that would benefit from reduced oxygen levels and managed carbon dioxide levels. A unique membrane solution manages all gas transfer requirements for the package, leaving more flexibility for the balance of the package to meet shipping or merchandising requirements. </description></code>
  <code><value>BRITISH_DENTAL_HEALTH</value><name></name><description>A symbol used in the UK to indicate the dental health claims are clinically proven by the British Dental Health Foundation.</description></code>
  <code><value>BRITISH_RETAIL_CONSORTIUM_CERTIFICATION</value><name>British Retail Consortium Certification</name><description>BRC Global Standards is a leading safety and quality certification. The Standards guarantee the quality, safety and operational criteria and ensures that manufacturers fulfil their legal obligations and provide protection for the end consumer. </description></code>
  <code><value>BSCI</value><name></name><description>Stands for Business Social Compliance Initiative, and aims to improve the working conditions in the supply chain around the world. It shows consumers that an article is produced according to ethical practices as regards working conditions.</description></code>
  <code><value>BULLFROG</value><name>Bullfrog Power</name><description>Bullfrog Power emerged on the energy scene with a visionary goal: to transform the electricity landscape in Canada. BullfrogPower  offered homes and businesses a green choice where previously there wasn’t one:  energy.</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_BEEF</value><name>Made with Canadian Beef</name><description>"Product of Canada" claims can be applied to meat from Canadian animals that are slaughtered in Canada. Animals are considered Canadian if they are born or hatched, raised and slaughtered in Canada or, in the case of feeder cattle, if they have spent a period of at least 60 days in Canada prior to slaughter in Canada.</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_BOTH_DOM_IMPORT</value><name>Made in Canada from Domestic and Imported Ingredients</name><description>When a food contains both domestic and imported ingredients, the label would state "Made in Canada from domestic and imported ingredients". This claim may be used on a product that contains a mixture of imported and domestic ingredients, regardless of the level of Canadian content in the product.</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_BULK</value><name>Imported in bulk and packaged in Canada</name><description>To describe a food which is imported in bulk and packaged in Canada</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_CANNED</value><name>“Canned in Canada" to describe green beans</name><description>To describe green beans that were canned in Canada</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_DISTILLED</value><name>“Distilled in
Canada" to
describe
bottled water</name><description>To describe bottled water that was distilled in Canada</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_IMPORT</value><name>Made in Canada (a)</name><description>When a food is made with ingredients that are all sourced from outside of Canada, the label would state "Made in Canada from imported ingredients</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_INGREDIENT</value><name>Made with Canadian _(ingredient)_</name><description>The claim "Canadian" is considered to be the same as a "Product of Canada" claim. As such, all or virtually all major ingredients, processing, and labour used to make the food product must be Canadian. For example, the claim "Canadian" on a container of frozen lasagna would mean that the food meets the "Product of Canada" criteria.</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_MADE</value><name>Made in Canada</name><description>A "Made in Canada" claim with a qualifying statement can be used on a food product when the last substantial transformation of the product occurred in Canada, even if some ingredients are from other countries.</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_MUSTARD_SEEDS</value><name>Made with Canadian Mustard Seeds</name><description>The claim "Canadian" is considered to be the same as a "Product of Canada" claim. As such, all or virtually all major ingredients, processing, and labour used to make the food product must be Canadian. For example, the claim "Canadian" on a container of frozen lasagna would mean that the food meets the "Product of Canada" criteria</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_OATS</value><name>Made with 100% Canadian Oats</name><description>When the claim "100% Canadian" is used on a label, the food or ingredient to which the claim applies must be entirely Canadian rather than "all or virtually all" Canadian</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_PREPARED</value><name>"Prepared in Canada"</name><description>To describe a food which has been  intirely prepared in Canada</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_PROCESSED</value><name>"Processed in Canada"</name><description>To describe a food which has been entirely processed in Canada</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_PRODUCT</value><name>Product of Canada</name><description>A food product may use the claim "Product of Canada" when all or virtually all major ingredients, processing, and labour used to make the food product are Canadian. This means that all the significant ingredients in a food product are Canadian in origin and that non-Canadian material is negligible.</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_PROUD</value><name>Proudly Canadian</name><description>A claim such as "Proudly Made in Canada" would need a qualifying statement if the product contains imported ingredients as this claim includes the phrase "Made in Canada</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_REFINED</value><name>"Refined in Canada"</name><description>To describe imported cane sugar which has been refined in Canada;</description></code>
  <code><value>CA_ROASTED_BLENDED</value><name>“Roasted and
blended in
Canada"
to describe
coffee</name><description>To describe coffee since the coffee beans are always imported</description></code>
  <code><value>CAC_ABSENCE_EGG_MILK</value><name>Absence of Eggs and Milk is a Certified Allergen Control (CAC)</name><description>The Absence of Eggs and Milk  mark indicates that the product meets The Association quebecoise des allergies alimentaires (AQAA)'s Allergen Control (CAC) Mark of Conformity.  This program is intended for the food processing industry and aims to establish uniformity in allergen control measures in processed foods so that people directly or indirectly affected by food allergies can purchase safer products.</description></code>
  <code><value>CAC_ABSENCE_EGG_MILK_PEANUTS</value><name>Absence of Eggs, Milk and Peanuts is a Certified Allergen Control (CAC)</name><description>The Absence of Eggs, Milk and Peanuts  mark indicates that the product meets The Association quebecoise des allergies alimentaires (AQAA)'s Allergen Control (CAC) Mark of Conformity.  This program is intended for the food processing industry and aims to establish uniformity in allergen control measures in processed foods so that people directly or indirectly affected by food allergies can purchase safer products.</description></code>
  <code><value>CAC_ABSENCE_OF_ALMOND</value><name></name><description>The Absence of Almond mark indicates that the product meets The Association quebecoise des allergies alimentaires (AQAA)'s Allergen Control (CAC) Mark of Conformity.  This program is intended for the food processing industry and aims to establish uniformity in allergen control measures in processed foods so that people directly or indirectly affected by food allergies can purchase safer products. </description></code>
  <code><value>CAC_ABSENCE_OF_EGG</value><name></name><description>The Absence of Egg mark indicates that the product meets The Association quebecoise des allergies alimentaires (AQAA)'s Allergen Control (CAC) Mark of Conformity.  This program is intended for the food processing industry and aims to establish uniformity in allergen control measures in processed foods so that people directly or indirectly affected by food allergies can purchase safer products. 
</description></code>
  <code><value>CAC_ABSENCE_OF_MILK</value><name></name><description>The Absence of Milk mark indicates that the product meets The Association quebecoise des allergies alimentaires (AQAA)'s Allergen Control (CAC) Mark of Conformity.  This program is intended for the food processing industry and aims to establish uniformity in allergen control measures in processed foods so that people directly or indirectly affected by food allergies can purchase safer products. 
</description></code>
  <code><value>CAC_ABSENCE_OF_PEANUT</value><name></name><description>The Absence of Peanut mark indicates that the product meets The Association quebecoise des allergies alimentaires (AQAA)'s Allergen Control (CAC) Mark of Conformity.  This program is intended for the food processing industry and aims to establish uniformity in allergen control measures in processed foods so that people directly or indirectly affected by food allergies can purchase safer products</description></code>
  <code><value>CAC_ABSENCE_PEANUT_ALMOND</value><name>Absence of Peanuts &amp; Almonds is a Certified Allergen Control (CAC)</name><description>The Absence of  Peanuts &amp; Almonds mark indicates that the product meets The Association quebecoise des allergies alimentaires (AQAA)'s Allergen Control (CAC) Mark of Conformity.  This program is intended for the food processing industry and aims to establish uniformity in allergen control measures in processed foods so that people directly or indirectly affected by food allergies can purchase safer products.</description></code>
  <code><value>CAFE_PRACTICES</value><name>C.A.F.E. Practices</name><description>Coffee and Farmer Equity (C.A.F.E.) Practices evaluates, recognizes and rewards producers of high-quality sustainably grown coffee. C.A.F.E. Practices is a green coffee sourcing guideline with third-party evaluation. </description></code>
  <code><value>CAN_BNQ_CERTIFIED</value><name>CAN/ BNQ Certified</name><description>The Bureau de normalisation du Québec (BNQ) is accredited by the Standards Council of Canada (SCC) as a certification organization. This accreditation guarantees the BNQ’s impartiality in the process, and the BNQ’s compliance with SCC requirements, as well as those of the International Organization for Standardization (ISO) in terms of competence and ethical practices.</description></code>
  <code><value>CANADA_GAP</value><name>CanadaGAP program certification mark of conformity</name><description>CanadaGAP™ is a food safety program for companies that produce, pack and store fruits and vegetables. It is designed to help implement effective food safety procedures within fresh produce operations</description></code>
  <code><value>CANADIAN_AGRICULTURAL_PRODUCTS</value><name></name><description>Products which are identified by the Canadian Agricultural Products (CAP) Act, e.g. dairy, eggs, fruits, vegetables, honey, maple, meat, poultry, fish. http://laws-lois.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/c-0.4/page-6.html#h-8</description></code>
  <code><value>CANADIAN_ASSOCIATION_FIRE_CHIEFS_APPROVED</value><name>Canadian Association of Fire Chiefs Approved

</name><description>The Canadian Association of Fire Chiefs (CAFC) is an independent, non-profit organization with a voluntary membership representing approximately 3,500 fire departments across Canada. CAFC promotes the highest standard of public safety in an ever changing and increasingly complex world to ensure the protection of the public through leadership, advocacy and active collaboration with key stakeholders</description></code>
  <code><value>CANADIAN_CERTIFIED_COMPOSTABLE</value><name>Canadian Certified Compostable</name><description>The right to use the mark of conformity "COMPOSTABLE" on compostable plastic bags and on compostable products is granted only to those manufacturer/distributors that demonstrate that their product conforms with specific performance attributes and adheres to the parameters for "compostability" as set out in the BNQ documents, Compostable Plastic Bags - Certification Program 
</description></code>
  <code><value>CANADIAN_DERMATOLOGY_ASSOCIATION_SKIN_HEALTH</value><name>Recognized Canadian Dermatology Association Skin Health</name><description>The Skin Health Program’s framework is based, in large part, on the CDA’s longstanding and successful Sun Protection Program (SPP).  However, the scope of the Skin Health Program is much broader. The SHP was created to effectively fill a need expressed to us by consumers and industry for the development of an effective evidence-based program that reflects the most recent available dermatological science. The SHP will help people navigate the variety of products on the market designed to enhance and maintain skin health.</description></code>
  <code><value>CANADIAN_DERMATOLOGY_ASSOCIATION_SUN_PROTECTION</value><name>Recognized Canadian Dermatology Association Sun Protection</name><description>The Canadian Dermatology Association, founded in 1925, represents Canadian dermatologists.  The association exists to advance the science and art of medicine and surgery related to the care of the skin, hair and nails; provide continuing professional development for its members; support and advance patient care; provide public education on sun protection and other aspects of skin health; and promote a lifetime of healthier skin, hair and nails.</description></code>
  <code><value>CARBON_FOOTPRINT_STANDARD</value><name>Carbon Footprint Standard</name><description>Carbon Footprint Ltd is ISO14001 certified for environmental management and has a Quality Management System certified to ISO 9001:2008. PAS 2060 Carbon Neutrality programme meets the British Standard Institute (BSI)'s specification on carbon neutrality. </description></code>
  <code><value>CARBON_NEUTRAL</value><name>Carbon Neutral</name><description>CarbonNeutral® certification, from The CarbonNeutral Company, is the global standard for businesses, products or services that have measured, reduced and offset their carbon emissions to net zero, set out in accordance with the rules and regulations of the CarbonNeutral Protocol.</description></code>
  <code><value>CARBON_NEUTRAL_NCOS_CERTIFIED</value><name>Carbon Neutral NCOS Certified</name><description>The Carbon Neutral Certified by NCOS certification attribute includes all products that have published the Carbon Neutral Certified seal by NCOS (National Carbon Offset Standard) on their packaging.</description></code>
  <code><value>CRUELTY_FREE_PETA</value><name>Cruelty Free PETA</name><description>"PETA People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) is the largest animal rights organization in the world, with more than 6.5 million members and supporters.

PETA focuses its attention on the four areas in which the largest numbers of animals suffer the most intensely for the longest periods of time: in laboratories, in the food industry, in the clothing trade, and in the entertainment industry. We also work on a variety of other issues, including the cruel killing of rodents, birds, and other animals who are often considered “pests” as well as cruelty to domesticated animals.https://www.peta.org/living/personal-care-fashion/beauty-without-bunnies/"</description></code>
  <code><value>CARING_CONSUMER_PETA</value><name>Caring Consumer PETA</name><description>Companies that manufacture kind cosmetics, personal-care products, and household cleaners must answer our questions and sign a statement of assurance verifying that they do not conduct, commission, or pay for any tests on animals for ingredients, formulations, or finished products anywhere in the world. They also pledge not to do so in the future. Once they are certified, companies can use our logos on their products, packaging, website, and materials to promote their animal-friendly values. </description></code>
  <code><value>CCA_GLUTEN_FREE</value><name></name><description>Gluten Free Certification Program is available to those manufacturers &amp; brand owners who produce gluten-free products. Manufacturers must comply with regulations governing gluten-free claims as set out by the Canadian Government.</description></code>
  <code><value>CCC</value><name>China Compulsory Certification</name><description>“CCC” is the abbreviation of “China Compulsory Certification”, more commonly known as “3C Certification” or “3C Certificate”, a conformity assessment system of market access, is implemented by Chinese government in line with the international practices to assess products’ conformity with national compulsory standards and technical specifications. It is a mandatory requirement imposed on certain products sold in China market. For the list of madatory products, visit http://www.ccc-certificate.org/en/renzhengzhidu/qiangzhixingchanpinmubi</description></code>
  <code><value>CCF_RABBIT</value><name>CCF Rabbit Certification </name><description>CCF Rabbit Certification includes all products that present a CCF Rabbit Not Tested on Animal logo.  </description></code>
  <code><value>CCOF</value><name></name><description>California Certified Organic Farmers (CCOF) is a full-service organic certification agency and trade association passionate about being the leading voice for organic, and certifying, educating, advocating, and promoting organic.</description></code>
  <code><value>CEBEC</value><name></name><description>CEBEC is a Belgian label for electrical low voltage (1,000 V). It indicates that compliance is met with the rules applicable to such equipment from the European Union (including the Low Voltage Directive).</description></code>
  <code><value>CEL</value><name>Canadian Eco Logo</name><description>The Canadian EcoLogo (also known as Environmental Choice) helps you identify products and services that have been independently certified to meet strict environmental standards that reflect their entire life cycle — from manufacturing to disposal. EcoLogo standards are designed so that only the top 20% of products available on the market can achieve certification. More than 7,000 products — from paint to paper — carry this logo.</description></code>
  <code><value>CELIAC_SPRUE_ASSOCIATION</value><name>Celiac Sprue Association</name><description>The Celiac Support Association certification represents a company's manufacturing practices to reduce the risk of allergen contamination for celiac and gluten sensitive customers. Products with this certification are tested using the most sensitive validated testing method to ensure it's gluten free status. This recognition seal also indicates the company's commitment to communicating product information to the consumer. </description></code>
  <code><value>CENTRAL_RABBINICAL_CONGRESS_KOSHER</value><name>Central Rabbinical Congress Kosher</name><description>Central Rabbinical Congress Kosher Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIE_TERROIR_CHARLEVOIX</value><name>Certifie Terroir Charlevoix</name><description>A certification program to promote the products meet the original criteria of agricultural and food products of the Charlevoix terroir.</description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_ANGUS_BEEF</value><name></name><description>A package mark awarded to products that meet the certification criteria defined by Certified Angus Beef®</description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_B_CORPORATION</value><name>Certified B Corporation</name><description>Certified B Corporations voluntarily meet the highest standards of verified, overall social and environmental performance, public transparency, and legal accountability. B Corps are certified by the non-profit organisation B Lab.</description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_CARBON_FREE</value><name>Certified Carbon Free</name><description>Certified Carbon Free by Carbonfund is the 1st carbon neutral label in the US. It indicates the product is environmentally-friendly and carbon neutral. </description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_HUMANE_ORGANISATION</value><name>Certified Humane Organisation</name><description>Humane Farm Animal Care (HFAC) is the leading non-profit certification organisation dedicated to improving the lives of farm animals in food production from birth through slaughter. The goal of the program is to improve the lives of farm animals by driving consumer demand for kinder and more responsible farm animal practices. When you see the Certified Humane Raised and Handled label on a product you can be assured that the food products have come from facilities that meet precise, objective standards for farm animal treatment.</description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_NATURALLY_GROWN</value><name>Certified Naturally Grown</name><description>Certified Naturally Grown attribute includes all products that present a Certified Naturally Grown logo. </description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_OE_100</value><name></name><description>The OE 100 standard is a chain-of-custody standard that gives third party verification to a final product containing a given amount of organically grown cotton.</description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_ORGANIC_BAYSTATE_ORGANIC_CERTIFIERS</value><name>Certified Organic Baystate Organic Certifiers</name><description>Baystate Organic Certifiers is a USDA National Organic Program accredited certifying agent certifying farm and processing operations throughout the continental United States. </description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_ORGANIC_BY_ORGANIC_CERTIFIERS</value><name>Certified Organic By Organic Certifiers</name><description>Organic Certifiers is USDA, ISO 17065, EU Equivalent, COR (Canadian Organic Regimen) accredited, and has been certifying the organic community since 1996. Organic Certifiers was one of the first accredited by the USDA in early 2002. </description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_PALEO</value><name>Certified Paleo</name><description>"The Paleo Foundation was first organized for the purpose of helping Paleo Diet Adherents easily identify products that met the basic tenets of the diet. Certified Paleo certifies products that contain Paleo Diet ingredients, but have some 21st century processing methods allowing for shelf stability. https://paleofoundation.com"</description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_PALEO_FRIENDLY</value><name>Certified Paleo Friendly</name><description>The Paleo Foundation offers The Paleo Friendly Program for products that are generally regarded as grey-area products such as kombucha, dark chocolate, and even grass-fed dairy. Some restrictions apply. </description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_WBENC</value><name>Certified WBENC</name><description>WBENC Certification validates that the business is 51 percent owned, controlled, operated, and managed by a woman or women. WBENC Certification gives women owned businesses the ability to compete for real-time business opportunities provided by WBENC Corporate Members and government agencies. </description></code>
  <code><value>CERTIFIED_WILDLIFE_FRIENDLY</value><name>Certified Wildlife Friendly</name><description>Products may be certified by WFEN if: 
The product contributes directly to in situ conservation of key species.
Production has a positive impact on the local economy.
Individuals or communities living with wildlife participate in the production, harvest, processing or manufacture of the product.
The product’s conservation mission includes a clear enforcement mechanism, such that failure to follow through with required conservation actions results in immediate consequences, including forfeiture of any economic reward. </description></code>
  <code><value>CFG_PROCESSED_EGG</value><name>Canadian Federal Government – Processed Egg Products</name><description>National trademarks under the Canada Agricultural Products Act and the Meat Inspection Act</description></code>
  <code><value>CFIA</value><name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) as Federally Registered &amp; Inspected Facility e.g., meat</name><description>National trademarks under the Canada Agricultural Products Act and the Meat Inspection Act</description></code>
  <code><value>CFIA_DAIRY</value><name>Canadian Federal Government – Dairy Product
Grade</name><description>National trademarks under the Canada Agricultural Products Act and the Meat Inspection Act</description></code>
  <code><value>CFIA_FISH</value><name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) as Federally Registered &amp; Inspected Facility - Fish</name><description>National trademarks under the Canada Agricultural Products Act and the Meat Inspection Act</description></code>
  <code><value>CFIA_GRADE_A</value><name>Canadian Federal Government – CFIA Grade Stamps Canada A e.g. poultry &amp; eggs</name><description>National trademarks under the Canada Agricultural Products Act and the Meat Inspection Act</description></code>
  <code><value>CFIA_GRADE_C</value><name>Canadian Federal Government – CFIA  Grade Stamps Canada C e.g. poultry &amp; eggs</name><description>National trademarks under the Canada Agricultural Products Act and the Meat Inspection Act</description></code>
  <code><value>CFIA_ORGANIC</value><name>Canada Organic Canadian Organic Logo</name><description>The Canadian Organic Logo symbolizes products that are organic certified by the Canadian Food Inspection Agency. The use of the organic logo is only permitted on products that have an organic content that is greater than or equal to 95% and have been certified according to the requirements of the Canada Organic Regime.</description></code>
  <code><value>CFIA_UTILITY_POULTRY_EGG</value><name>Canadian Federal Government – CFIA Grade Stamps Canada Utility e.g. poultry &amp; eggs</name><description>National trademarks under the Canada Agricultural Products Act and the Meat Inspection Act</description></code>
  <code><value>CHASSEURS_DE_FRANCE</value><name>Chasseurs de France</name><description>The National Federation of Hunters (FNC) is a French fighter organization.

It is chaired by Willy Schraen, who is also president of the departmental federation of hunters of the Pas-de-Calais, since August 2016. It brings together all the departmental and regional federations of hunters and represents approximately 1.1 million French hunters.</description></code>
  <code><value>CHEESE_WORLD_CHAMPION_CHEESE_CONTEST</value><name>Cheese – World Champion Cheese Contest</name><description>The World Championship Cheese Contest  is the largest technical cheese, butter, and yogurt competition in the world.  The contest organized by Wisconsin Cheese Makers Association.</description></code>
  <code><value>CHICAGO_RABBINICAL_COUNCIL</value><name>Chicago Rabbinical Council</name><description>Chicago Rabbinical Council Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>CLIMATE_NEUTRAL</value><name>Climate Neutral</name><description>The Climate Neutral Guaranteed standard gives you the acknowledgement that the results of your work are helping and are meaningful. The steps that have been taken are expertly tested against published criteria in a transparent process. With the logo, you can clearly communicate your commitment to your stakeholders, who are becoming more critical when it comes to socially, ecologically and economically responsible business. The Climate Neutral Group has offices in the Netherlands an South-Africa.</description></code>
  <code><value>CLIMATE_NEUTRAL_PARTNER</value><name>Climate neutral partner</name><description>"The Climate Neutral label Indicates that Climate Partner guarantees that all carbon emissions of the product have been calculated and offset via recognised carbon offset projects.

"</description></code>
  <code><value>CNG</value><name>Certified Naturally Grown (CNG)</name><description>Certified Naturally Grown (CNG) offers peer-review certification to farmers and beekeepers producing food for their local communities by working in harmony with nature, without relying on synthetic chemicals or GMOs</description></code>
  <code><value>CO2LOGIC_CO2_NEUTRAL_CERTIFIED</value><name>CO2 Neutral Certified</name><description>The CO2 neutral label by CO2logic is meant to provide both customers and companies with a basic understanding of the CO2 neutrality concept, based on the internationally recognised PAS2060 standard. This website helps them fully grasp, appreciate and recognise the benefits and challenges of the ‘CO2 Neutral’ approach. </description></code>
  <code><value>COCOA_HORIZONS</value><name>Cocoa Horizons</name><description>Cocoa Horizons is an impact driven program focused on cocoa farmer prosperity and helping build self-sustaining farming communities that protect nature and children. The purpose is to improve the livelihoods of cocoa farmers and their communities through the promotion of sustainable, entrepreneurial farming, improved productivity, and community development, which protects nature and children.</description></code>
  <code><value>COCOA_LIFE</value><name>Cocoa Life</name><description>Cocoa Life is farmer-centric, empowered by strong partnerships, and aligned with our sourcing. These three non-negotiable principles inform every choice we make, every goal we set, and every initiative we launch.</description></code>
  <code><value>COMPOSTABLE_DIN_CERTCO</value><name></name><description>DIN CERTCO Gesellschaft für Konformitätsbewertung mbH offers the certification of compostable products of biologically degradable materials and assigns for this the label developed by the European Bioplastics (formerly Interessengemeinschaft biologisch abbaubare Werkstoffe e.V.)</description></code>
  <code><value>COMTE_GREEN_BELL</value><name>Comte green bell</name><description>Comté is a hard raw milk cheese from the French region of Franche-Comté. Its production area extends to the departments of Jura, Doubs and eastern Ain.</description></code>
  <code><value>CONFORMITE_EUROPEENNE</value><name>Conformité Européenne (CE) – EU Conformance</name><description>The letters ‘CE’ appear on many products traded on the extended Single Market in the European Economic Area (EEA). They signify that products sold in the EEA have been assessed to meet high safety, health, and environmental protection requirements. When you buy a new phone, a teddy bear, or a TV within the EEA, you can find the CE mark on them. CE marking also supports fair competition by holding all companies accountable to the same rules.</description></code>
  <code><value>CONSUMER_CHOICE_AWARD</value><name>Consumer Choice Award</name><description>Consumer Choice Award  recognizes business excellence in small and medium sized businesses.  They only organization in Canada to conduct statistically accurate independent market research surveys to determine brand reputation, customer satisfaction and business excellence</description></code>
  <code><value>COR_DETROIT</value><name>Council of Orthodox Rabbis of Greater Detroit Certification </name><description>Council of Orthodox Rabbis of Greater Detroit Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>COR_KOSHER</value><name>Kashruth Council of Canada Kosher Certification</name><description>Kashruth Council of Canada (COR) Kosher Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>CORRUGATED_RECYCLES</value><name>Corrugated Recycles</name><description>The UK Corrugated Industry have been running a continuous campaign for some time to highlight and raise awareness of the recyclability of cardboard boxes, they have done this by creating an internationally recognised logo which is to be placed on all manufactured recyclable boxes</description></code>
  <code><value>COSMEBIO</value><name></name><description>COSMEBIO is the Professional Association for Natural, Ecological and Organic cosmetics. COSMEBIO federates the professional players in the industry and brings together over 390 members in France and abroad. Since 2002, COSMEBIO has been working to promote natural and ecological cosmetics made with ingredients from organic farming and developed using green technologies (green chemistry). http://www.cosmebio.org/en/ .</description></code>
  <code><value>COSMEBIO_COSMOS_NATURAL</value><name>Cosmebio COSMOS natural</name><description>The Cosmebio COSMOS natural signature is available for products that comply with the COSMOS-standard in all respects but do not meet the required minimum organic percentages as specified in the COSMOS-standard.</description></code>
  <code><value>COSMEBIO_COSMOS_ORGANIC</value><name>Cosmebio COSMOS organic</name><description>The Cosmebio COSMOS organic signature is available for products that comply with the COSMOS-standard in all respects and contain the required percentages of organic ingredients as specified in the COSMOS-standard.</description></code>
  <code><value>COTTON_MADE_IN_AFRICA</value><name></name><description>Cotton made in Africa is the first, and as yet the only initiative of the Aid by Trade Foundation. It improves the conditions of life of cotton farmers and their families in Africa, and contributes to environmental protection by promoting sustainable methods of cultivation.</description></code>
  <code><value>CPE_SCHARREL_EIEREN</value><name></name><description>Eggs with this Dutch packaging mark are from chicken that are held according to certain quality standards.</description></code>
  <code><value>CPE_VRIJE_UITLOOP_EIEREN</value><name></name><description>Eggs with this Dutch packaging Mark are from chicken that have the possibility for free range in  open air.</description></code>
  <code><value>CRADLE_TO_CRADLE</value><name>Cradle To Cradle</name><description>The Cradle to Cradle Certified Product Standard guides designers and manufacturers through a continual improvement process that looks at a product through five quality categories - material health, material reutilization, renewable energy and carbon management, water stewardship, and social fairness. A product receives an achievement level in each category - Basic, Bronze, Silver, Gold, or Platinum - with the lowest achievement level representing the product's overall mark. </description></code>
  <code><value>CROSSED_GRAIN_SYMBOL</value><name></name><description>Crossed grain logo is a trademark owned and administered by Coeliac. It is a wolrdwide symbol for safe gluten-free foods. Each country has their own Coeliac website for example UK www.coeliac.org.uk</description></code>
  <code><value>CROWN_CHK</value><name>Bais Din of Crown Heights Vaad HaKashrus Certification </name><description>Bais Din of Crown Heights Vaad HaKashrus Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>CSA_INTERNATIONAL</value><name></name><description>CSA International tests products for compliance to national and international standards, and issue certification marks for qualified products. Certification marks tell potential customers and users that a product has been evaluated by a formal process-involving examination, testing and follow-up inspection-and that it complies with applicable standards for safety and performance. </description></code>
  <code><value>CSA_NCA_GLUTEN_FREE</value><name>CSA/NCA - Gluten Free</name><description>NCA has become the recognized education and advocacy group for people with celiac disease and other gluten-related disorders.</description></code>
  <code><value>CSI</value><name>Organic Certifying Body - Centre for Systems Integration,</name><description>As an independent, not-for-profit organization, CSI is able to offer programs and services to augment and support the work of regulatory officials, including standards development, and certification system development.</description></code>
  <code><value>CZECH_FOOD</value><name>Czech Food</name><description>This logo can be only used on labels of food products made only or mostly from Czech ingredients and manufactured in the Czech Republic. Rules for using the logo are maintained by the Ministry of Agriculture of the Czech Republic and they are available at http://eagri.cz/public/web/mze/potraviny/znacky-kvality-potravin/ceska-potravina/ .
</description></code>
  <code><value>DALLAS_KOSHER</value><name>Dallas Kosher Certification</name><description>Dallas Kosher Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>DANSK_IP_KVALITET</value><name>Dansk IP Kvalitet</name><description>The objective of Danish I.P. gardeners and growers are producing fruits and vegetables of high quality in a holistic manner that is prudent to both nature and man.
Integrated Production requires, e.g.. taking advantage of the natural regulatory and useful mechanisms in nature. The goal is to reduce the use of pesticides and fertilizer to the bare minimum. Documentation and independent control is the guarantee of security. Nothing is left to chance when Danish fruit and vegetables is grown by I.P. method.</description></code>
  <code><value>DANSK_MAELK</value><name>Dansk Maelk</name><description>The purpose of DANSK MÆLK marque is to determine that the products sold - using the DANSK MÆLK marque - originates from Danish milk, is produced and packaged in Denmark. The DANSK MÆLK marque is owned by Danish Dairy Board (Mejeriforeningen). The DANSK MÆLK marque may only be used for milk, dairy and drinking milk products. Only members of the Dairy Board can use the DANSK MÆLK marque.</description></code>
  <code><value>DEBIO</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Debio</name><description>All providers of organic products in Norway are certified by Debio. We ensure that farms and fish farms, processing and marketing enterprises, importers and others follow the regulations for organic production, and meet the requirements for marketing organic products under Debio’s Ø-label. - See more at: http://www.debio.no/information-in-english#sthash.TttuMTn9.dpuf</description></code>
  <code><value>DEMETER_LABEL</value><name></name><description>Demeter International trademark for products of certified biodynamic production. Www.demeter.net</description></code>
  <code><value>DESIGN_FOR_THE_ENVIRONMENT</value><name>Design for the Environment (DFE)</name><description>The Design for the Environment Safer Product Labeling Program advances the United States Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) mission to protect human health and the environment. The program uses EPA's chemical knowledge and resources to carefully evaluate products and to label only those that have met the program's leadership standard. </description></code>
  <code><value>DESIGN_FROM_FINLAND</value><name>Design From Finland</name><description>Finnish label for designing.</description></code>
  <code><value>DIAMOND_K</value><name>Diamond K - Massachusetts Certification </name><description>Diamond K - Massachusetts Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>DIAMOND_KA_KASHRUT_AUTHORITY_OF_AUSTRALIA_AND_NZ</value><name>Diamond Ka Kashrut Authority Of Australia And Nz</name><description>The Kashrut Authority of Australia and NZ Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>DK_ECO</value><name> Ø-mærke </name><description>The red Ø-mærke with the text "Statskontrolleret økologisk", tells that the Danish authorities have been controlling the farm or the company which have processed, packed or marked an organic product.</description></code>
  <code><value>DLG_AWARD</value><name></name><description>DLG award in bronze, silver and gold. The DLG promotes product quality of foods on the basis of binding and impartial quality standards, based on current scientific findings and the recognised test methods it has developed. With its International Tests the DLG leads quality assessment in Europe and is accredited in accordance with international norms.</description></code>
  <code><value>DLG_CERTIFIED_ALLERGEN_MANAGEMENT</value><name>DLG certified allergen management</name><description>Indicates that on the basis of the allergen management and risk assessment, the product is assessed that it will not cause allergic reactions in the majority of the allergic population. The label "DLG-certified allergen management" is awarded by the DLG TestService GmbH in cooperation with the German Allergy and Asthma Federation e.V. (DAAB).</description></code>
  <code><value>DNV_BUSINESS_ASSURANCE</value><name>DNV - Business Assurance</name><description>DNV Business Assurance part of DNV GL (Det Norske Veritas) "the Norwegian truth" is one of the world's leading certification bodies, helping businesses assure the performance of their organization, products, people, facilities and supply chains through certification, verification, assessment, and training services. They certify the compliance of companies according to a third party standard, such as ISO 9001 (quality management system) or ISO 14001 (environmental management system). </description></code>
  <code><value>DOLPHIN_SAFE</value><name></name><description>The Earth Island Institute monitors tuna companies around the world to ensure the tuna is caught by methods that do not harm dolphins and protect the marine ecosystem.</description></code>
  <code><value>DRP</value><name>Dermatology Review Panel ™ ("DRP") independent dermatologist’s review</name><description>The Dermatology Review Panel™, a division of DRP Dermatology Inc. ("DRP") has been formed to provide an independent dermatologists' review of non-prescription skin care products (includes over-the-counter and other consumer products with skin care-related claims).</description></code>
  <code><value>DUURZAAM_VARKENSVLEES</value><name></name><description>This label is awarded to farmers that comply with strict regulations for the well-being of both pigs and the environment. The compliance to these guidelines is reviewed yearly by independent certification bodies.




</description></code>
  <code><value>DVF_VEGAN</value><name>DVF (Dansk Vegetarisk Forening) Vegan</name><description>The label of 'Vegan' from the The Vegetarian Society of Denmark, also known as Dansk Vegetarisk Forening (DVF), is a label to trust with stricter requirements than most other vegan labels. Besides the normal requirements for vegan, then products are not allowed to be tested on animals either for this vegan label. The logo is a registered trademark.</description></code>
  <code><value>DVF_VEGETARIAN</value><name>DVF (Dansk Vegetarisk Forening) Vegetarian</name><description>"The label of 'Vegetarian' from the The Vegetarian Society of Denmark, also known as Dansk Vegetarisk Forening (DVF), is a label to trust with stricter requirements than most other vegetarian labels. Besides the normal requirements for vegetarian, then any product from animals should be organic for this vegetarian label. The logo is a registered trademark.

"</description></code>
  <code><value>DYRENES_BESKYTTELSE</value><name>Dyrenes Beskyttelse </name><description>The requirements for the label "Recommended by Animal Protection Association " is focused on animal welfare in production, transport and accommodation at the slaughterhouse and may be summarized in five points:
1. Animals must always have the freedom to move freely and be able to exhibit normal behaviour.
2. Animals must not be harmed physically or mentally.
3. Animals must not starve, but should have free access to natural feedstuffs and water so that they can maintain good health and vigour.
4. Animals must not be unnecessarily exposed to infection or suffer any harm.
5. Animals must not in any way be intimidated or unduly stressed.</description></code>
  <code><value>DZG_GLUTEN_FREE</value><name></name><description>The German Coeliac Society (Deutsche Zöliakiegesellschaft – DZG) was founded 1974. Today the DZG has more than 40,000 members. The aim is to help people with coeliac disease or with Dermatitis Herpetiformis Duhring. The organisation also try to increase the publicity of coeliac disease and to improve the living conditions for coeliacs in Germany. </description></code>
  <code><value>EARTHKOSHER_KOSHER</value><name>EarthKosher Kosher Certification </name><description>EarthKosher Kosher Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>EARTHSURE</value><name></name><description>Earthsure is the Ecolabel program of IERE. It provides environmental product declarations, or Environmental Product Declarations.  Much like a nutrition label the EPD shows some or all of the following impacts:
climate change, depletion of the stratospheric ozone layer, acidification of land and water sources &amp; other impacts. </description></code>
  <code><value>ECO_KREIS</value><name></name><description>Corresponds to  printers and fax machines, for the health and environmental criteria audited by TÜV Rheinland: www.tuv.com.</description></code>
  <code><value>ECO_LABEL_CZECH</value><name>Eco Label Czech</name><description>Mark accredited to products with low impact on environment. It is accredited by CENIA - Czech Environmental Information Agency of the Ministry of Environment of the Czech Republic.</description></code>
  <code><value>ECO_LABEL_LADYBUG</value><name></name><description>This is a Finnish label used by the Organic union, which represents the entire Finnish organic industry, consumers and producers in a common interest group. They work as a neutral voice in various working groups and consultations, and prepare position papers and presentations. The Federation also organizes training events and professional seminars. The Organic Federation also publishes the magazine Organic.</description></code>
  <code><value>ECO_LOGO</value><name></name><description>Formerly known as Environmental Choice. North America's leading benchmark of environmentally responsible products and services.</description></code>
  <code><value>ECOCERT_CERTIFICATE</value><name></name><description>ECOCERT is a certification body for sustainable development. Www.ecocert.com</description></code>
  <code><value>ECOCERT_COSMOS_NATURAL</value><name></name><description>The COSMOS-standard certification was officially launched at the Biofach in February. The COSMOS-standard is a new cosmetic certification developed to harmonize various certifications and labels in order to create one standard that is internationally recognized for natural and organic cosmetics. The new certification is a result of Europe’s leading natural cosmetic certifiers coming together and forming a non-profit association, COSMOS-standard AISBL.</description></code>
  <code><value>ECOCERT_COSMOS_ORGANIC</value><name></name><description>The COSMOS-standard certification was officially launched at the Biofach in February. The COSMOS-standard is a new cosmetic certification developed to harmonize various certifications and labels in order to create one standard that is internationally recognized for natural and organic cosmetics. The new certification is a result of Europe’s leading natural cosmetic certifiers coming together and forming a non-profit association, COSMOS-standard AISBL.</description></code>
  <code><value>ECOCERT_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – EcoCert, Quebec, Canada</name><description>Ecocert (Canada) is a control and certification organization that certifies organic products in Canada with its Ecocert label. It is managed by a private corporation based in Quebec, but that operates Canada-wide and is independent from all commercial entities</description></code>
  <code><value>ECOGARANTIE</value><name></name><description> Ecogarantie is an international mark for ecological products. Ecogarantie has developed standards for cosmetics, personal care, washing- and cleaning products and salt. Consumers can rely on the fact that products with the Ecogarantie label, meet strict requirements whose goal it is to guarantee quality, safety and durability for generations to come. http://www.ecogarantie.com/en .</description></code>
  <code><value>ECOLAND</value><name>ECOLAND</name><description>The Ecoland label stands for regional production, sustainable agriculture and social commitment. Products with this label have not been treated with chemical pesticides or synthetic fertilizers. Producers commits itself to promote the biodiversity of their area, to preserve soil fertility and to use water-efficient irrigation systems. All organic farmers are controlled in accordance with the strict requirements of the EU Organic Regulation and the guidelines of the Ecoland-Verband. This is done by state-approved inspection bodies, which are supervised by the state control authorities
</description></code>
  <code><value>ECOLOGO_CERTIFIED</value><name>The EcoLogo Certification</name><description>The EcoLogo certification attribute includes all products that have published the EcoLogo Certified seal on their packaging. </description></code>
  <code><value>ECOVIN</value><name></name><description>The ecovin label certifies wines produced with ecological production methods based on the EU eco regulation.</description></code>
  <code><value>ECZEMA_SOCIETY_OF_CANADA</value><name>Eczema Society of Canada- Accepted</name><description>Products that are identified as ‘accepted’ by the Eczema Society are free of ingredients know to be irritating for sensitive skin, have undergone dermatologist formulation review, and have earned our Seal of Acceptance.</description></code>
  <code><value>EESTI_OKOMARK</value><name></name><description>Estonian Eco Label: Ministry of Agriculture Ökomärk (Label of Organic Food). www.agri.ee</description></code>
  <code><value>EESTI_PARIM_TOIDUAINE</value><name></name><description>Best Food  - Association of Estonia Food Industry http://www.toiduliit.ee/ Our mission is to support and promote Estonian food industry and economy, and contribute to a balanced and appropriate ethics to members of a favorable business environment for development.</description></code>
  <code><value>EKO</value><name></name><description>This symbol stands for organic production certified by Skal that meets the requirements of the EU-regulation for organic production. Skal is the inspection body for the organic production in the Netherlands.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENEC</value><name></name><description>ENEC is a European high quality mark for lighting equipment and related products and stands for European Norms Electrical Certification. ENEC is an alternative to the national marks within the entire European Union. This mark eliminates a producer the need for a separate label in each individual country. Each European country there are 1 or more independent testing bodies that are appointed to issue the ENEC certification mark to a product.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_A</value><name>Energy label A</name><description>Energy label A The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_A+</value><name>Energy label A+</name><description>Energy label A+ The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_A++</value><name>Energy label A++</name><description>Energy label A++ The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_A+++</value><name>Energy label A+++</name><description>Energy label A+++ The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_B</value><name>Energy label B</name><description>Energy label B The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_C</value><name>Energy label C</name><description>Energy label C The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_D</value><name>Energy label D</name><description>Energy label D The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_E</value><name>Energy label E</name><description>Energy label E The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_F</value><name>Energy label F</name><description>Energy label F The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_LABEL_G</value><name>Energy label G</name><description>Energy label G The EU energy label gives information about the energy efficiency of a product. The label rates products from dark green (most efficient) to red (least efficient). The label also shows total energy consumption and provides other information relevant to that product. Examples of products are lamps (light bulbs) and electric household appliances.</description></code>
  <code><value>ENERGY_STAR</value><name></name><description>ENERGY STAR is a voluntary government-backed program dedicated to helping individuals protect the environment through energy efficiency. The ENERGY STAR mark is the national symbol for energy efficiency, making it easy for consumers and businesses to identify high-quality, energy-efficient products, homes, and commercial and industrial buildings. </description></code>
  <code><value>EPA_DFE</value><name>Design for the Environment (DfE)</name><description>The Safer Choice label, it means that every ingredient in the product has been reviewed by EPA scientists. Only products that meet our Safer Choice Standard, which includes stringent human health and environmental criteria, are allowed to carry the label.</description></code>
  <code><value>EPEAT_BRONZE</value><name></name><description>Electronic Product Environmental Assessment Tool</description></code>
  <code><value>EPEAT_GOLD</value><name></name><description>Electronic Product Environmental Assessment Tool</description></code>
  <code><value>EPEAT_SILVER</value><name></name><description>Electronic Product Environmental Assessment Tool</description></code>
  <code><value>EQUAL_EXCHANGE_FAIRLY_TRADED</value><name>Equal Exchange Fairly Traded</name><description>Equal Exchange's mission is to build long-term trade partnerships that are economically just and environmentally sound, to foster mutually beneficial relationships between farmers and consumers and to demonstrate, through our success, the contribution of worker co-operatives and Fair Trade to a more equitable, democratic and sustainable world. </description></code>
  <code><value>ERDE_SAAT</value><name></name><description>The label of Bioberband Earth &amp; Seed indicates organic agriculture that interacts in a constructive and life-enhancing way with natural systems and cycles.</description></code>
  <code><value>ERKEND_STREEK_PRODUCT</value><name></name><description>The Dutch mark Erkend Streekproduct indicates that the product and its ingredients come from a specific region. During production there has been attention for preservation and maintenance of characteristic values of the landscape and the environment.</description></code>
  <code><value>ETP</value><name>Ethical Tea Partnership</name><description>Membership is open to any company involved in the sourcing, trading or packing of tea sold in Europe, North America, Australia and New Zealand.
When you see the ETP Hand and Leaf logo on packaging it means the tea inside is from a member of Ethical Tea Partnership. Members range from large global brands and retailers to small boutique labels and specialty teas.
Because we focus purely on improving the sustainability of tea production – and not herbs, the ETP logo can only be used on products that contain a minimum of 55% Camellia sinensis (tea) by weight.
</description></code>
  <code><value>EU_ECO_LABEL</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked with the European Union Eco label a European environmental initiative supported by the European Commission.</description></code>
  <code><value>EU_ENERGY_LABEL</value><name></name><description> The EU adopted the Directive 2010/30/EU on energy labels. Energy labels help consumers choosing products which save energy and thus money. They also provide incentives for the industry to develop and invest in energy efficient product design.</description></code>
  <code><value>EU_ORGANIC_FARMING</value><name></name><description>New EU organic logo the EU introduced a new organic logo to ensure consumer protection and common standards. See www.organic-farming.europa.eu</description></code>
  <code><value>EUROPEAN_V_LABEL_VEGAN</value><name>V Label Vegan</name><description>The V-label is an internationally approved and protected brand to identify vegetarian and vegan products. Owner of the trademark "V-Label" is the European Vegetarian Union (EVU), which coordinates the work of the various national Veggie organisations.
Today the Vegetarier-Bund Deutschlands e.V. (VEBU) is the biggest body representing the interests of vegetarians and vegans in Germany and the VEBU awards the certification of the two existing Versions of the V-Label.
It support consumer decision buying Food without studying the  list of ingredients. 

Vegan food products are not of animal origin and  don't have                  
- Ingredients (including additives, excipients, flavourings and enzymes) of animal origin
or
- Processing aids or
- Non-food additives, used in the same manner as Processing aids of animal origin.
</description></code>
  <code><value>EUROPEAN_V_LABEL_VEGETARIAN</value><name>V Label Vegetarian</name><description>The V-LABEL is an internationally approved and protected brand to identify vegetarian and vegan products. Owner of the trademark  "V-LABEL" is the European Vegetarian Union (EVU), which coordinates the work of the various national Veggie organisations.
Today the Vegetarier-Bund Deutschlands e.V. (VEBU) is the biggest body representing the interests of vegetarians and vegans in Germany and the VEBU awards the certification of the two existing Versions of the V-LABEL.
It support consumer decision buying Food without studying the  list of ingredients. 

Vegetarian foods meet the requirements of vegan food.  
In the production, however, the following components or derived products can be added or used:
1. milk
2. colostrum
3. means eggs
4. honey
5. beeswax
6. propolis 
7. lanolin / lanolin from live sheep from wool.</description></code>
  <code><value>EUROPEAN_VEGETARIAN_UNION</value><name>European Vegetarian Union</name><description>The V Label is intended for the labelling of vegetarian and vegan products. The V Label makes it possible to safely and conveniently select vegetarian and vegan food without having to study the ingredients or make enquiries with the manufacturer. Products bearing the V Label must not contain any of the following ingredients: - Meat, fish and poultry - Ingredients that are produced from dead animals such as gelatine and fish oil - Eggs from hens kept in cages - Gelatine for the clarification of juices or vinegar - Calf-rennet for the production of cheese The V Label always states the vegetarian category the labelled product belongs to. The label must at least indicate the category “vegetarian” or “vegan”. Vegetarian products with milk and without egg can be labelled “lacto-vegetarian” (or “without eggs”) and vegetarian products with egg and without milk can be labelled “ovo-vegetarian” (or “without milk”).</description></code>
  <code><value>EWG_VERIFIED</value><name>EWG Verified</name><description>The EWG VERIFIED™ mark, from Environmental Working Group (EWG), helps shoppers in stores and online to quickly and easily identify cosmetics and other personal care products which: avoid EWG's ingredients of concern, provide full transparency, and use good manufacturing practices.</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIR_FLOWERS_FAIR_PLANTS</value><name>Fair Flowers Fair Plants</name><description>Fair Flowers Fair Plants is a label attached to flowers and plants that originate from growers that meet the highest demands related to the environment and personnel, when it comes to issues such as working conditions, hygiene and safety.
</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIR_FOOD_PROGRAM_LABEL</value><name>Fair Food Program Label</name><description>The Coalition of Immokalee Workers' (CIW) Fair Food Program is a unique partnership among farmers, farmworkers, and retail food companies that ensures humane wages and working conditions for the workers who pick fruits and vegetables on participating farms. It harnesses the power of consumer demand to give farmworkers a voice in the decisions that affect their lives, and to eliminate the longstanding abuses that have plagued agriculture for generations. </description></code>
  <code><value>FAIR_FOR_LIFE</value><name></name><description>Fair for Life Social &amp; FairTrade Certification guarantees that human rights are guaranteed at any stage of production, that workers enjoy good and fair working conditions and that smallholder farmers receive a fair share. Fair trade improves the livelihood of thousands of smallholder farmers and workers by providing the means for social community projects and empowerment of people.</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIR_TRADE_MARK</value><name></name><description>The FAIR TRADE Mark certifies that products meet the social, economic and environmental International Fairtrade Standards. The FAIR TRADE Mark is usually supported by a local Fair Trade Labelling Organisation and certifies products not companies. It does not cover the companies or organizations selling the product</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIR_TRADE_USA</value><name></name><description>Fair Trade USA- The Fair Trade certification model is designed and audited to ensure equitable trade practices at every level of the supply chain. To earn a license from Fair Trade USA to use the Fair Trade Certified™ label on their products, companies must buy from certified farms and organizations, pay Fair Trade prices and premiums and submit to a rigorous supply chain audits. This process entails a high level of transparency and traceability in their global supply chains. Today, our partner companies range from small, mission-driven coffee roasters to some of the largest transnational corporations in the world.</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIR_TRADE_USA_INGREDIENTS</value><name>Fair Trade USA Ingredients </name><description>Products bearing the Fair Trade Certified Ingredient logo are required to contain 20% or more Fair Trade Certified Ingredients by weight excluding water and salt. Additionally, any individual Fair Trade Certified ingredients used in the product are 100% Fair Trade Certified.

</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIR_TSA</value><name>FairTSA </name><description>The Fair Trade Sustainability Alliance (FairTSA) is an organisation specializing in Fair Trade and social responsibility standard development, ethical supply chain management, and accountable, sustainable community development. We are the only Fair Trade standard holder with an "open" certification system, meaning that every certifier who is interested in working with our standard can do so, provided that they comply with our basic requirements. These can be found on the Producers and Licensees pages respectively.  </description></code>
  <code><value>FAIRTRADE_COCOA</value><name></name><description>The Fairtrade Cocoa Program enables companies to buy Fairtrade cocoa in bulk, for example all the cocoa they need to produce their chocolate bars, cakes and biscuits. Companies can also commit to purchase a percentage of their total cocoa as Fairtrade, such as 10%, 30% or even all the cocoa they need.</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIRTRADE_COTTON</value><name></name><description>For an item to bear the FAIRTRADE Cotton Mark, that cotton is tracked all the way from farm to shop shelf: that makes it fully traceable, but it’s a long, complex process. Companies can buy Fairtrade cotton in bulk, mixing it with other cotton and fibres as needed. That way they can really increase the amount of Fairtrade cotton they buy, to 10%, 20%, 40% of their business, or even more.</description></code>
  <code><value>FAIRTRADE_SUGAR</value><name></name><description>The Fairtrade Sugar Program, businesses can buy this sugar on Fairtrade terms and use it in their manufacturing. It’s a new way for businesses to commit to Fairtrade, alongside labelling and certifying end consumer products with the FARTRADE Mark.</description></code>
  <code><value>FALKEN</value><name></name><description>Not Available</description></code>
  <code><value>FCC</value><name>Federal Communications Commission (U.S.)</name><description>The FCC is responsible for managing and licensing the electromagnetic spectrum for commercial users and for non-commercial users including: state, county and local governments. This includes public safety, commercial and non-commercial fixed and mobile wireless services, broadcast television and radio, satellite and other services.  In licensing the spectrum, the Commission promotes efficient and reliable access to the spectrum for a variety of innovative uses as well as promotes public safety and emergency response.</description></code>
  <code><value>FEDERALLY_REGISTERED_INSPECTED_CANADA</value><name></name><description>Federally Registered/ Inspected in Canada</description></code>
  <code><value>FINNISH_HEART_SYMBOL</value><name></name><description>The heart symbol to inform the consumer at one glance that the product marked with this symbol is a preferred choice in its product group with regard to fat and sodium.  Finnish Heart Association www.sydanmerkki.fi</description></code>
  <code><value>FISH_WISE_CERTIFICATION</value><name>Fish Wise Certification </name><description>Fish Wise certification defines sustainable seafood as coming from sources, whether fished or farmed, that can maintain or increase production in the future without jeopardizing the structure or function of affected ecosystems. </description></code>
  <code><value>FLAMME_VERTE</value><name></name><description>Flamme Verte label was launched in France in 2000 by l’Agence de l'Environnement et de la Maîtrise de l'Energie (ADEME), and manufacturers of household appliances. Its mission: to promote the use of wood processing heating appliances of which the design responds to the most demanding quality in terms of fuel efficiency and emissions. In addition, Flamme verte provides assurance that its products are environmentally friendly by emitting very few fine particles.</description></code>
  <code><value>FLEURS_DE_FRANCE</value><name>Fleurs de France</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case flowers: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France". 

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>FODMAP</value><name>Monash University FODMAP (Fermentable Oligosaccharides, Disaccharides, Monosaccharides, and Polyols) </name><description>Monash University identified a group of short-chain carbohydrates found in food that are either poorly absorbed in the small intestine or impossible to digest. The Monash team named these carbohydrates FODMAPs, an acronym which stands for Fermentable Oligosaccharides, Disaccharides, Monosaccharides, and Polyols. This accreditation signifies the product can be used in a low FODMAP diet which can reduce symptoms in people with Irritable Bowel Syndrome (IBS). https://www.monashfodmap.com</description></code>
  <code><value>FODMAP_FRIENDLY</value><name>FODMAP (Fermentable Oligosaccharides, Disaccharides, Monosaccharides, and Polyols) Friendly</name><description>The Fermentable Oligosaccharides, Disaccharides, Monosaccharides, and Polyols (FODMAP) Friendly certification (Fodmap Accreditation) program, incorporating the FODMAP Friendly logo, is the only registered certification trademark worldwide certifying FODMAP levels in food products that have been laboratory tested to be low in FODMAP’s. It is designed to enable consumers with symptoms of Irritable Bowel Syndrome (IBS) who are following a Low FODMAP diet to easily identify and select suitable packaged food products. </description></code>
  <code><value>FOOD_ALLIANCE_CERTIFIED</value><name>Food Alliance Certified</name><description>Food Alliance Certified attribute includes all products that present a Food Alliance Certified logo. </description></code>
  <code><value>FOOD_JUSTICE_CERTIFIED</value><name>Food Justice Certified</name><description>Food Justice Certified is a label based on high-bar social justice standards for farms, processors, and retailers, including every link in the food chain from farm to table. Our approach is holistic; we ensure fair treatment of workers, fair pricing for farmers, and fair business practices. Food Justice Certified is designed for all agricultural production systems, fibre and cosmetics as well as food. </description></code>
  <code><value>FOOD_SAFETY_SYSTEM_CERTIFICATION_22000</value><name>Food Safety System Certification 22000</name><description>The FSSC 22000 Food Safety Management System provides a framework for effectively managing your organisation's food safety responsibilities. FSSC 22000 is fully recognized by the Global Food Safety Initiative (GFSI) and is based on existing ISO Standards. It demonstrates your company has a robust Food Safety Management System in place that meets the requirements of your customers and consumers. Already, 10.000+ organisations over 140 countries achieved FSSC 22000 certification. With currently 100+ Licensed Certification Bodies and over 1,500 auditors worldwide, our mission is to ensure consumer trust in the supply of safe food and drinks.  </description></code>
  <code><value>FOODLAND_ONTARIO</value><name></name><description>Foodland Ontario is a consumer promotion program of the Ontario Ministry of Agriculture and Food. It has partnered with producers to champion, promote and support the consumption of fresh Ontario produce and processed agricultural foods.</description></code>
  <code><value>FOR_LIFE</value><name>For Life (Social Responsibility)</name><description>Demonstration of social and fair business practices; providing good working conditions, guaranteeing the fair treatment of employees and the community and environmental responsibility.</description></code>
  <code><value>FOREST_PRODUCTS_Z809</value><name>Forest Products - Product Lines From a Certified Forest</name><description>At least 70% of the input used to make this product line has been tracked and monitored from its point of origin (a Z809 certified forest) to the end consumer. This mark appears on product and/or packaging. None of the wood-based raw materials shall have come from Controversial Sources.</description></code>
  <code><value>FOREST_STEWARDSHIP_COUNCIL_100_PERCENT</value><name></name><description>FSC is a global, not-for-profit organization dedicated to the promotion of responsible forest management worldwide.
The 100% label stands for products containing 100% material from FSC certified forests.</description></code>
  <code><value>FOREST_STEWARDSHIP_COUNCIL_LABEL</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked with the Forest Stewardship Council label.</description></code>
  <code><value>FOREST_STEWARDSHIP_COUNCIL_MIX</value><name></name><description>FSC is a global, not-for-profit organization dedicated to the promotion of responsible forest management worldwide.
Products with material from FSC certified forests , recycled materials or other controlled sources.</description></code>
  <code><value>FOREST_STEWARDSHIP_COUNCIL_RECYCLED</value><name></name><description>FSC is a global, not-for-profit organization dedicated to the promotion of responsible forest management worldwide.
The label stand for products containing only recycled material.</description></code>
  <code><value>FOUNDATION_ART</value><name></name><description>The Foundation ART has the aim to increase the level of anti-theft prevention of two-wheeled vehicles (bicycles, mopeds, scooters and motor cycles). Anti-theft prevention of two-wheeled vehicles can be promoted by influencing social behaviour, registration and tracing, guarded shelters and anti-theft provisions.
The activities of Foundation ART are focussed on (mechanical) anti-theft provisions. The Foundation ART promotes the safety provisions against theft by:
•arranging requirements for mechanical security systems for two-wheeled vehicles
•testing (by third parties) of systems for which an application for homologation was submitted
•certification of approved products
•promoting the use of approved mechanical security systems.
</description></code>
  <code><value>FRAN_SVERIGE</value><name>Fran Sverige</name><description>In composite products, i.e. a product with at least one added ingredient, at least 75% to be Swedish (water does not count) . Bread, cheese and fruit yogurt are examples of composite products. Meat, eggs and raw milk should always be 100% Swedish, even as an ingredient in a product. All animals must be born, raised and slaughtered in Sweden .Cultivation should have taken place in Sweden .All processing and packaging must take place in Sweden.</description></code>
  <code><value>FRANCE_LIMOUSIN_MEAT</value><name></name><description>France Limousin meat is meat that is constantly monitored from birth to slaughter. Every animal has it's own unique registration number and when exported is assigned an official certificate of origin.</description></code>
  <code><value>FREILAND</value><name></name><description>The yellow triangle with the flower is only awarded to food and firms that adhere strictly to the principles of organic farming and beyond the highest standards of animal husbandry.</description></code>
  <code><value>FRIEND_OF_THE_SEA</value><name></name><description>Friend of the Sea Approved Fisheries:
- target stocks which are not overexploited
- use fishing methods which don't impact the seabed, and
- generate less than average 8% discards.</description></code>
  <code><value>FRUITS_ET_LEGUMES_DE_FRANCE</value><name>Fruits et Legumes de France</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case fruit and legumes: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>GAA</value><name></name><description>Gäa is a diverse farming association for farmers, processors and traders inside. The focal point is Germany. Gäa is a special design for the structure of the organic farming.</description></code>
  <code><value>GAP_1</value><name>Global Animal Partnership (G.A.P.) 1</name><description>Animal Welfare Certified - Base Certification: Base certification is our minimum G.A.P. animal welfare certification level. This means that all of the farms and/or ranches raising the animal have met over 100+ animal welfare standards including more space to move around, and no cages or crates that would confine them. When you see our G.A.P. Animal Welfare Certified label, it means that the animals were raised without antibiotics and no added hormones, and were also fed a vegetarian diet with no animal by-products.</description></code>
  <code><value>GAP_2</value><name>Global Animal Partnership (G.A.P.) 2</name><description>Animal Welfare Certified - Enriched Environment: Animals were raised in environments that provide them with more space and additional enrichments (such as straw bales and perches) to encourage natural behaviors. Again, all G.A.P. certified animals were raised without antibiotics or any added hormones, and were fed a vegetarian diet with no animal by-products.</description></code>
  <code><value>GAP_3</value><name>Global Animal Partnership (G.A.P.) 3</name><description>Animal Welfare Certified - Outdoor Access: Animals have the choice of indoor or outdoor living (weather permitting for poultry), and also have additional enrichments indoors and out. At this level, farms and ranches ensure the animals are managed in both environments. </description></code>
  <code><value>GAP_4</value><name>Global Animal Partnership (G.A.P.) 4</name><description>Animal Welfare Certified - Pasture Raised: Animals are raised on pasture year-round. In some climates where pastures need to be protected for use the next year, animals must still be given daily access to outdoor areas. Cattle, sheep, goats and bison are not permitted to be finished in feedlots. Farmers and ranchers raise animals that are well suited for outdoor living, and sustainably manage their environments.</description></code>
  <code><value>GAP_5</value><name>Global Animal Partnership (G.A.P.) 5</name><description>Animal Welfare Certified - Animal Centered: Animals live on pasture year-round, with protection from the environment (shelters, windbreak, etc.). Farmers and ranchers raise animals that are well suited for outdoor living, and sustainably manage their environments. No physical alterations are performed on any of the animals (e.g. castration, tail docking, etc).</description></code>
  <code><value>GAP_5_PLUS</value><name>Global Animal Partnership (G.A.P.) 5 Plus</name><description>Animal Welfare Certified - Entire Life on Farm: This is our top tier of animal welfare certification. All of the requirements of the Animal Centered level are met (animals live on pasture year round with protection, no physical alterations allowed, etc.) but animals are also processed on-farm, or through the use of a mobile slaughter facility, so their entire life is spent on the farm.</description></code>
  <code><value>GASKEUR</value><name></name><description>Gaskeur is a hallmark of KIWA. The label is   applied voluntarily in the Netherlands to boilers. It indicates the additional standards the installation complies with, above the legal requirements that the equipment must meet. It is an addition to the CE mark.</description></code>
  <code><value>GASTEC</value><name></name><description>GASTEC QA (Quality Approved) is a quality mark for gas related products and is issued exclusively by KIWA. GASTEC QA not only makes the quality and safety of the product itself visible but also of the whole production process.</description></code>
  <code><value>GENUSS_REGION_AUSTRIA</value><name>Genuss Region Austria</name><description>"GENUSS REGION ÖSTERREICH is an initiative of the Agrarmarkt Austria Marketing GesmbH and the Austrian Federal Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry, Environment and Water Management. It stands for domestic and regional agricultural products and specialities. 

www.gutes.at"</description></code>
  <code><value>GEPRUEFTE_SICHERHEIT</value><name></name><description>The Geprüfte Sicherheit ("Tested Safety") or GS mark is a voluntary certification mark for technical equipment. It indicates that the equipment meets German and, if available, European safety requirements for such devices.</description></code>
  <code><value>GEZONDERE_KEUZE</value><name></name><description>Identifies basic staple products (such as fruit, milk, bread, etc.) that constitute a healthier choice for consumers because of their higher nutritional value in comparison to similar products according to the guidelines of the Dutch Wetenschappelijke Commissie. See: http://www.ikkiesbewust.nl/</description></code>
  <code><value>GFCO</value><name></name><description>The Gluten-Free Certification Organization (GFCO) is a program of The Gluten Intolerance Group.  GFCO’s Scientific and Professional Board review the practices of GFCO.   GFCO inspects products and manufacturing facilities for gluten. GFCO does not certify products for other potential allergens. The contents of this site are not intended as medical advice.</description></code>
  <code><value>GFCP</value><name></name><description>The Gluten-Free Certification Program (GFCP), Endorsed by the National Foundation for Celiac Awareness (NFCA)- The National Foundation for Celiac Awareness endorsed Gluten-Free Certification Program (GFCP) is a voluntary certification program designed to designate trusted gluten-free products in the marketplace by displaying the NFCA certification trademark. Based on a robust third-party audit certification process at the manufacturing facility, the GFCP verifies that the manufacturing process for a product regularly meets stringent requirements for managing gluten as part of their food safety programs.  The GFCP is a North American solution, using a single process to certify products for distribution in the US and Canada.</description></code>
  <code><value>GIG_GLUTEN_FREE_FOODSERVICE</value><name>GIG - Gluten Free Foodservice</name><description>The Gluten-Free Food Services (GFFS) Training and Accreditation Program, a program of GIG, is designed to work with all food service establishments who wish to provide for and serve gluten-free consumers. GFFS works with experts in food preparation to develop, educate, and train service establishments to meet and adhere to the highest gluten-free standards. </description></code>
  <code><value>GLOBAL_CARE</value><name>Global Care</name><description>Global Care" represents our commitment to social and environmental responsibility worldwide. As a leader in innovative lighting solutions, we are dedicated to products and processes that contribute to solving global sustainability challenges, address economic needs and protect the environment for today and for the future. That way we ensure sustainable development not only for the company, but also for society and the environment.</description></code>
  <code><value>GLOBAL_GAP</value><name></name><description>GLOBALG.A.P. is a private sector body that sets voluntary standards for the certification of production processes of agricultural (including aquaculture) products around the globe. The GLOBALG.A.P. standard is primarily designed to reassure consumers about how food is produced on the farm by minimising detrimental environmental impacts of farming operations, reducing the use of chemical inputs and ensuring a responsible approach to worker health and safety as well as animal welfare.</description></code>
  <code><value>GLOBAL_ORGANIC_LATEX_STANDARD</value><name>Global Organic Latex Standard</name><description>The Global Organic Latex Standard certification attribute includes all products that have published the Global Organic Latex Standard seal on their packaging. </description></code>
  <code><value>GLOBAL_ORGANIC_TEXTILE_STANDARD</value><name></name><description>The Global Organic Textile Standard (GOTS)  ensure organic status of textiles, from harvesting of the raw materials, through environmentally and socially responsible manufacturing up to labelling in order to provide credible assurance to the consumer.</description></code>
  <code><value>GLOBAL_RECYCLED_STANDARD</value><name>Global Recycled Standard</name><description>The Global Recycled Standard is intended for companies that are making and/or selling products with recycled content. The standard applies to the full supply chain and addresses traceability, environmental principles, social requirements, and labeling. Developed with the textile industry in mind, the GRS may also be applied to products from any industry.</description></code>
  <code><value>GLYCAEMIC_INDEX_FOUNDATION</value><name>Glycaemic Index Foundation</name><description>The Glycaemic Index Foundation certification includes all products that have published the Glycemic Index Foundation stamp on their package. </description></code>
  <code><value>GLYCAEMIC_RESEARCH_INSTITUTE</value><name>Glycaemic  Research Institute</name><description>The Glycaemic Research Institute certification includes all products that have published the Glycemic Research Institute stamp on their package. </description></code>
  <code><value>GMO_GUARD_FROM_NATURAL_FOOD_CERTIFIERS</value><name>GMO Guard from Natural Food Certifiers</name><description>The GMO-Guard from Natural Food Certifiers certification includes all products that have published the GMO-Guard from Natural Food Certifiers stamp on their package. </description></code>
  <code><value>GMO_MARKED</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked as of genetically modified origin.</description></code>
  <code><value>GMP_CERTIFIED</value><name></name><description>Good Manufacturing Practices (GMP) introduces a management systems approach to documenting and regulating the production, control, storage, and shipment of products.  For example in 2011, the World Health Organization updated GMP requirements in the good manufacturing practices standard (WHO TRS 961, 2011 for certification of Pharmaceuticals). WHO has also created GMP processes for other product types. Also FDA and other organisations.</description></code>
  <code><value>GMP_ISO_22716</value><name></name><description>Good Manufacturing Practices (GMP) introduces a management systems approach to documenting and regulating the production, control, storage, and shipment of products. ISO standard 22716 is for cosmetic products that are manufactured according to Good Manufacturing Practices (GMP). </description></code>
  <code><value>GOA_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Global Organic Alliance (GOA), Ohio, U.S.A.</name><description>Global Organic Alliance (GOA) provides services to various organic certification or compliance verification programs.</description></code>
  <code><value>GOOD_HOUSEKEEPING</value><name></name><description>Good Housekeeping maintains good taste and exercises strict editorial judgment as to products that are eligible for Good Housekeeping's limited warranty to consumers. Good Housekeeping bestows its limited warranty Seal on those products that have been evaluated by the Good Housekeeping Institute and been assessed to perform as intended. These judgments are the basis of the Good Housekeeping Consumers' Refund Policy.</description></code>
  <code><value>GOODS_FROM_FINLAND_BLUE_SWAN</value><name></name><description>http://www.finfood.fi/ Finfood Suomen Ruokatieto Ry</description></code>
  <code><value>GOODWEAVE</value><name>GoodWeave</name><description>GoodWeave aims to stop child labour in the carpet industry and to replicate its market-based approach in other sectors.</description></code>
  <code><value>GRASKEURMERK</value><name></name><description>This label is awarded by the Stichting Gras Keurmerk to manufacturers of both vegetable and animal products who comply with the Dutch guidelines for pasturing and agriculture (Normering Grasdier Landbouw). These guidelines establish that cattle/animals are to be kept at stables with enough space and are allowed to go outside daily. Under these guidelines, crops are to be grown using animal fertilizer and with very limited use of other substances. 
</description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_AMERICA_CERTIFIED_BUSINESS</value><name>Green America Certified Business</name><description>The Green America Certified Business certification attribute includes all products that have published the Green America Certified Business Gold, Silver, or Bronze seal on their packaging. Businesses earn this seal after staff at Green America's Green Business Network reviews and approves their application. </description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_DOT</value><name></name><description>Not Available</description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_E_ENERGY_CERT</value><name>Green-e Energy Certified</name><description>Green-e Energy certifies renewable energy that meets the highest standards in North America: it must be generated from new facilities, marketed with complete transparency and accuracy, and delivered to the purchaser, who has sole title. Green-e verifies the entire chain of custody of certified renewable energy from generation to retirement to ensure individuals and businesses are getting exactly what they paid for.</description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_E_ORG</value><name>Green-e Energy </name><description>Green-e Energy is the nation's leading voluntary certification program for renewable energy. For two decades, Green-e Energy has been certifying renewable energy that meets environmental and consumer protection standards that it developed in conjunction with leading environmental, energy and policy organisations. Green-e Energy also requires that sellers of certified renewable energy disclose clear and useful information to potential customers, allowing consumers to make informed choices. </description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_RESTAURANT_ASSOCIATION_ENDORSED</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked with the Green Restaurant Association Endorsed symbol.</description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_SEAL</value><name></name><description>An independent, non-profit organization that strives to achieve a healthier and cleaner environment by identifying and promoting products.</description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_SEAL_CERTIFIED</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked with the Green Seal Certified symbol.</description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_SHIELD_CERTIFIED</value><name>Green Shield Certified</name><description>Green Shield Certified is an independent, non-profit certification program that promotes practitioners of effective, prevention-based pest control while minimizing the need to use pesticides. </description></code>
  <code><value>GREEN_STAR_CERTIFIED</value><name></name><description>Green Star Certified- "GMO FREE CERTIFIED™ brand program certifies producers have provided laboratory results that their produce or products are GMO Free.  The United States does not mandate GMO Free labelling or even recommend labelling, however producers want to provide peace of mind their produce and products are GMO free with the trusted GMO FREE CERTIFIED™ seal.  Green Star Certified allows these same producers and manufactures to participate in the "GMO FREE CERTIFIED™" program by having there produce, seeds, feed and processed food tested by leading independent genetic testing laboratories. Once their products meet and maintain the Green Star Certified standards/threshold these producers can place the GMO FREE CERTIFED™ brand on their marketing and product labels. </description></code>
  <code><value>GREENCHOICE</value><name>GreenChoice</name><description>GreenChoice 100™ is superior paperboard and the only one that is Eco-Logo, FSC, and Rainforest Alliance certified all at the same time. All energy used for GreenChoice 100™ is 100% offset by renewable wind energy producers. It’s 100% carbon-neutral, as all carbon emitted is fully offset by new plantings. GreenChoice 100™ is also 100% recyclable, as 100% of fibres used come from recycled sources. Approximately 35% is post-consumer material and 65% is pre-consumer (fibres returned from the supply chain). 
</description></code>
  <code><value>GROEN_LABEL_KAS</value><name></name><description>This label is awarded to companies which use environment-friendly greenhouses. These greenhouses are to be set up according to strict regulations which aim to ensure the impact of the environment remains at a minimal level (less water and energy waste, no chemical waste).

</description></code>
  <code><value>GRUYERE_FRANCE</value><name>French Gruyère</name><description>Gruyère de France comes from the meadows of Savoie and Franche-Comté (Haute-Saône and Doubs). It is a tasty cooked pressed cheese with raw milk, guaranteeing precious nutritional qualities.</description></code>
  <code><value>GUARANTEED_IRISH</value><name></name><description>Ireland: The Guaranteed Irish symbol makes shopping for Irish products and services a lot easier. Shoppers know that when they buy a product or service featuring the guaranteed Irish logo they are supporting Irish companies and safeguarding Irish jobs. http://www.guaranteedirish.ie/</description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_AUSTRALIA</value><name>Halal Australia</name><description>For all exports, only recognised Islamic organisations such as Halal Australia can certify halal meat and meat products in Australia. The Halal Australia certification is back by Australian government assurance that the product has been produced in accordance with Islamic Shari'aa standards.</description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_CORRECT</value><name></name><description>The standard HALAL CORRECT is a standard quality and guarantees the Halal conformity of the whole chain, from slaughtering until the packaging of the Halal products.</description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_FOOD_COUNCIL_OF_SOUTH_EAST_ASIA_THAILAND</value><name>Halal Food Council of South East Asia Thailand</name><description>HALAL Certification of Halal Food Council of South East Asia Thailand
</description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_HIC</value><name>Halal Inspections and Certification (HIC)</name><description>Halal Inspections and Certification (HIC) CANADA BY THE B.C. MUSLIM ASSOCIATION (BCMA) was established to help ensure that all muslims could be confident that the meat and products they consume are ‘genuinely Halal’. The HIC CANADA organization is an independent, not for profit, registered charity which monitors, inspects and certifies halal products for the benefit of the muslim community.</description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_HPDS</value><name>Halal HPDS (Halal Product Development Services)</name><description>Halal Product Development Services (HPDS) is a Canadian company providing a range of halal and market related services. HPDS has experience in providing halal services to various sectors of the food business including agriculture, processing, food service and the grocery sector.</description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_INDIA</value><name>Halal India</name><description>Halal India is one of the established Halal Certification body in India. They are committed to achieve excellence in consultation, issuing halal compliance certification, independent auditing &amp; monitoring systems and promoting other acceptable products and services as per shariah (law). </description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_ISLAMIC_FOOD_CANADA</value><name>Halal Islamic Food and Nutrition Council of Canada (IFANCC)</name><description>The Islamic Food and Nutrition Council of Canada (IFANCC) is Canada’s leading Halal certifying organization. The IFANCC Halal certificate is an authoritative, reliable and independent testimony to support your claim as a manufacturer or operator that your products meet Halal requirements</description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_ISLAMIC_SOCIETY_OF_NORTH_AMERICA</value><name>Halal  Islamic Society of North America (ISNA) </name><description>ISNA® Canada  has been providing Halal Certification service to the Muslim communities not only in Canada and the United States but throughout the Muslim world. ISNA® Canada developed its Halal Logo (see below) to be put on the packages certified by it to assure the Muslims that package contains the Halal food. </description></code>
  <code><value>HALAL_PLUS</value><name></name><description>The standard HALAL PLUS is high-quality Halal, certified by the Foundation Halal Correct and biologically certified by SKAL. </description></code>
  <code><value>HAUTE_VALEUR_ENVIRONNEMENTALE</value><name>Haute Valeur Environnementale</name><description>The National Commission for Environmental Certification (NCEC), was created on October 25, 2011 to monitor the implementation of the device. It is made up of representatives of the State, agricultural unions, approved associations for the protection of the environment, the agri-food industry, distribution and consumer organizations.
The NCEC has in particular defined the control plans defining the precise framework allowing the certification of farms for each level of the system.</description></code>
  <code><value>HAZARD_ANALYSIS_CRITICAL_CONTROL_POINT</value><name>Hazard Analysis Critical Control Point </name><description>Hazard Analysis Critical Control Point (HACCP) is an approach to food safety that is systematic and preventive. It is recommended by the Codex Alimentarius Commission, the United Nations international standards organization for food safety. HACCP is used by most countries around the world. It has been in use since the 1960s.
A HACCP system allows you to identify hazards and put in place controls to manage these throughout your supply chain during production. The HACCP scheme meets the requirements of the Codex Alimentarius Commission (CAC) – established by the World Health Organisation and the Food and Agriculture Organisation of the United Nations to bring together international food standards, guidelines and codes of practice to ensure fair trade. It can also be used to support the requirements of management standard requirements, such as ISO 22000 Food Safety Management.   </description></code>
  <code><value>HEALTH_CHECK</value><name></name><description>Specifies if product has been certified by Canadian Heart &amp; Stroke Health Check Program.</description></code>
  <code><value>HEALTH_FOOD_BLUE_HAT_SIGN</value><name>Health Food Blue Hat Sign</name><description>With the approval of relevant regulatory authorities, the blue hat sign is marked on health food's package.</description></code>
  <code><value>HEUMILCH</value><name></name><description>ARGE Heumilch Milk production of "hay milk" is the most natural form of milk production. Products that use "Hay Milk" in their production are awarded the certification label. Hay milk is milk that no animals feed from food that is from silage (fermented feed) is produced. The feeding is the natural course of the year: summer up to 50 different types of grasses and herbs in the meadows, pastures and meadows. In winter, the animals are fed with hay and grain meal, are just some examples of the guidelines. Heumilch from Austria is made according to a strict regulations. This is monitored by independent authorities. The AMA seal of approval guarantees 100% Austrian raw materials.http://www.heumilch.at/ .  </description></code>
  <code><value>HFAC_HUMANE</value><name>Certified Humane</name><description>Certified Humane Raised and Handled® label on a product ensure that the food products have come from facilities that meet precise, objective standards for farm animal treatment</description></code>
  <code><value>HMCA_HALAL_MONTREAL_CERTIFICATION_AUTHORITY</value><name>HMCA - Halal Montreal Certification Authority</name><description>The mission at Halal Montreal Certification Authority (HMCA) has always been that of guidance and support to companies wishing to broaden their Halal market potential, whether local or abroad. </description></code>
  <code><value>HOW_2_RECYCLE</value><name>How2Recycle</name><description>How2Recycle is a standardized labeling system that clearly communicates recycling instructions to the public. It involves a coalition of forward thinking brands who want their packaging to be recycled and are empowering consumers through smart packaging labels. The How2Recycle label was created to provide consistent and transparent on-package recycling information to consumers in North America.</description></code>
  <code><value>HUMANE_HEARTLAND</value><name>Humane Heartland </name><description>Humane Heartland attribute includes all products that present a Humane Heartland logo. </description></code>
  <code><value>HYPERTENSION_CANADA_MEDICAL_DEVICE</value><name>Hypertension Canada Medical Device</name><description>Hypertension Canada is the only national non-profit organization dedicated solely to the prevention and control of hypertension and its complications. We work with leading minds across medical and health disciplines to advance research and professional and public education, and with policy makers to ensure Canadians can avoid the potentially deadly complications of hypertension.</description></code>
  <code><value>ICADA</value><name></name><description>The ICADA (International Cosmetic and Detergents Association) mark makes it for the consumer visible that only raw materials were used for the production of organic and natural cosmetics, which conform to the strict requirements. 
http://www.icada.eu/. </description></code>
  <code><value>ICEA</value><name></name><description> ICEA (Instituto Certicazione Etica e Ambientale, Environmental and Ethical Certification Institute) is a Consortium that control and certifies companies that carry out their activities in respect of people and nature, defending workers dignity and rights of consumers. ICEA is among most important bodies of the sector in Italy and in Europe, where it operates to favour a fair and socially sustainable development that ranges from organic farming to other bio related sectors. http://www.icea.info/en/.</description></code>
  <code><value>ICELAND_RESPONSIBLE_FISHERIES</value><name></name><description>The Iceland Responsible Fisheries logo indicates Icelandic origin of fish catches in Icelandic waters and responsible fisheries management.</description></code>
  <code><value>ICS_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body - International Certification Services, Inc. (ICS), North Dakota, USA</name><description>Organic Certification assures consumers that organically produced foods and textiles meet a consistent set of standards that were developed and are regulated by the USDA National Organic Program (USDA NOP), or similar internationally recognized standard.   In order to label products as Organic, certification is required by law in the U.S. and many other countries.

As a USDA NOP Accredited Certifier, ICS verifies that all its clients are compliant with these standards.  ICS certifies all categories of operations: Family Farms, Commercial Farms, On-farm processing, Contract Services, Processor/Manufacturers, and Handlers.</description></code>
  <code><value>IFANCA_HALAL</value><name>IFANCA Halal </name><description>IFANCA, one of the world's leading resources for halal information. Halal, when applied to food, is a dietary set of guidelines for Muslims living an Islamic lifestyle. Since 1982, IFANCA is committed to helping halal consumers through research, education and advocacy. One of the services IFANCA provides to halal consumers is third-party halal certification. Our certification symbol, the Crescent helps halal consumers select goods, assuring them that what they buy is halal without a doubt. </description></code>
  <code><value>IFOAM</value><name></name><description>International Federation of Organic Agriculture Movements (IFOAM) Accreditation is primarily a means of ensuring fair and orderly trade of organic products. It is in this sense a service for the trade and producers as well as for certifiers. IFOAM Accreditation facilitates equivalency of organic certification bodies worldwide by confirming whether they meet IFOAM's international norms.</description></code>
  <code><value>IFS_HPC</value><name></name><description>IFS Standards help to comply with all legal food and non-food safety and quality requirements and give common and transparent standards to all concerned suppliers and service providers as well as a concrete and strong answer to the high safety and quality expectations of customers.</description></code>
  <code><value>IHTK_SEAL</value><name></name><description>Cosmetics according to the guidelines of the German Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals ( Deutscher Tierschutzbund e. V. ) The German Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals and the International Manufactory Association against Animal Testing in Cosmetics ( IHTK e. V.) carry on their consequent work against animal testing in 2001 http://www.ihtk.de/ihtk-en.htm.</description></code>
  <code><value>IKB_EIEREN</value><name></name><description>IKB egg is a Dutch quality system for the production of eggs.</description></code>
  <code><value>IKB_KIP</value><name></name><description>The Product Board for Poultry and Eggs has registered the IKB Chicken quality mark with the Benelux Trademarks Office,
for the purpose of recognisability of rigorously inspected, quality poultry meat, produced and handled in conformity with the regulations of the IKB Chicken certification scheme stipulated by the management of the Product Board for Poultry and Eggs.</description></code>
  <code><value>IKB_VARKEN</value><name></name><description>Products produced within the Dutch quality system IKB pig come from companies that are checked with regard to their use of animal feed, use of animal medication, hygiene and transportation.</description></code>
  <code><value>INDEKLIMA_MAERKET</value><name>Indeklima Maerket</name><description>Dansk Indeklima Mærkning (DIM) is a voluntary labeling scheme. DIM requires documented limited emission of gas, fibres, particles and smell to secure high indoor climate.</description></code>
  <code><value>INSTITUT_FRESENIUS</value><name></name><description>This INSTITUT FRESENIUS Quality Seal on a package, certify, that this item is a quality product that consumer can trust in. That’s because Fresenius thoroughly examine products, that indicates it is high-class quality. The main focus on food products and related cooking products.</description></code>
  <code><value>INT_PROTECTION</value><name></name><description>The IP Code (International Protection Rating, sometimes called Ingress Protection) on electrical appliances is an indication of the degree of protection of the design of electrical and electronic equipment against internal damage in "hostile environments" and against any danger to the user.
The IP designation is internationally standardized in IEC 60529. The IP designation has two numbers: the first indicates the degree of protection against contact and ingress of objects, the second indicates the degree of protection against moisture.  Companies can use their own logo.</description></code>
  <code><value>INTERNATIONAL_ALOE_SCIENCE_COUNCIL_CERTIFICATE</value><name>International Aloe Science Council Certificate</name><description>The International Aloe Science Council Cert certification includes all products that have published the International Aloe Science Council Certification stamp on their package. </description></code>
  <code><value>INTERNATIONAL_KOSHER_COUNCIL</value><name>International Kosher Council</name><description>The International Kosher Council was established to assist food manufacturers in the many facets that encompass getting a product kosher certified.</description></code>
  <code><value>INTERNATIONAL_TASTE_QUALITY</value><name>International Taste &amp; Quality (iTQi) Superior Taste Award</name><description>The Superior Taste Award label is a powerful marketing tool that is used to communicate about the products and the company's success, in both domestically and internationally. Its visibility of the label brings an immediate differentiation amongst the vast product choices on the marketplace and reassures consumers in their buying decision.</description></code>
  <code><value>INTERTEK_CERTIFICATE</value><name>Intertek Certificate </name><description>The ETL Mark is proof of product compliance to North American safety standards. Authorities Having Jurisdiction(AHJs) and code officials across the US and Canada accept the ETL Listed Mark as proof of product compliance to published industry standards. The ETL Listed Mark is proof that a product has been independently tested and meets the applicable published standard. </description></code>
  <code><value>INTERTEK_ETL</value><name>Intertek Electrical Testing Laboratories (ETL) Mark</name><description>Intertek’s ETL Mark is a safety mark which is recognised all over North America. It indicates that your product has been tested by an accredited third party testing laboratory, and meets the applicable safety standards and minimal requirements for sale or distribution within North America.</description></code>
  <code><value>ISCC</value><name>ISCC (International Sustainability and Carbon Certification)</name><description>"ISCC (International Sustainability and Carbon Certification) is a voluntary certification standard to support the shift towards the circular economy and bio-economy. This label can be used by ISCC system users with a valid ISCC certificate or that are certified under an ISCC group certification. (https://www.iscc-system.org/)

"</description></code>
  <code><value>ISCC_SUPPORTING_THE_BIOECONOMY</value><name>ISCC Supporting the Bioeconomy</name><description>"ISCC (International Sustainability and Carbon Certification) is an independent multi-stakeholder organisation providing a globally applicable certification system for the sustainability of raw materials and products. This label can be used for products linked to bio-circular materials. Bio-circular materials are materials made from biological waste and residues. This logo can also be used for mixed products linked to bio-circular and bio materials. (https://www.iscc-system.org/process/marketing-with-iscc/)

"</description></code>
  <code><value>ISEAL_ALLIANCE</value><name></name><description>ISEAL is the global association for sustainability standards. They develop guidance and facilitate coordinated efforts to improve their members’ effectiveness and scale up their social and environmental impacts.</description></code>
  <code><value>ISO_QUALITY</value><name>ISO Quality </name><description>Products bearing this certification are certified by a 3rd party ensuring they follow the ISO standards. ISO standards give world-class specifications for products, services and systems, to ensure quality, safety and efficiency. They are instrumental in facilitating international trade. </description></code>
  <code><value>IVN_NATURAL_LEATHER</value><name></name><description>"Naturleder" is an IVN ( Internationaler Verband der Naturtextilwirtschaft e. V.) standard. This is the only standard for eco-friendly leather products in Europe.  All products certified with this standard offer a high level of ecology and quality.</description></code>
  <code><value>IVN_NATURAL_TEXTILES_BEST</value><name></name><description>This IVN ( Internationaler Verband der Naturtextilwirtschaft e. V.) quality seal, well known within Europe, currently sets the strictest ecological standard for textile production at the highest technical level currently feasible. BEST reflects the standards for eco-friendly textiles developed by the International Association of Natural Textile Industry (IVN) since 1990 and reviews the entire textile production chain both in terms of ecological standards and in terms of social accountability.</description></code>
  <code><value>IVO_OMEGA3</value><name>IVO™ Seal – International Verified Omega-3
e.g., Fish oil</name><description>International Verified Omega-3 is an independent not-for-profit organization whose goal is to: 1) increase consumer confidence in the quality of marine oils (including fish oils) rich in omega-3s, 2) help consumers identify and select the best omega-3 products for their health, 3) to advocate for and support responsible marine stewardship and the long term sustainability of fish populations and habitat around the world.</description></code>
  <code><value>JAS_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body - JAS (Japanese Agricultural Standards)</name><description>Japanese Agricultural Standards  are  standards for the agriculture industry maintained by the Japanese Government. They are comparable to Japanese Industrial Standards but for food and agricultural products. Once a product has passed tests conducted by government-backed rating bureaus the JAS seal (right) is appended to the product</description></code>
  <code><value>JAY_KOSHER_PAREVE</value><name>Jay Kosher Pareve</name><description>Jay Kosher Pareve Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>JODSALZ_BZGA</value><name></name><description>The "Jodsiegel" were built up by the Federal Centre for Health and Education (BZgA) on behalf of the Federal Ministry of Health. The seal is provided on packages of products by the food manufacturer, when the products made with iodized salt. With the help of the label, consumers can see the use of iodized salt directly. The logo is part of a series of awareness campaigns BZgA together with the Arbeitskreis Jodmangel (working group of iodine deficiency), which aim to make the use of iodized salt to a rule.</description></code>
  <code><value>KABELKEUR</value><name></name><description>Kabelkeur is the quality mark for television and television cables, splitters and amplifiers and is an initiative of the industry association of the Dutch NLkabel cable companies. The purpose of this label is to increase the quality of television and television accessories.</description></code>
  <code><value>KEHILLA_KOSHER_CALIFORNIA_K</value><name>Kehilla Kosher California K</name><description>Kehilla Kosher California-K Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>KEHILLA_KOSHER_HEART_K</value><name>Kehilla Kosher Heart K</name><description>Kehilla Kosher Heart-K Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>KEMA_KEUR</value><name></name><description>KEMA quality mark is a household name in the Netherlands and is based on international standards for electrical safety. It is recognized throughout Europe.</description></code>
  <code><value>KIWA</value><name></name><description>The KIWA quality mark applies mainly to the (construction) technical qualities of a product and, depending on the product, environmental aspects . The KIWA label is mainly reflected on products from the construction sector, specially from the drinking water supply such as pipes, fittings and faucets. </description></code>
  <code><value>KLASA</value><name>Klasa</name><description>Czech national mark of quality. The KLASA Mark has been awarded by the Ministry of Agriculture since 2003. Only the best quality food and agricultural products earn it.</description></code>
  <code><value>KOF_K_KOSHER</value><name>KOF K Kosher</name><description>KOF-K Kosher Supervision is one of the world’s most widely known kosher certification and supervision agencies, serving food producers, manufacturers, and processors around the world. KOF-K’s roster of clients includes Fortune 500 companies and the world’s largest brand names. The KOF-K trademark on a product is recognized and respected world wide as a designation of quality and purity that has been earned through full compliance with the highest of kosher standards to meet the expectations of the kosher market. The KOF-K symbol is protected under U.S. Federal law and is vigilantly guarded against unauthorized use, so that the customer can choose a KOF-K labelled product with complete confidence.
</description></code>
  <code><value>KOMO</value><name></name><description>The KOMO-quality mark is a collective mark of quality with a focus on products in the construction and installation sector and requires quality, environmental and safety aspects for the Dutch market. The trademark KOMO covers several quality marks for specific sectors (KOMO- reduction, KOMO install and KOMO climb-label). The Foundation KOMO manages the labels and the KOMO-quality certificates are submitted by certification settings.</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_AUSTRALIA</value><name>Kosher Australia Certification </name><description>Kosher Australia Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_BDMC</value><name>Kosher BDMC (Kosher Beth Din Minchas Chinuch)</name><description>The Badatz Tartikov hechsher has been the seal of one of the most respected kashrus supervision organizations in the world for close to 20 years,. To this day, our specialty remains to satisfy the standards of the most stringent consumers in the Jewish world.</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_CERTIFICATION_SERVICE</value><name>Kosher Certification Service</name><description>Kosher Certification Service Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_CHECK</value><name>Kosher Check</name><description>Kosher Check is a non-profit global kosher certification agency headquartered in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada. With Regional offices located throughout Asia, Europe, and North America. We currently serve hundreds of food manufacturers throughout Canada, the US, the Pacific Rim, and the Far East, through our extensive network of regional rabbinic representatives around the globe</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_CHICAGO_RABBINICAL_COUNCIL_DAIRY</value><name>Kosher - Chicago Rabbinical Council (CRC) Dairy</name><description>The largest regional Orthodox organization in North America, the cRc is a not-for-profit offering a wide variety of Jewish services including  kosher certification (kosher approval for products). Kosher certification is available around the world and throughout the year, including kosher Passover supervision.
</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_CHICAGO_RABBINICAL_COUNCIL_PAREVE</value><name>Kosher Chicago Rabbinical Council (CRC)  Pareve</name><description>The largest regional Orthodox organization in North America, the cRc is a not-for-profit offering a wide variety of Jewish services including  kosher certification (kosher approval for products). Kosher certification is available around the world and throughout the year, including kosher Passover supervision.
</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_COR_DAIRY</value><name>Kosher COR Dairy</name><description>Kosher COR Dairy</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_COR_DAIRY_EQUIPMENT</value><name>Kosher COR Dairy Equipment</name><description>Kosher COR Dairy Equipment</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_COR_FISH</value><name>Kosher COR Fish</name><description>Kosher COR Fish</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_EIDAH_HACHAREIDIS</value><name>Kosher Eidah Hacharidis</name><description>The Beis Din Tzedek of the Eidah Hachareidis of Jerusalem Binyanei Zupnick.</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_GRAND_RABBINATE_OF_QUEBEC_PARVE</value><name>Kosher Grand Rabbinate of Quebec Parve</name><description>Certified Kosher by the Grand Rabbinate of Quebec. </description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_GREECE</value><name>Kosher Kosher Greece</name><description>Kosher Kosher Greece</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_INSPECTION_SERVICE_INDIA</value><name>Kosher Inspection Service India</name><description>Kosher Inspection Service India Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_KW_YOUNG_ISRAEL_OF_WEST_HEMPSTEAD</value><name>Kosher KW Young Israel Of West Hempstead</name><description>Kosher KW Young Israel of West Hempstead Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_MADRID_SPAIN</value><name>Kosher Kosher Madrid Spain</name><description>Kosher Kosher Madrid Spain</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_OK_DAIRY</value><name>Kosher OK Dairy</name><description>OK Kosher Dairy Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_ORTHODOX_JEWISH_CONGREGATION_PARVE</value><name>Kosher Orthodox Jewish Congregation Parve</name><description>The OU (Orthodox Union) Kosher Parve certification</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_OTTAWA_VAAD_HAKASHRUT_CANADA</value><name>Kosher Ottawa Vaad HaKashrut Canada</name><description>OTTAWA VAAD HaKASHRUT facilitates the availability of a wide variety of reliably kosher food, products, and services to the Ottawa Jewish Community</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_PARVE_BKA</value><name>Kosher Parve B.K.A.</name><description>Kosher Parve B.K.A. Brazil To enable the regular supply of products that require the supervision seal, Kosher Mart Produtos Alimentícios Ltda . Was created , for which special lots with a seal are billed (verified and manufactured with mashguiach monitoring ) and later passed on to the points of sale.</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_PARVE_NATURAL_FOOD_CERTIFIER</value><name>Kosher Parve Natural Food Certifier</name><description>NFC (Natural food Certifier)  exclusively certifies the natural, and organic products industry. Their certification includes NFC Apple Kosher </description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_PERU</value><name>Kosher Peru Certification </name><description>Kosher Peru Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_RAV_LANDAU</value><name>Kosher Rav (Rabbi) Landau</name><description>Rabbi Moshe Yehudah Leib Landau kosher certification agency in Beni Brak, Israel.</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_STAR_K_PARVE</value><name>Kosher Star-K-Parve</name><description>Kosher Star-K-Parve</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_STAR_K_PARVE_PASSOVER</value><name>Kosher Star-K -Parve and Passover</name><description>Kosher Star-K -Parve, Passover</description></code>
  <code><value>KOSHER_STAR_S_P_KITNIYOT</value><name>Kosher Star S for passover kitniyot</name><description>The Rabbinical Assembly, the governing body for the Conservative movement of Judaism, declared that kitniyot, which encompasses legumes (such as peanuts, beans and peas), rice, and corn, are kosher for Passover.</description></code>
  <code><value>KOTT_FRAN_SVERIGE</value><name>Kott Fran Sverige</name><description>Products labelled with “Kott Fran Sverige” contain 100 % Swedish meat according to the criteria that all animals must be born, raised and slaughtered in Sweden .Cultivation should have taken place in Sweden .All processing and packaging must take place in Sweden.</description></code>
  <code><value>KRAV_MARK</value><name></name><description>Not Available</description></code>
  <code><value>KSA_KOSHER</value><name>KSA - Kosher</name><description>Kosher Supervision of America is a not-for-profit Kashrus certification agency recognized by rabbinical associations throughout the world. KSA is the largest, recognized and accepted, kosher certification agency based in the western United States.</description></code>
  <code><value>KSA_KOSHER_DAIRY</value><name>KSA D - Kosher Dairy</name><description>Kosher Supervision of America for dairy products is a not-for-profit Kashrus certification agency recognized by rabbinical associations throughout the world. KSA is the largest, recognized and accepted, kosher certification agency based in the western United States.</description></code>
  <code><value>KVBG_APPROVED</value><name></name><description>The Royal Association of Belgian Gas companies (ARGB) unites the natural gas suppliers and distribution system operators who are active in Belgium.  The Association's role is to ensure the safety and good functioning of natural gas lands as well as to promote a good image for the use natural gas.</description></code>
  <code><value>LAATUVASTUU</value><name>Finnish Pork Meat Certification System</name><description>Finnish Pork Meat certification system</description></code>
  <code><value>LABEL_OF_THE_ALLERGY_AND_ASTHMA_FEDERATION</value><name></name><description>Allergy and Asthma Federation is a non-profit public health organisation. Our aim is to improve quality of life of the allergy and asthma patients. http://www.allergia.fi/in-english/</description></code>
  <code><value>LABEL_ROUGE</value><name></name><description>Label Rouge products guarantee that the 
poultry and eggs you purchase are superior to standard products because they are produced using traditional, free-range farming methods that ensure the poultry’s welfare and protect the environment.</description></code>
  <code><value>LACON</value><name></name><description>Lacon Institute stands for the assurance of quality and the certification of organically produced food.</description></code>
  <code><value>LAENDLE_QUALITAET</value><name></name><description>The logo stands for regional and domestic products which are produced, processed and prepared in a given geographical area using recognised quality standards. Only local products with 100 percent guarantee of origin are given this seal. It is given not only the green Ländle brand products but also other products  that keep clearly defined in writing and retained quality guidelines.</description></code>
  <code><value>LAPIN_DE_FRANCE</value><name>Lapin de France</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case rabbit: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>LE_PORC_FRANCAIS</value><name>le Porc Francais</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case pork: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>LEAPING_BUNNY</value><name></name><description>The Coalition for Consumer Information on Cosmetics (CCIC) Leaping Bunny Program administers a cruelty-free standard and the internationally recognized Leaping Bunny Logo for companies producing cosmetic, personal care, and household products. The Leaping Bunny Program provides the best assurance that no new animal testing is used in any phase of product development by the company, its laboratories, or suppliers. See also www.leapingbunny.org</description></code>
  <code><value>LETIS_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Letis S.A.</name><description>Certification is a process in which an independent third party certification body, as LETIS, ensures compliance with a specific standard.

At LETIS, compliance is assessed by a methodical system of audits, accredited by national and international monitoring and accreditation bodies</description></code>
  <code><value>LGA</value><name></name><description>According to the LGA (Landesgewerbeanstalt Bayern) directive, checks are done on security, features, usability, performance, electromagnetic compatibility (EMC) and hygiene of various products. The LGA has become part of TÜV, this quality mark is therefore issued by TÜV.</description></code>
  <code><value>LOCALIZE</value><name>Ontario - Localize</name><description>Localize is the only Local shelf label program in North America. We are dedicated to continuously collecting, growing, and ensuring the integrity of our data. Localize’s powerful database and application contain geographical and socially relevant information that is valuable for grocers and vital to shoppers looking for information at the shelf-edge</description></code>
  <code><value>LONDON_BETH_DIN_KOSHER</value><name>London Beth Din Kosher </name><description>Court of The Chief Rabbi London Beth Din Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>LOODUSSOBRALIK_TOODE_ESTONIA</value><name></name><description>Eco-friendly product The sign "eco-friendly product" is designed to make environmentally friendly products on store shelves more as significant. When it comes to food shall be used for agriculture, natural farming methods. No use of mineral fertilizers, insect control and plant poisons. http://www.stockmann.ee/portal/7765/</description></code>
  <code><value>LOVE_IRISH_FOOD</value><name></name><description>Love Irish Food - a promotional label printed on the product packaging to indicate to the consumer that the food is manufactured in Ireland using Irish ingredients. http://www.loveirishfood.ie/</description></code>
  <code><value>LVA</value><name></name><description>The Lebensmittel Vertrauen Analsen LVA is ISACert ISACert Austria as partner of the globally successful certification company. ISACert the leading certifier is in the area of ​​food safety.</description></code>
  <code><value>MADE_IN_FINLAND_FLAG_WITH_KEY</value><name></name><description>Made in Finland  Products that are made in Finland Avainlippu (Key Flag) Suomalaisen Työn www.avainlippu.fi</description></code>
  <code><value>MADE_OF_PLASTIC_BEVERAGE_CUPS</value><name>Beverage cups made from single-use plastic.</name><description>Labelled/embossed on beverage cups made of plastic.  Regulatory requirement of single-use plastic products have to be marked: EU regulation 2020/2151. Note: The language(s) on the label may vary by country.</description></code>
  <code><value>MADE_WITH_CANADIAN_BEEF</value><name>Made with Canadian Beef</name><description>Canada Beef Inc. is an independent national organization representing the research, marketing and promotion of the Canadian cattle and beef industry worldwide. Its efforts to maximize demand for Canadian beef and optimize the value of Canadian beef products is funded by cattle producers and the National Beef Check-Off, which in turn makes it possible to access beef industry market development funds provided by the Government of Canada and the Government of Alberta.</description></code>
  <code><value>MAITRE_ARTISAN</value><name>Maitre artisan</name><description>A product containing the Maitre Artisan label that an experienced craftsman (more than 3 years experience) made the product and recognises their ability as a craftsman. Also, they have obtained a technician certificate (Obtained in 2 years of study).</description></code>
  <code><value>MARINE_STEWARDSHIP_COUNCIL_LABEL</value><name></name><description>The MSC is the world's leading certification and ecolabelling program for sustainable seafood. Look for the blue MSC ecolabel when shopping or dining out. The item is physically marked with the Marine Stewardship Council label.</description></code>
  <code><value>MAX_HAVELAAR</value><name>Fairtrade Max Havelaar</name><description>Fair trade Max Havelaar symbol awarded to manufacturers which contribute to improving the living and working conditions of small farmers and agricultural workers in disadvantaged regions. This symbol may also be used in France and Switzerland.</description></code>
  <code><value>MCIA_ORGANIC</value><name>MCIA Organic </name><description>MCIA is an Accredited Certifying Agent (ACA) authorized by the USDA National Organic Program (NOP) to provide organic certification that allows you to display the NOP Certified Organic seal on qualified products. </description></code>
  <code><value>MEHR_WEG</value><name></name><description>Mehrweg platform for the promotion of Austrian refillable beverage containers and returnable transport packaging. In addition to the website as an information centre and forum for discussion mehrweg.at is targeted lobbying activity for reuse systems.</description></code>
  <code><value>MILIEUKEUR</value><name></name><description>Products and services with Milieukeur are produced with a lower impact on the environment and respect for working conditions, animal welfare and food safety. This is applicable for the Dutch market.</description></code>
  <code><value>MJOLK_FRAN_SVERIGE</value><name>Mjolk Fran Sverige</name><description>The ‘Från Sverige’, ‘Kött från Sverige’ and ‘Mjölk från Sweden’ origin labelling scheme is a joint initiative of the Swedish Food Federation, Svensk Dagligvaruhandel (Swedish Food Traders) and the Federation of Swedish Farmers (MILK)</description></code>
  <code><value>MOMS_CHOICE_AWARD</value><name>Mom’s Choice Award</name><description>The Mom’s Choice Awards® (MCA) evaluates products and services created for children, families and educators. The program is globally recognized for establishing the benchmark of excellence in family-friendly media, products and services. The organization is based in the United States and has reviewed thousands of items from more than 55 countries.</description></code>
  <code><value>MONTREAL_VAAD_HAIR_PAREVE</value><name>Montreal Vaad Hair Mk Pareve</name><description>Montreal Vaad Hair (MK) - Pareve Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>MPS_A</value><name></name><description>MPS-A is an environmental registration certificates. The qualification is awarded to participants who record their usage of crop protection agents, fertilisers,  energy and waste. The qualification MPS-A stands for most environmentally-friendly cultivation. The qualifications MPS-B, MPS-C and MPS-D also exist depending on the earned points.</description></code>
  <code><value>MUNDUSVINI_GOLD</value><name></name><description>The "GOLD" award of the Great MUNDUS VINI International Wine Awards. At least 90 points must be achieved in the judging of the wines by the international jury. Only the wines achieving the highest number of points in this range will receive the gold medal. This means that the minimum number of points required for this award may be higher.</description></code>
  <code><value>MUNDUSVINI_SILVER</value><name></name><description>The "SILVER" award of the Great MUNDUS VINI International Wine Awards. At least 85 points must be achieved in the judging of the wines by the international jury. Only the wines achieving the highest number of points in this range will receive the gold medal. This means that the minimum number of points required for this award may be higher.</description></code>
  <code><value>MUSLIM_JUDICIAL_COUNCIL_HALAAL_TRUST</value><name>Muslim Judicial Council Halaal Trust</name><description>Internationally, the Muslim Judicial Council Halaal Trust (MJCHT) is well-known and acknowledged by various renowned Halal Certifying Bodies or Authorities (HCB) from numerous countries,.</description></code>
  <code><value>MY_CLIMATE</value><name></name><description>The non-profit foundation myclimate – The Climate Protection Partnership, is an international initiative with Swiss origins. Founded in 2002 as an ETH Zurich spinoff, myclimate is among the world leaders when it comes to voluntary carbon offsetting measures. </description></code>
  <code><value>NAOOA_CERTIFIED_QUALITY</value><name>NAOOA Certified Quality</name><description>The North American Olive Oil Association (NAOOA) offers a Certified Quality Seal Program as a way to recognize and promote olive oils that measure up to the industry's standards of excellence.</description></code>
  <code><value>NASAA_CERTIFIED_ORGANIC</value><name>NASAA (National Association for Sustainable Agriculture Australia) Certified Organic</name><description>The National Association for Sustainable Agriculture Australia (NASAA) plays a critically important role in supporting and promoting the adoption of sustainable agricultural practices that lead to safer and more sustainable food production systems. Our subsidiary business, NASAA Certified Organic (NCO), certifies organic commodities to meet all domestic and international export market requirements.</description></code>
  <code><value>NATRUE_LABEL</value><name></name><description>The NATRUE Label guarantees that the products that carry it are made only with natural and organic ingredients, through soft manufacturing processes and environmentally friendly practices. The NATRUE Label is awarded by NATRUE, a non-profit organisation committed to promote and protect high standards of quality and environmental integrity. See: http://www.natrue.org/home/</description></code>
  <code><value>NATURE_ET_PROGRES</value><name>Nature Et Progres</name><description>Nature et Progrès operates as a PGS with its own private organic standard and its own certification procedures (involving peer review). The aim of the initiative is to grant an organic quality guarantee on the basis of its 15 different production standards (vegetable, livestock, cosmetics, wine, beer, etc.) and of its Ethical Chart, defined through a participatory approach by its members. Since 2011, these standards are part of the IFOAM Family of Standards and IFOAM - Organics International has endorsed Nature et Progrès through its PGS recognition program. </description></code>
  <code><value>NATUREPLUS</value><name></name><description>Natureplus is the international label of quality for all building and accommodation products, which provides an orientation towards sustainability for all those involved in the building process. Products which carry this label are characterised by their high level of quality in the areas of health, the environment and functionality. </description></code>
  <code><value>NATURLAND</value><name></name><description>Naturland promotes organic agriculture the world over and its 53,000 members make it one of the major organic farming associations. As a forward-looking association, Naturland attributes the same importance to issues of social responsibility as to organic expertise. </description></code>
  <code><value>NATURLAND_FAIR_TRADE</value><name></name><description>Naturland established in 2005 with its social standards. It now has erected a third pillar of sustainability to provide added support to our organic association’s holistic concept: International partners can apply for certification to Naturland for fair trade standards in the course of their annual organic inspection. 
http://www.naturland.de/fairzertifizierung.html. </description></code>
  <code><value>NATURLAND_WILDFISH</value><name>Naturland Wildfish</name><description>Naturland is an association of organic farmers, and develops standards for organic farming. Naturland has also developed a standard for sustainable fishing. This standard considers sustainability from a holistic perspective and includes ecological and social and economic factors, such as food quality and working conditions, in the assessment. Not only the effects of the fishing practices themselves, but also of the product processing are assessed. The assessment is carried out by an independent expert and there is a possibility for public participation. The supply chain history of the fish products is easily traceable.</description></code>
  <code><value>NC_NATURAL_COSMETICS_STANDARD</value><name>NC Natural Cosmetics Standard</name><description>Products bearing the Natural Cosmetics Standard (NCS) label undergo in-depth tests and fulfil the highest quality requirements ensuring the products are consist of natural original materials.</description></code>
  <code><value>NC_NATURAL_COSMETICS_STANDARD_ORGANIC_QUALITY</value><name>NC Natural Cosmetics Standard organic quality</name><description>Products bearing the Natural Cosmetics Standard (NCS) label undergo in-depth tests and fulfil the highest quality requirements ensuring the products are consist of natural original materials and a minimum of 95% organic sources.</description></code>
  <code><value>NC_VEGAN_NATURAL_COSMETICS</value><name>NC Vegan Natural Cosmetics</name><description>Products bearing the Natural Cosmetics Standard (NCS) label undergo in-depth tests and fulfil the highest quality requirements ensuring the products are consist of natural original materials, neither from nor by animal products.</description></code>
  <code><value>NC_VEGAN_NATURAL_COSMETICS_STANDARD_ORGANIC_QUALITY</value><name>NC Vegan Natural Cosmetics Standard organic quality</name><description>Products bearing the Natural Cosmetics Standard (NCS) label undergo in-depth tests and fulfil the highest quality requirements ensuring the products are consist of natural original materials with organic  and vegan quality.</description></code>
  <code><value>NCA_GLUTEN_FREE</value><name>National Celiac Association- Gluten Free</name><description>The National Celiac Association is dedicated to educating and advocating for individuals with celiac disease and non-celiac gluten sensitivities, their families, and communities throughout the nation. https://nationalceliac.org/</description></code>
  <code><value>NDOA</value><name></name><description>Nevada Department of Agriculture (NDOA) - The Nevada Organic Certification Program provides assurance to consumers who purchase organic products by verifying that products were grown and handled according to USDA National Organic Program standards. The program also benefits Nevada's agricultural producers and handlers by providing an in-state organic certification service which allows eligible operations to market agricultural products as “organic”.</description></code>
  <code><value>NEA</value><name>NEA Seal of Acceptance™</name><description>As a service to individuals and the corporate community, and to encourage/recognize product innovations that provide benefits and improve the quality of life for people with eczema and sensitive skin, the National Eczema Association has established the NEA Seal of Acceptance™ program.</description></code>
  <code><value>NEULAND</value><name></name><description> The Neuland logo marks meat and meat products which have humane and environmentally friendly livestock origin. The high demands of the marking based on guidelines, which include among others criteria on housing, feeding and transporting the animals. The seal was founded in 1988, by the Verein für tiergerechte und umwelt-schonende Nutztierhaltung e. V. Sponsors by BUND and the Arbeitsgemeinschaft Bäuerliche Landwirtschaft. </description></code>
  <code><value>NF_MARQUE</value><name></name><description>The NF mark is a French collective certification mark. It guarantees the quality and safety of the products and services certified. The NF mark guarantees compliance not only with current standards, but also with additional quality criteria that meet consumers' needs.</description></code>
  <code><value>NFCA_GLUTEN_FREE</value><name>Gluten-free Certified: Allergen Control Group/ National Foundation for Celiac Awareness (NFCA)</name><description>NFCA endorsed GFCP trademark – for use on products destined for sale in the United States.  This is a registered trademark owned by the National Foundation for Celiac Awareness who grants exclusive rights to ACG as part of operating the Gluten-Free Certification Program.</description></code>
  <code><value>NIX18</value><name>Nix18</name><description>The NIX18 campaign is to strengthen the social norm "do not drink and smoke until your 18". The initiative is from the Dutch Ministry of Health, Welfare and Sport and a large number of partners (Koninklijke Horeca Netherlands, KWF Cancer, Lung Fund, Trimbos Institute, NOC * NSF, supermarkets united in the Food Retail, GGD Netherlands, Thuiswinkel.org, the Dutch Food Safety Authority and the Ministry of Security and Justice). The campaign focuses on the whole society, in particular the area of youth. </description></code>
  <code><value>NMX</value><name>NMX</name><description>The Mexican Standards (NMX) are technical regulations issued by the Ministry of Economy whose application is voluntary and that allow to establish quality specifications on processes, products, services, test methods, competences, etc., as well as helping in the orientation of the consumer.</description></code>
  <code><value>NOM</value><name>NOM</name><description>It is the symbol that allows the consumer to verify that the products comply with the official regulations of our country that apply to them.
Compliance with the Official Mexican Standards (NOM) is mandatory for producers, manufacturers, importers and service providers, as they provide the consumer with confidence and confidence in the products they purchase.</description></code>
  <code><value>NON_GMO_BY_EARTHKOSHER</value><name>Non-GMO By Earthkosher</name><description>EarthKosher’s non-GMO Certification Program evaluates the final product from its’ initial stages of ingredient sourcing, handling and throughout the production process until it reaches the store shelf. By evaluating and controlling the sourcing, handling, production and distribution of the  products, EarthKosher’s non-GMO Certification Program ensures that the company’s products are non-GMO compliant and safe. </description></code>
  <code><value>NON_GMO_PROJECT</value><name></name><description>The Non-GMO Project is a non-profit organization committed to preserving and building the non-GMO food supply, educating consumers, and providing verified non-GMO choices. The verification seal indicates that the product bearing the seal has gone through the Non-GMO Project verification process. Verification is an assurance that a product has been produced according to consensus-based best practices for GMO avoidance.</description></code>
  <code><value>NPA</value><name></name><description>Natural Products Association (NPA) - The Science and Regulatory Affairs Department at NPA oversees the TruLabel® program and is charged with implementing education and certification programs—third-party certified good manufacturing practices (GMPs) for all supply members.  </description></code>
  <code><value>NSF</value><name></name><description>National Standards Foundation (NSF) accredited third-party certification provides all stakeholders – industry, regulators, users and the general public – assurance that a certified product, material, component or service complies with the technical requirements of the referenced standard.  The NSF certification process is specific to the product, process or service being certified and the type of certification.</description></code>
  <code><value>NSF_CERTIFIED_FOR_SPORT</value><name>NSF Certified For Sport</name><description>The NSF - Certified for Sport certification includes all products that have published the NSF - Certified for Sport stamp on their package. NSF's Certified for Sport® Program helps athletes, coaches, dietitians and trainers make more informed decisions when choosing sports supplements. The program is recognized by NFL, NFLPA, MLB, MLBPA, PGA, LPGA, NHL, CPSDA, Taylor Hooton Foundation and CCES. </description></code>
  <code><value>NSF_GLUTEN_FREE</value><name>NSF Gluten Free </name><description>http://www.nsf.org/consumer-resources/what-is-nsf-certification/gluten-free-certification</description></code>
  <code><value>NSF_NON_GMO_TRUE_NORTH</value><name>NSF Non GMO True North </name><description>http://www.nsf.org/services/by-industry/food-safety-quality/label-claims/gmo-transparency</description></code>
  <code><value>NSF_SUSTAINABILITY_CERTIFIED</value><name>NSF Sustainability Certified</name><description>The NSF Sustainability certification attribute includes all products that have published the NSF Sustainability Certified seal on their packaging. </description></code>
  <code><value>NSM</value><name>Transport Canada National Safety Mark (NSM)
e.g., child car seats</name><description>The national safety mark (NSM) is the property of the Government of Canada and its use is authorized by the Minister of Transport to manufacturers of new vehicles offered for sale in Canada. Transport Canada requires the manufacturers that are authorized to affix the mark, to have the capability to certify their vehicle production to comply with the regulations under the Motor Vehicle Safety Act.</description></code>
  <code><value>NYCKELHALET</value><name></name><description>The green key hole is to be put on the healthy foods in Sweden, Denmark, and Norway within certain product groups in order to make it easier for the customers to make a healthy choice. http://www.norden.org/</description></code>
  <code><value>OCEAN_WISE</value><name>Ocean Wise Recommended Sourced Responsibly</name><description>Ocean Wise is a Vancouver Aquarium conservation program, created to help businesses and their customers make environmentally friendly choices. The Ocean Wise symbol next to a seafood item assures you that option is the best choice for the health of the oceans</description></code>
  <code><value>OCIA</value><name></name><description>Organic Crop Improvement Association (OCIA) International provides certification services to thousands of organic farmers, processors and handlers in North, Central and South America, and Asia.</description></code>
  <code><value>OCQV_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Organisme de Certification Québec Vrai (OCQV)</name><description>Québec Vrai is accredited (no. AC-07-03) for certifying organic products in accordance with ISO / IEC Guide 65:1996 through the Reserved Designations and Added-Value Claims Board (CARTV). This is the only provincial authority that is responsible for the management and protection of reserved designations in Quebec. It is by virtue of the powers conferred by the Act Respecting Reserved Designations and Added-Value Claims (RSQ cA-20.03) and the recognition granted by the United States Department of Agriculture under Regulation 7 CFR § 205.500 (1) that the CARTV allows organic certification for agricultural and food products (goods and services). Québec Vrai is also accredited to verify the Chain of Custody of certified products. The requirements for organic certification are contained in the Quebec Organic Reference Standards and the National Organic Program (NOP) Regulations.</description></code>
  <code><value>OECD_BIO_INGREDIENTS</value><name>Biodegradable Ingredients</name><description>This Test Guideline is a screening method for the evaluation of ready biodegradability of chemicals.</description></code>
  <code><value>OEKO_CONTROL</value><name></name><description>ÖkoControl is a subsidiary of the Europäischen Verbands ökologischer Einrichtungshäuser e.V., in which about 50 ecologically engaged furniture dealers have joined forces. The objective of this eco-leading group is to provide consumers, retailers and manufacturers with more safety in a healthy living. With ÖkoControl the association has created a powerful tool to control the products offered. </description></code>
  <code><value>OEKO_KREISLAUF</value><name></name><description>Ökologischer Kreislauf Moorbad Harbach The label marks agricultural products grown organically that progress towards an entire organic production chain, which is both socially just and ecologically responsible.</description></code>
  <code><value>OEKO_QUALITY_GUARANTEE_BAVARIA</value><name></name><description> Öko Qualität Garantiert Bayern is for products of organic farming origin in Bavaria a regional eco-label organic quality guaranteed Bavarian. This is maintained by Bayerisches Staatsministerium für Ernährung, Landwirtschaft und Forsten (StMELF)</description></code>
  <code><value>OEKO_TEX_LABEL</value><name></name><description>Confidence in textiles.This has been the motto of the independent test institutes of the International Oeko-Tex®  Association since 1992, with their tests for harmful substances according to Oeko-Tex®  Standard 100 for textile products of all types which pose no risk whatsoever to health. See www.oeko-tex.com</description></code>
  <code><value>OEUFS_DE_FRANCE</value><name>Oeufs de France</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case eggs: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>OFF_ORGANIC</value><name>Food Federation</name><description>It shows that the  product complies with organic regulations.  The Organic Food Federation is one of the UK’s leading certification bodies operating nationally in all areas of organics.UKAS accredited to ISO/IEC 17065:2012.</description></code>
  <code><value>OFFICIAL_ECO_LABEL_SUN</value><name></name><description>Luomo Sun Sign Denotes controlled organic production. The official label of the Finnish inspection authorities; owned by the Ministry of Agriculture and Forestry. http://opetus.ruokatieto.fi/</description></code>
  <code><value>OFG_ORGANIC</value><name>Farmers &amp; Growers (Organic Certification UK2)</name><description>Organic Certification is OF&amp;G’s main inspection and certification scheme, and is relevant to the majority of licensees.
The programme is based on the European Organic Regulation which sets the core standards organic producers must adhere to across the EU (regulation EC 834/2007).</description></code>
  <code><value>OHNE_GEN_TECHNIK</value><name></name><description>VLOG controls the “Ohne GenTechnik” product seal ­­(GM-free, produced without genetic engineering). The “Ohne GenTechnik” seal enables consumers to choose foods that have been produced without genetic engineering and to support GM-free agriculture.</description></code>
  <code><value>OK_COMPOST_VINCOTTE</value><name>OK Compost label by Vincotte</name><description>Packaging or products featuring the OK Compost label by Vincotte are guaranteed as biodegradable in an industrial composting plant. This applies to all components, inks and additives. The sole reference point for the certification programme is the harmonised EN 13432: 2000 standard: in any event any product featuring the OK compost logo complies with the requirements of the EU Packaging Directive (94/62/EEC).</description></code>
  <code><value>OK_KOSHER</value><name>OK Kosher Certification</name><description>OK Kosher Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>OKOTEST</value><name></name><description>Ökotest  is a magazine that tests product for of the health risks, side effects  environmental impact. They issue labels to products which have passed their tests for safety and publish results in their magazine.</description></code>
  <code><value>ONE_PERCENT_FOR_THE_PLANET</value><name>1% for the Planet</name><description>1% for the Planet is a global movement inspiring businesses and individuals to support environmental solutions (Education, alternative transportation, fossil fuel efficiency, etc.) through annual memberships and everyday actions.</description></code>
  <code><value>ONTARIO_APPROVED</value><name>Ontario approved legend - Inspected meat products, provincially licensed plants</name><description>Inspection of a food animal by an inspector in accordance with Part VIII before the animal is slaughtered; (“inspection ante mortem”)</description></code>
  <code><value>ONTARIO_PORK</value><name>Made with Ontario Pork</name><description>Ontario Pork represents over 1, 500 pork farmers across the province in consumer education, research, government representation, environmental issues, animal care and food quality assurance. Ontario Pork acts as the official spokes-group for the industry and is a source of information about all things pork and pigs.</description></code>
  <code><value>ORBI</value><name></name><description>ORBI Organic Bio is a community of farmers to enhance organic agriculture and is the pioneer group of organic-organic farming in Austria.</description></code>
  <code><value>OREGON_KOSHER</value><name>Kosher Oregon Kosher</name><description>Oregon Kosher is a non-profit organization dedicated to promoting Kashrus through supervision, education, and research.
certifies many food production facilities, bakeries, and wineries here in the Pacific Northwest. We have become an affordable kosher certification accepted across the globe. Oregon Kosher</description></code>
  <code><value>OREGON_TILTH</value><name>Oregon Tilth</name><description>Oregon Tilth provides certification services of the highest quality that reflect and respect your dedication to organics. Regardless of where you are in the certification process, our staff is committed to providing you with excellent customer service and technical assistance to ensure that your certification experience is educational, transparent and timely. </description></code>
  <code><value>ORGANIC_100_CONTENT_STANDARD</value><name></name><description>The Organic Content Standard (OCS) relies on third-party verification to verify a final product contains the accurate amount of a given organically grown material.</description></code>
  <code><value>ORGANIC_COTTON</value><name>Organic Cotton</name><description>Organic cotton is grown without the use of toxic and persistent pesticides, fungicides and synthetic fertilizers.
*No formaldehyde is used in finishing product.
*These all impact our environment and the people who have to farm the cotton as well. The organic cotton is a kinder choice to the earth and to the workers.
*Organic cotton has not been exposed to metals and chemicals, and this likely gives the fabric lasting strength over time.
*Organic cotton has strict standards in the way it is manufactured. We feel good about giving our dogs and yours a fabric that is grown, processed and dyed in a rigorous manner, purchased from excellent sources that meet the certification requirements of organic materials.</description></code>
  <code><value>ORGANIC_TRADE_ASSOCIATION</value><name>Organic Trade Association </name><description>Organic Trade Association on behalf of their membership, promotes and protects organic agriculture and trade through legislative and regulatory advocacy in Canada and US.</description></code>
  <code><value>ORIGIN_OF_EGGS</value><name>Origin of eggs</name><description>"The label indicates the ""Origin of eggs - approved by KAT"". The label guarantees the actual origin of  eggs used for egg products or food production. 

Egg products with this label may only be produced from eggs from KAT-certified laying farms. This means that only KAT eggs may be used for the production of KAT egg products. This is the only way to guarantee a cross-stage traceability throughout the entire process chain from the laying farm to the egg product factory and the food industry.

"</description></code>
  <code><value>ORIGINE_FRANCE_GARANTIE</value><name>Origine France Garantie</name><description>The Origine France Garantie certification was created in June 2010 following the publication of Yves Jégo's report on the France brand.

The certification, simple and understandable by all, is the result of a collective approach of actors who wish to work together to promote the "produce in France" and the valorization of industrial and artisan know-how.

The Pro France association which promotes Origine France Garantie is made up of business leaders supporting this initiative. Its goal is:

Give clear and precise information to the consumer about the French origin of the products
Make known the companies that manufacture in France
The Origine France Garantie certification distinguishes itself from other mentions such as "made in France", "designed in France", "Made in France" ... which are self-declarative and too loose.

Origine France Garantie is the only certification that certifies the French origin of a product. It is transversal (all sectors combined) and indisputable (certification, mandatory, is carried out by an independent certifying body).

The Origine France Garantie certification ensures consumers traceability of the product by giving a clear and objective indication of origin.

Certification is achieved through two cumulative criteria that companies must meet to obtain it:

Between 50% and 100% of the unit cost is French
The product takes its essential characteristics in France</description></code>
  <code><value>OTCO_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body - OTCO (OREGON TILTH  CERTIFIED ORGANIC),
Oregon, U.S.A.</name><description>Oregon Tilth is a leading nonprofit certifier, educator and advocate for organic agriculture and products since 1974. Our mission to make our food system and agriculture biologically sound and socially equitable requires us to find practical ways to tackle big challenges. We advance this mission to balance the needs of people and planet through focus on core areas of certification, conservation, public health, policy and the marketplace.</description></code>
  <code><value>OU_KOSHER</value><name>Orthodox Union Kosher </name><description>Orthodox Union: the oldest Orthodox Jewish organisations in the United States. It is best known for its kosher certification service. Its circled-U symbol, Ⓤ, a hechsher mark, is found on the labels of many kosher commercial and consumer food products. https://oukosher.org/</description></code>
  <code><value>OU_KOSHER_DAIRY</value><name>OU Kosher Dairy</name><description>The Hebrew word “kosher” means fit or proper as it relates to Jewish dietary law. Kosher foods are permitted to be eaten, and can be used as ingredients in the production of additional food items. Products bearing the OU-D logo are certified kosher by the Orthodox Union and are or contain dairy.

</description></code>
  <code><value>OU_KOSHER_FISH</value><name>OU Kosher Fish</name><description>The Hebrew word “kosher” means fit or proper as it relates to Jewish dietary law. Kosher foods are permitted to be eaten, and can be used as ingredients in the production of additional food items. Products bearing the OU-Fish logo are certified kosher by the Orthodox Union and are or contain fish.

</description></code>
  <code><value>OU_KOSHER_MEAT</value><name>OU Kosher Meat</name><description>The Hebrew word “kosher” means fit or proper as it relates to Jewish dietary law. Kosher foods are permitted to be eaten, and can be used as ingredients in the production of additional food items. Products bearing the OU-Meat logo are certified kosher by the Orthodox Union and are or contain meat.

</description></code>
  <code><value>OU_KOSHER_PASSOVER</value><name>OU Kosher Passover</name><description>The Hebrew word “kosher” means fit or proper as it relates to Jewish dietary law. Kosher foods are permitted to be eaten, and can be used as ingredients in the production of additional food items. Products bearing the OU-P logo are certified kosher for Passover by the Orthodox Union.
 </description></code>
  <code><value>OZONE_FRIENDLY_GENERAL_CLAIM</value><name></name><description>A mark or label on a trade item communicating that the trade item itself, associated production processes and/or packaging do not produce gases that are harmful to the ozone layer during the trade item’s entire life cycle. There is currently no standard definition for the term. There is no organization independently certifying this claim. The producer or manufacturer decides and self-declares to use the claim and is not free from its own self-interest.</description></code>
  <code><value>PACS_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body –Pacific Agricultural Certification
Society (PACS), British Columbia, Canada</name><description>The PACS is an incorporated society within the province of British Columbia and as a not for profit society is controlled by the clients it serves. As there are no profits, fees are tied directly to costs. The PACS has a number of programs including Canada Organic Regime organic certification, which gives clients the option of exporting to other provinces, the USA and overseas. We certify enterprises Canada wide.</description></code>
  <code><value>PALEO_APPROVED</value><name>Paleo Approved </name><description>The Paleo Foundation was first organized for the purpose of helping Paleo Diet Adherents easily identify products that met the basic tenets of the diet.  The Paleo Approved Certification Program certifies Farms and Ranches that meet requirements for species-appropriate diet, and environmentally beneficial husbandry practices. Differing from other Paleo Certifications, Paleo Approved Standards vary by species.</description></code>
  <code><value>PALEO_BY_EARTHKOSHER</value><name>Paleo By Earthkosher</name><description>EarthKosher offers joint Kosher + Paleo certification. What further distinguishes the EarthKosher Paleo certified symbol, is that EarthKosher actually inspects certified companies on an ongoing basis to insure that they strictly comply with Paleo standards. This approach exceeds the standards of other forms of Paleo Certification, which simply ask for a list of ingredients, and based on this alone, provide Paleo Certification. </description></code>
  <code><value>PARENT_TESTED_PARENT_APPROVED</value><name>Parent Tested Parent Approved (PTPA) Winner’s Seal of Approval</name><description>Parent Tested Parent Approved is about putting your product in the hands of real parents, listening to their honest opinions and letting your new brand advocates spread the word about how awesome your product is for families</description></code>
  <code><value>PAVILLON_FRANCE</value><name>Pavillon France</name><description>It is the collective brand involving all the actors of the French fishing valuing its trades, its commitments and its products. It is supported by the association "France Filière Pêche", an association of interprofessional nature, that is to say which gathers all the links of the sector</description></code>
  <code><value>PCO</value><name></name><description>Pennsylvania Certified Organic (PCO) is a USDA-accredited organic certifying agency that educates and certifies growers, processors and handlers of organic crops, wild crops, livestock and livestock products in Pennsylvania and adjoining states.</description></code>
  <code><value>PEFC</value><name></name><description>Programme for Endorsement of Forest Certification (PEFCC_ is an international non-profit, non-governmental organisation dedicated to promoting Sustainable Forest Management (SFM) through independent third-party certification</description></code>
  <code><value>PEFC_CERTIFIED</value><name></name><description>PEFC Programme for the Endorsement of Forest Certification Schemes
PEFC Certified:  at least 70% of wood from PEFC-certified forests that meets or exceeds PEFC’s Sustainability Benchmark requirements and recycled material; and wood from controlled sources. The overall content of recycled material shall not be higher than 85%.  Where the product does not include recycled material, the label claim shall be used without the world 'recycled'.</description></code>
  <code><value>PEFC_RECYCLED</value><name></name><description>PEFC Programme for the Endorsement of Forest Certification Schemes: PEFC Recycled
 at least 70%,  PEFC certified material from recycled sources; and  wood from controlled sources.</description></code>
  <code><value>PET_TO_PET</value><name></name><description>PET to PET stands for a company responsible for the recycling of PET bottles.</description></code>
  <code><value>PGI_CNIPA</value><name>Protected Geographical Indication-CNIPA</name><description>A special mark granted by the China National Intellectual Property Administration (CNIPA) for a product protected by a geographical indication.</description></code>
  <code><value>PGI_GAQSIQ</value><name>Protected Geographical Indication-GAQSIQ</name><description>A special mark granted by the former General Administration of Quality Supervision, Inspection and Quarantine of China (GAQSIQ) for a product protected by a geographical indication.</description></code>
  <code><value>PGI_MARA</value><name>Protected Geographical Indication-MARA</name><description>A special mark granted by the Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Affairs of China (MARA) for an agro-product protected by a geographical indication.</description></code>
  <code><value>PGI_TO_SAIC</value><name>Protected Geographical Indication-TO-SAIC</name><description>A special mark granted by the Trademark Office of the State Administration for Industry and Commerce of China (TO-SAIC) for a product protected by a geographical indication.</description></code>
  <code><value>PLASTIC_IN_FILTER_TOBACCO</value><name>Single-use plastic in tobacco products with filters.</name><description>Labelled on packaging "Plastic in Filter" of tobacco products with filters, and packaging for filters marketed for use in combination with tobacco products . Regulatory requirement of single-use plastic products have to be marked: EU regulation 2020/2151. Note: The language(s) on the label may vary by country.</description></code>
  <code><value>PLASTIC_IN_PRODUCT_BEVERAGE_CUPS</value><name>Single-use plastic in beverage cups.</name><description>Labelled on beverage cups containing plastic.  Regulatory requirement of single-use plastic products have to be marked: EU regulation 2020/2151. Note: The language(s) on the label may vary by country.</description></code>
  <code><value>PLASTIC_IN_PRODUCT_TAMPONS</value><name>Single-use plastic tampons and tampon applicators.</name><description>Labelled on packaging of tampons and tampon applicators containing plastic. Regulatory requirement of single-use plastic in products have to be marked: EU regulation 2020/2151. Note: The language(s) on the label may vary by country.</description></code>
  <code><value>PLASTIC_IN_PRODUCT_WIPES_SANITARY_PADS</value><name>Single-use plastic in wipes and sanitary towels (pads).</name><description>Labelled on packaging of personal wipes and sanitary towels (pads) containing plastic.  Regulatory requirement of single-use plastic products have to be marked: EU regulation 2020/2151. Note: The language(s) on the label may vary by country.</description></code>
  <code><value>PLASTIC_NEUTRAL</value><name>Plastic neutral</name><description>"Indicates that partners ensure to compensate an equivalent amount of plastic brought to the market in cooperation with Plastic Bank. Plastic Bank neutralize the product’s plastic footprint and helps to improve lives by cleaning the environment.

"</description></code>
  <code><value>POMMES_DE_TERRES_DE_FRANCE</value><name>Pommes de Terres de France</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case potatoes: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".  Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs. Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>PREGNANCY_WARNING</value><name>Pregnancy warning</name><description>The purpose of the pregnancy icon is making clear to pregnant women that they should not drink alcoholic beverages. Legislation or self-regulation is country dependent.</description></code>
  <code><value>PRO_TERRA_NON_GMO_CERTIFICATION</value><name>Pro-Terra Non-GMO Certification </name><description>Pro-Terra Non-GMO Certification attribute includes all products that present a Pro-Terra Non-GMO logo.  </description></code>
  <code><value>PROCERT_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Pro-Cert Organic Systems, Saskatchewan, Canada</name><description>Pro-Cert provides professional organic certification services to the following Standards/Regulations:
1.The Canadian Organic Standard (CAN/CGSB - 32.310 and 32.311) and Organic Products Regulation (OPR)
2.Equivalency to the European Organic Program
3.The USDA National Organic Program (NOP)
4.The Quebec Organic Program (CARTV)
5.Japanese Agricultural Standard (JAS via CERES)
6.BIOSUISSE (Switzerland) - Data collection only
7.Brazil Organic Program (via IBD)

The above programs provide global access for Pro-Cert clients.  Unregulated countries accept these programs and arrangements for organic status.</description></code>
  <code><value>PRODERM</value><name></name><description>proDERM address manufacturers of high quality products who do not fear an intense test.To meet qualification a the formula must meet current dermatological and toxicological standards. And the product must have been tested in two independent studies. These would usually be a consumer orientated study (i. e. a Use-test in which the products are self-applied at home) and a tolerability study (a patch test appropriate for the product)</description></code>
  <code><value>PRODUCT_OF_THE_YEAR_CONSUMER_SURVEY</value><name>Product of the Year, Consumer Survey</name><description>Product of the Year™ is the world’s largest consumer-voted award for product innovation. Product of the Year is a champion of innovation, is voted on by consumers and is recognized globally. Product of the Year currently operates in 40 countries with the same goal: to guide consumers to the most innovative products in their market and reward the entrants for quality and innovation.

In Canada, the Product of the Year seal is backed by the votes of thousands of Canadian consumers, serving as a shortcut for shoppers to save time and money. For entrants of the winning products, the award is a powerful marketing message proven to increase product awareness, trial and quality.
</description></code>
  <code><value>PRODUIT_EN_BRETAGNE</value><name>Produit en Bretagne</name><description>Originally designed to indicate the Breton origin of the product, the logo displays it in letters. It is during a family meal in Savoy that one of the Breton entrepreneurs hears from his brother, which for him, Savoyard, was representative of our region: a lighthouse, a map of Brittany, a light beam. This is how the current logo was born, on a corner of paper tablecloth.

This sketch was brought back to Brittany and acclaimed by the members of the time.

After two years of tests in stores, and a very favourable reception from Scarmor stores (E. Leclerc stores), the logo is adopted and the statutes are fixed in 1995.</description></code>
  <code><value>PROTECTED_DESIGNATION_OF_ORIGIN</value><name></name><description>The Protected designation of origin is the name of an area, a specific place or, in exceptional cases, the name of a country, used as a designation for an agricultural product or a foodstuff,  the entire product must be traditionally and ENTIRELY manufactured (prepared, processed AND produced) within the specific region and thus acquire unique properties. Protected Geographical Status (PGS) is a legal framework defined in European Union law to protect the names of regional foods.</description></code>
  <code><value>PROTECTED_GEOGRAPHICAL_INDICATION</value><name></name><description>The Protected geographical indication is the name of an area, a specific place or, in exceptional cases, the name of a country, used as a description of an agricultural product or a foodstuff, the entire product must be traditionally and at least PARTIALLY manufactured (prepared, processed OR produced) within the specific region and thus acquire unique properties. Protected Geographical Status (PGS) is a legal framework[1] defined in European Union law to protect the names of regional foods.</description></code>
  <code><value>PROTECTED_HARVEST_CERTIFIED</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked with the Protected Harvest Certified symbol.</description></code>
  <code><value>PROVEN_QUALITY_BAVARIA</value><name></name><description>The quality label "Geprüfte Qualität Bayern" is featuring agriculture and food industry of Bavaria. Support of the sign by the State of Bavaria, represented by the Bavarian State Ministry for Food, Agriculture and Forestry. The Ministry decides on the granting of licenses. The aim of the quality label is agricultural produce economic and nutritional products of high quality.</description></code>
  <code><value>PUHTAASTI_KOTIMAINEN</value><name></name><description>Seed leaf flag indicates vegetables, berries and flowers of Finnish origin. Its license is granted and monitored by the Finnish Horticultural Products Society. Products will be first-class quality and from environmentally friendly farming. Product quality is also monitored in stores. Vegetable products in connection with any vegetable raw material must be Finnish. www.sirkkalehti.fi .</description></code>
  <code><value>QAI</value><name></name><description>Quality Assurance International (QAI) is a leading USDA-accredited organic product certifying agency. QAI is an active leader in the organic industry, advocating for high integrity organic. QAI is committed to ensuring organic integrity at every link in the organic production chain and providing excellent customer service, domestically and internationally. QAI is a member of the NSF International family of companies. NSF is a global leader in public health and safety. QAI's certification programs are designed to provide certification services throughout the supply chain. QAI certification assures compliance with organic standards for: agricultural producers, food processing facilities, integrated manufacturing operations, contract packing operations, traders, distributors, retailers, and ultimately consumers.</description></code>
  <code><value>QCS_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Quality Certification Services (QCS), Florida, U.S.A.</name><description>QCS Offers Certification Internationally in All Areas of the Organic Supply Chain, as well as Several Food Safety and Ethical Certification Schemes.</description></code>
  <code><value>QS</value><name></name><description>QS is a quality assurance scheme for fresh foodstuffs that involves all participants in the food industry – from farm to shop. By inspecting and integrating the entire supply chain, the QS certification mark creates the basis for increased food safety and well-founded trust from the consumers.</description></code>
  <code><value>QS_PRODUCTION_PERMIT</value><name>QS Production Permit</name><description>The blue QS sign containing Chinese characters "生产许可" (Production Permit) on the packaging of products, as approved by relevant regulatory authorities.</description></code>
  <code><value>QUALITAET_TIROL</value><name>Qualitaet Tirol </name><description>Seal of quality for high-quality products from regional and small-scale farming and is awarded by the Agrarmarketing Tirol (AM Tirol). Products bearing this seal of approval are produced exclusively from Tyrolean raw materials and processed in the Tyrol.www.qualitaet.tirol.at, </description></code>
  <code><value>QUALITY_CONFORMANCE_MARKING_CN</value><name>Quality Conformance Marking China</name><description>Marks, signs or characters that are marked on the packaging of cosmetics, pet food and other products in China to declare that the item conforms to quality requirements, as specified by relevant regulations.</description></code>
  <code><value>QUALITY_MARK_IRELAND</value><name></name><description>Control IMO Organic farming is an alternative, environmentally friendly method of food production. It forbids the use of chemicals and requires production methods that respect animal welfare and do not damage the environment. The term â€˜organicâ€™ can only be used on food labels in Ireland if the food product meets strict Irish and EU organic standards and is licensed by an approved certification body.</description></code>
  <code><value>QUALITY_RHOEN</value><name></name><description>The logo represents the regional Rhön products. The products with this sign has a regional origin and quality of agricultural products and services on the basis of criteria the partially extend beyond legal requirements and came from this typical area.</description></code>
  <code><value>RABBINICAL_COUNCIL_OF_BRITISH_COLUMBIA</value><name>Rabbinical Council Of British Columbia BCK</name><description>Rabbinical Council of British Columbia Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>RABBINICAL_COUNCIL_OF_CALIFORNIA_(RCC)</value><name>Rabbinical Council Of California </name><description>Rabbinical Council of California (RCC) Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>RABBINICAL_COUNCIL_OF_NEW_ENGLAND</value><name>Rabbinical Council Of New England</name><description>Rabbinical Council of New England Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>RAINFOREST_ALLIANCE</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked with the Rainforest Alliance Certified symbol.</description></code>
  <code><value>RAINFOREST_ALLIANCE_PEOPLE_NATURE</value><name>Rainforest Alliance people &amp; nature</name><description>Rainforest Alliance people &amp; nature label indicates that partner supports a healthier planet and an improve quality of life for people in farming communities.</description></code>
  <code><value>RAL_QUALITY_CANDLES</value><name></name><description>This RAL (Reichs-Ausschuss für Lieferbedingungen) quality mark indicates, that the trade item complies with the standard of the  of the Quality Association for Candles in terms of raw materials, burning duration and burning behaviour. Compliance with these standards is monitored by DEKRA Umwelt GmbH.</description></code>
  <code><value>REAL_CALIFORNIA_CHEESE</value><name>Real California Cheese</name><description>The California Milk Advisory Board (CMAB), an instrumentality of the California Department of Food and Agriculture, exists for one purpose: to spread the word about the extraordinary dairy products made with Real California Milk. This label states that this is made with Califiornian cheese.</description></code>
  <code><value>REAL_CALIFORNIA_MILK</value><name>Real California Milk</name><description>The California Milk Advisory Board (CMAB), an instrumentality of the California Department of Food and Agriculture, exist for one purpose: to spread the word about the extraordinary dairy products made with Real California Milk.</description></code>
  <code><value>REAL_FOOD_SEAL</value><name>Real Food Seal</name><description>The dairy industry four decades ago created the REAL® Seal. It’s an assurance that you are buying a genuine dairy product, made with milk from cows on U.S. dairy farms, and meeting strict manufacturing requirements.</description></code>
  <code><value>RECUPEL</value><name></name><description>Recupel strives in Belgium for a better environment through optimal recovery of materials from waste of electrical devices. Recupel ensures that waste of electrical appliances are collected and processed in a sustainable and cost-effective manner.</description></code>
  <code><value>RECYCLABLE_GENERAL_CLAIM</value><name></name><description>A generic Recycling codes are used to identify the material from which an item is made, to facilitate easier recycling or other reprocessing. Multiple agencies use this design.</description></code>
  <code><value>REGIONAL_FOOD_CZECH</value><name>Regional Food Czech</name><description>Mark accredited by Czech Ministry of Agriculture to the best quality agricultural or food products from each region of the Czech Republic. </description></code>
  <code><value>REGIONALFENSTER</value><name></name><description>Products that bear the "Regionalfenster" for food, ensure greater transparency. Consumers can identify with the logo at a glance which foods actually come from the region indicated on the packaging. This gives consumers a nationwide uniform and reliable identification of regional products. The initiative was started by Bundesministerium für Ernährung, Landwirtschaft und Verbraucherschutz (BMELV).</description></code>
  <code><value>REGIONALTHEKE_FRANKEN</value><name></name><description>The logo "Regionaltheke Franken" identifies products by Frankish farmers and documented to be of regional origin and quality of agricultural products and services in this area. The quality criteria go in relation to the proof of origin partly legal specifications as well. The logo is pursuing a criteria and control system for regional products with the involvement of the Bundesverbands der Regionalbewegungen.</description></code>
  <code><value>RETURNABLE_PET_BOTTLE_NL</value><name>Returnable PET bottle (NL)</name><description>Statiegeld Nederland is the implementing organization for the Dutch deposit system for large and small PET bottles of soft drinks and water. The use of the logo is mandatory on large and small PET bottles from 1 July 2021, which are charged with a deposit and are registered in the deposit system. The logo makes it clear to consumers and collection points whether or not a package has a deposit associated with it.</description></code>
  <code><value>RHP</value><name></name><description>This quality mark is managed by the Foundation RHP. RHP optimizes and secures the quality of peat products, raw materials, potting soil compositions, substrates, soil supply and soil improvers.</description></code>
  <code><value>ROQUEFORT_RED_EWE</value><name>Roquefort red ewe</name><description>Roquefort is a cheese made from raw, whole ewe's milk, blue-veined and with a natural rind, produced exclusively in a large part of the department of Aveyron and a few communes in the departments of Aude, Lozère, Gard, Hérault and Tarn in the Occitanie region.</description></code>
  <code><value>ROUNDTABLE_ON_RESPONSIBLE_SOY</value><name>Round Table on Responsible Soy</name><description>The Round Table on Responsible Soy is a civil organisation that promotes responsible production, processing and trading of soy on a global level.

Encourage current and future soybean is produced in a responsible manner to reduce social and environmental impacts while maintaining or improving the economic status for the producer.
Through:
• The development, implementation and verification of a global standard
• The commitment of the stakeholders involved in the value chain of soybean.

That soy help to meet social needs, environmental and economic consequences of the present generation without compromising the resources and the welfare of future generations and allowing the construction of a better world through consensus and joint action.</description></code>
  <code><value>SAFE_FEED_SAFE_FOOD</value><name>Safe Feed Safe Food</name><description>Safe Feed/Safe Food Certification Program is designed for the total feed industry. The Safe Feed/Safe Food program establishes comprehensive standards of excellence that go beyond existing regulations to maximize food and feed safety. </description></code>
  <code><value>SAFE_QUALITY_FOOD</value><name>Safe Quality Food</name><description>The SQF Code offers a solution for primary producers, manufacturers, distributors, and brokers by creating one standard for food safety from farm to fork. Also, by requiring both regulatory and customer compliance, the SQF code is equipped for an ever evolving market. </description></code>
  <code><value>SAFER_CHOICE</value><name>Safer Choice</name><description>The United States Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) Safer Choice label helps consumers, businesses, and purchasers identify products which perform and contain ingredients that are safer for human health and the environment. The label is for products which meet requirements for: Safer chemical ingredients, Product performance, Packaging sustainability, Ingredient disclosure, Surveillance and audits, Volatile Organic Compounds (VOCs) emissions.  </description></code>
  <code><value>SALMON_SAFE_CERTIFICATION</value><name>Salmon Safe Certification</name><description>Salmon-Safe offers a series of peer-reviewed certification and accreditation programs linking site development land management practices with the protection of agricultural and urban watersheds. </description></code>
  <code><value>SALZBURGER_LAND_HERKUNFT</value><name>Salzburger Land Origin Certificate (Austria)</name><description>"Seal that marks products which are certified and guaranteed regional from the Austrian province Salzburg. 

www.garantiert-regional.at"</description></code>
  <code><value>SCHARRELVLEES</value><name></name><description>A symbol used in the Netherlands Target Market intended for meat based products which guarantees that the animals has been growth without the use of antibiotics.</description></code>
  <code><value>SCHLESWIG_HOLSTEIN_QUALITY</value><name></name><description>The label of the Chamber of Agriculture Schleswig-Holstein. All foods with this award are reviewed several times during a year by independent laboratories. Since product quality is closely linked to the process quality, the laboratories are testing the overall business as well. Through these measures, the requirements are met in terms of quality and taste of the label products. </description></code>
  <code><value>SCROLL_K</value><name>Vaad Hakashrus of Denver Scroll K Certification </name><description>Vaad Hakashrus of Denver (Scroll K) Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>SCS_RECYCLED_CONTENT_CERTIFICATION</value><name>SCS Recycled Content Certification (RCC)</name><description>SCS Recycled Content Certification (RCC) recognizes products made either in whole or part from recycled waste material in place of virgin raw materials. The percentage of post-consumer or pre-consumer recycled content is reported in compliance with Federal Trade Commission guidelines and ISO standards. </description></code>
  <code><value>SCS_SUSTAINABLY_GROWN</value><name>SCS Sustainably Grown</name><description>The certification program currently requires conformance with the Sustainably Grown Standard V1.3, which provides a comprehensive framework and common set of requirements grouped into three categories – Environmental Sustainability, Social &amp; Economic Sustainability, and Product Integrity. Agricultural crops of all types and production systems of all sizes are eligible.  </description></code>
  <code><value>SEACHOICE</value><name>SeaChoice</name><description>SeaChoice was created to help Canadian businesses and shoppers take an active role in supporting sustainable fisheries and aquaculture at all levels of the seafood supply chain. Based on scientific assessments, SeaChoice has created easy-to-use tools that help you make the best seafood choices.

Working in collaboration with the Monterey Bay Aquarium’s acclaimed Seafood Watch program, SeaChoice undertakes science-based seafood assessments, provides informative resources for consumers, and supports businesses through collaborative partnerships.</description></code>
  <code><value>SFC_MEMBER_SEAL</value><name>SFC Member Seal</name><description>The Sustainable Furnishings Council (SFC) Member Seal is a label representing those companies which have made a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability and to improvement. These companies are involved in the home furnishings industry. The Exemplary status is voluntary - all members make a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability, to transparency, and to continuous improvement. This seal is for basic members.</description></code>
  <code><value>SFC_MEMBER_SEAL_GOLD</value><name>SFC Member Seal Gold</name><description>The Sustainable Furnishings Council (SFC) Member Seal is a label representing those companies which have made a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability and to improvement. These companies are involved in the home furnishings industry. The Exemplary status is voluntary - all members make a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability, to transparency, and to continuous improvement. This seal is for gold level members.</description></code>
  <code><value>SFC_MEMBER_SEAL_PLATINUM</value><name>SFC Member Seal Platinum</name><description>The Sustainable Furnishings Council (SFC) Member Seal is a label representing those companies which have made a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability and to improvement. These companies are involved in the home furnishings industry. The Exemplary status is voluntary - all members make a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability, to transparency, and to continuous improvement. This seal is for platinum level members.</description></code>
  <code><value>SFC_MEMBER_SEAL_SILVER</value><name>SFC Member Seal Silver</name><description>The Sustainable Furnishings Council (SFC) Member Seal is a label representing those companies which have made a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability and to improvement. These companies are involved in the home furnishings industry. The Exemplary status is voluntary - all members make a public and verifiable commitment to sustainability, to transparency, and to continuous improvement. This seal is for silver level members.</description></code>
  <code><value>SGS_ORGANIC</value><name></name><description>SGS Our services enable companies to operate in a more sustainable manner by improving quality and productivity, reducing risk, verifying compliance and increasing speed to market.</description></code>
  <code><value>SHOPPER_ARMY</value><name>Shopper Army</name><description>Shopper Army is the proprietary name of a platform created by Toronto-based BrandSpark International to aggregate and deliver to the brand self-selecting but demographically appropriate groups of consumers who are willing to serve as sounding boards and guinea pigs for CPG product launches</description></code>
  <code><value>SKG_CERTIFICATE</value><name></name><description>SKG is the independent institute in the Netherlands for testing and certification for the building industry. Note:Do not use this code. Use SKG_CERTIFICATE_1_STAR, SKG_CERTIFICATE_2_STAR, or SKG_CERTIFICATE_3_STAR.</description></code>
  <code><value>SKG_CERTIFICATE_1_STAR</value><name>SKG 1 star</name><description>SKG is an independent organisation that monitors the quality of products in the construction industry. On the basis of an inspection SKG determines how much resistance a lock or latch provides against burglary. This resistance is in 3 classes.
1 Star - 3 minutes (standard burglar proof)
Building hardware with this label means that it provides at least 3 minutes resistance to burglary with simple tools like a crowbar or screwdriver.</description></code>
  <code><value>SKG_CERTIFICATE_2_STAR</value><name>SKG 2 star</name><description>SKG is an independent organisation that monitors the quality of products in the construction industry. On the basis of an inspection SKG determines how much resistance a lock or latch provides against burglary. This resistance is in 3 classes.
2 Stars - 3 minutes (heavily burglar-proof): With security locks and latches this label must provide for at least 3 minutes resistance to burglary with a comprehensive tool kit.</description></code>
  <code><value>SKG_CERTIFICATE_3_STAR</value><name>SKG 3 star</name><description>SKG is an independent organisation that monitors the quality of products in the construction industry. On the basis of an inspection SKG determines how much resistance a lock or latch provides against burglary. This resistance is in 3 classes.
3 Stars - 5 minutes (extra heavy anti-burglary): Building hardware with this label have to provide resistance to a burglar with heavy tools for at least 5 minutes for your property. It is not only the lock, the hinges and the cylinder that has to be of this heavy quality, but also the door and the frame must provide sufficient resistance.</description></code>
  <code><value>SLG_CHILD_SAFETY</value><name></name><description>SLG Sächsische Landesgewerbeförderungsgesellschaft mbH Distinguishes products that protect children from danger or indicates that no danger for the children comes from the product .</description></code>
  <code><value>SLG_TYPE_TESTED</value><name></name><description>The SLG (Sächsische Landesgewerbeförderungsgesellschaft mbH) Testing and Certification GmbH is a family-owned company. Industrial enterprises, commercial, private and public clients appreciate our neutral and independent services. We offer our customers a comprehensive range of testing and inspection services. </description></code>
  <code><value>SLK_BIO</value><name></name><description>SLK GmbH The aim of organic agriculture is to fullfil standards which emphasise careful processing methods, limited refining, energy saving technologies, minimal use of additives and processing aids etc.</description></code>
  <code><value>SOCIETY_PLASTICS_INDUSTRY</value><name>Society of the Plastics Industry (SPI)</name><description>Many plastic and packaging products display a symbol that looks like the Möbius loop, but has a different purpose and meaning. This symbol is part of a resin coding system produced by the Society of the Plastics Industry (SPI) that identifies the different resins found in plastic bottles and rigid containers. Recycling firms have varying standards for the plastics they accept and the presence of an SPI code does not mean the product is recyclable or recycled in your community. </description></code>
  <code><value>SOIL_ASSOCIATION_ORGANIC_SYMBOL</value><name></name><description>The Soil Association Organic Symbol is a symbol used in the UK to show that products meet a strict set of organic standards that protect health, sustainability and the environment.</description></code>
  <code><value>SPCA_BC</value><name>BC SPCA</name><description>SPCA Certified is an innovative farm certification and food-labelling program dedicated to improving farm animal welfare standards in Canada.</description></code>
  <code><value>STAR_D_KOSHER</value><name>Star D Kosher</name><description>Star D Kosher Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>STAR_K_KOSHER</value><name>STAR K Kosher</name><description>STAR-K Kosher Certification has provided kosher supervision for over fifty years. As a leader in the international world of kosher certification, the STAR-K is most proud of its reputation for providing prompt, friendly and professional service to both the kosher consumer and members of the food industry.
</description></code>
  <code><value>STEEL_RECYCLING</value><name>Steel Recycling
</name><description>The Steel Recycling Institute (SRI) was established in late 1988 as the Steel Can Recycling Institute, a not-for-profit trade association with the mission of promoting and sustaining steel can recycling. With headquarters in Pittsburgh, PA, it was formed by eight North American steel companies and the American Iron and Steel Institute (AISI). The Institute's focus was a grassroots effort to implement steel can recycling in communities across North America</description></code>
  <code><value>STELLAR_CERTIFICATION_SERVICES</value><name>Stellar Certification Services</name><description>Founded in 2002 and one of the oldest organic certifiers in the nation, Stellar Certification Services provides individualized attention and deep agricultural expertise to our members nationwide. When the USDA implemented the National Organic Program (NOP) to provide and enforce a uniform marketplace definition for the term “organic,” Stellar was originally formed to provide organic certification for our Biodynamic farmers and processors. While the NOP standard forms the base to the Demeter Biodynamic standard, in order for a Biodynamic member to receive organic certification they must be certified organic through the NOP program. </description></code>
  <code><value>STIFTUNG_WARENTEST</value><name></name><description>A consumer test organization was founded in 1964 by decision of the German Bundestag to the consumer through the comparative testing of goods and services to provide independent and objective assistance.</description></code>
  <code><value>STOP_CLIMATE_CHANGE</value><name></name><description>AGRA-teg agricultural and Umwelttechnick GmbH is a spin-off undertaking of the University of Goettingen and criteria according to strict scientific carries out the survey of emissions from a product line or from a company as a whole.</description></code>
  <code><value>STRICTLY_KOSHER_NORWAY</value><name>Strictly Kosher - Orthodox Rabbinate of Norway</name><description>In Norway, the Rabbi of the Jewish Community of Oslo certifies production facilities on behalf of the Orthodox Union (OU).  In addition, the community also performs its own certification making it possible to obtain an internationally recongised kosher certificate.</description></code>
  <code><value>SUOMEN_HAMMASLAAKARILIITTO_SUOSITTELEE_KSYLITOLIA</value><name>The Finnish Dental Association recommends xylitol</name><description>The Finnish Dental Association recommends xylitol and requires properties of the xylitol product. In order to receive a recommendation, the applicant for the recommendation must submit a document produced by an independent laboratory as an annex to the application, confirming that the product meets the criteria. Please see the website for the criteria required. https://www.hammaslaakariliitto.fi/en/home/recommendations-finnish-dental-association#.X9IAYdgzZPY</description></code>
  <code><value>SUS</value><name></name><description>The pork-labelling system "sus" makes it possible for consumers to pursue the path of the product without a long investigation. Sus stands for the traceability from birth to slaughter of pork.</description></code>
  <code><value>SUSTAINABLE_FORESTRY_INITIATIVE</value><name></name><description>SFI Inc. is an independent, non-profit organization responsible for maintaining, overseeing and improving a sustainable forestry certification program that is internationally recognized and is the largest single forest standard in the world.</description></code>
  <code><value>SUSTAINABLE_PALM_OIL_RSPO</value><name>Sustainable Palm Oil RSPO Certified</name><description>The 'Certified RSPO' logo needs to be displayed if one of the two supply chain models below are utilized:
Identity Preserved (IP): The Identity Preserved (IP) supply chain model assures that the RSPO certified oil palm product delivered to the end user is uniquely identifiable to a single RSPO certified mill and its certified supply base.
Segregated (SG): The Segregated (SG) supply chain model assures that RSPO certified oil palm products delivered to the end user come only from RSPO certified sources.

https://www.rspo.org/key-documents/certification/rspo-supply-chain-certification</description></code>
  <code><value>SUSTAINABLE_PALM_OIL_RSPO_CREDITS</value><name>Sustainable Palm Oil RSPO Credits</name><description>The 'Credits RSPO' logo needs to be displayed if the supply chain model below is utilized:
Book and Claim (BC): Model that supports the production of RSPO-certified sustainable oil palm products through the sale of RSPO Credits. One (1) RSPO Credit represents one (1) metric tonne of RSPO certified sustainable oil palm product.

https://www.rspo.org/key-documents/certification/rspo-supply-chain-certification</description></code>
  <code><value>SUSTAINABLE_PALM_OIL_RSPO_MIXED</value><name>Sustainable Palm Oil RSPO Mixed</name><description>Supply chain model that allows certified claims to be transferred from one oil palm product to another either through physical blending or administratively under strictly controlled circumstances.

https://www.rspo.org/key-documents/certification/rspo-supply-chain-certification</description></code>
  <code><value>SVANEN</value><name></name><description>The Swan is the Nordic environmental label. It was established by the Nordic Council of Ministers in 1989 and Denmark joined in 1997. The Swan is used in all Nordic countries, i.e. Denmark, Norway, Sweden, Finland and Iceland.</description></code>
  <code><value>SVENSK_FAGEL</value><name></name><description>From the year 2006 include all Swedish chicken and turkey that is part of Swedish Bird with a clear blue and yellow markings. The Swedish Poultry Meat Association represents 99 % of all broiler meat production in Sweden. They represent the total logistic chain i e from import of day-old Grand-Parent chickens to the slaughter plants. The hatcheries, growers and feed-companies are also members. The Blue and Yellow origin mark guarantees that the chicken is hatched, reared, slaughtered and processed in Sweden.</description></code>
  <code><value>SVENSKT_KOTT</value><name></name><description>The brand Swedish meat is a voluntary origin labelling. The mark indicates that the meat product derived from animals that were born and raised in Sweden. The product is also manufactured and packaged in Sweden. The mark may be used on meat and meat products derived from raw pork, beef and lamb. The trade organization Swedish meat is a brand independent organization that develops, manages and controls the voluntary origin labelling Swedish meat.</description></code>
  <code><value>SWEDISH_SEAL_OF_QUALITY</value><name></name><description>The item is physically marked with the Swedish Seal of Quality label which intends to guarantee the responsibility for the environment of the product.</description></code>
  <code><value>TARNOPOL_KASHRUS_KOSHER</value><name>Tarnopol Kashrus Kosher</name><description>Tarnopol Kashrus Kosher Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>TCO_DEVELOPMENT</value><name></name><description>A Swedish company that certifies products and services to provide a better environment.</description></code>
  <code><value>TCO_ORGANIC</value><name>Organic Certifying Body – Trans Canada Organic Certification Services (TCO), Saskatchewan, Canada</name><description>TCO Cert is member owned and controlled, Chapter based and is accredited as a Certifying Body under Canada’s Organic Regime. TCO Cert is managed by a Board of Directors elected by the Association’s members at the Annual General Meeting. The main office, in Humboldt, Saskatchewan, maintains documents pertaining to the incorporation of TCO Cert and has an experienced team able to meet the needs of its members</description></code>
  <code><value>THE_NATURAL_AND_ORGANIC_AWARDS</value><name>The Natural and Organic Awards</name><description>Natural Products is Britain’s leading trade magazine for the natural and organic products industry. Published since 1993 Natural Products provides a unique campaigning edge with a strong reputation for editorial quality and is the must-read title within the industry. </description></code>
  <code><value>THREE_LINE_KOSHER</value><name>Three Line Kosher</name><description>Three Line K Kosher Certification (Rabbi Kelemer &amp; Associates) Certification</description></code>
  <code><value>TIERSCHUTZBUND</value><name></name><description>The logo "for more animal welfare" indicates supermarket meat that comes from animals from conventional attitude, but were held in better conditions than those required by the law. The intention of this logo is to close the gap between industrial animal husbandry and meat from organic farms. </description></code>
  <code><value>TNO_APPROVED</value><name></name><description>TNO awards the TNO label to various products in the Netherlands which meet high standards of sustainable innovation. </description></code>
  <code><value>TOOTHFRIENDLY</value><name></name><description>A symbol to indicate the product is safe to teeth - non-cariogenic and non-erosive by the Institutes licensed by Toothfriendly International.</description></code>
  <code><value>TRADITIONAL_SPECIALTY_GUARANTEED</value><name></name><description>The Traditional specialty guaranteed is a trademark for an agricultural product or a foodstuff, which has a certain feature or a set of features, setting it clearly apart from other similar products or foodstuffs belonging to the same category. The product or foodstuff must be manufactured using traditional ingredients or must be characteristic for its traditional composition, production process, or processing reflecting a traditional type of manufacturing or processing.</description></code>
  <code><value>TRIANGLE_K</value><name>Triangle K Certification</name><description>Triangle K (kashrut) Kosher Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>TRUE_FOODS_CANADA_TRUSTMARK</value><name>True Foods Canada Trustmark</name><description>True Foods™ provides assurance to discerning consumers that food products bearing this trustmark are verified and continually monitored from farm to shelf to ensure that they consistently conform to the label claims on the package.</description></code>
  <code><value>TRUE_SOURCE_CERTIFIED</value><name>True Source Certified</name><description>True Source Certified attribute includes all products that present a True Source Certified logo.  </description></code>
  <code><value>TUEV_GEPRUEFT</value><name></name><description>German label for food safety. The TÜV SÜD as a recognized, neutral testing agency, with its mark both for trading partners and consumers is an important decision-making aid.</description></code>
  <code><value>TUNNUSTATUD_EESTI_MAITSE</value><name></name><description>Approved Estonian Taste - Quality/Tradition/Origin/Traceability for Estonian products. All raw materials must be 100% Estonian. Estonian Chamber of Agriculture and Commerce</description></code>
  <code><value>TUNNUSTATUD_MAITSE</value><name></name><description>Approved Taste label (designed as a barn swallow) denoting Estonian origin and high quality was introduced. This label has been given to products for Food quality and safety. Estonian Chamber of Agriculture and Commerce (ECAC) www.epkk.ee</description></code>
  <code><value>UDEN_GMO_FODER</value><name>UDEN GMO FODER</name><description>The purpose of “UDEN GMO FODER” marque is to determine and guarantee that the products sold - using the “UDEN GMO FODER” marque - originates from a Danish milk farm which cows are fed without any GMO feed (Genetically Modified Organisms). </description></code>
  <code><value>UMWELTBAUM</value><name></name><description>Conformity with Umweltbaum (The Environment Tree)'s standard is verified by an independent organization (third party). 
    Applicable life cycle and supply chain phases
    Social and environmental attributes
    Mutual recognition with other ecolabels
    Standard details, including standard document, review frequency.</description></code>
  <code><value>UNDERWRITERS_LABORATORY</value><name></name><description>The source across the globe for product compliance.</description></code>
  <code><value>UNDERWRITERS_LABORATORY_CERTIFIED_CANADA_US</value><name>Underwriters' Laboratory Certified, Canada “C” and U.S. US”</name><description>There are multiple variations of marks for UL’s Listing service, some of which are for use in the United States, others for use in Canada and still others for use in both markets. Products carrying marks for Canada have been evaluated to Canadian safety requirements, which may be somewhat different from U.S. safety requirements. A combination mark indicates compliance with both Canadian and U.S. requirements.</description></code>
  <code><value>UNIQUELY_FINNISH</value><name></name><description>Uniquely Finnish http://www.maakuntienparhaat.fi/en/ The Uniquely Finnish label is a national quality label for small entrepreneurs. ProAgria Association of Rural Advisory Centres grants the label to qualified foodstuff, handicraft and rural tourism companies based on applications.</description></code>
  <code><value>UNITED_EGG_PRODUCERS_CERTIFIED</value><name>United Egg Producers Certified</name><description>United Egg Producers or (UEP) Certified is an attribute that ensures hen welfare. Requirements for hen welfare are set by the nation's leading animal welfare researchers and veterinarians. UEP Certified is the only science-based animal welfare program for cage and cage-free egg production with standards endorsed by the Food Marketing Institute and the National Council of Chain Restaurants.  Independent and third-party inspections are carried out by either USDA or Validus.</description></code>
  <code><value>UNSER_LAND</value><name></name><description>The regional seal ""Unser Land"" (Our Country) documented regional origin and quality of agricultural products and services based on criteria that go beyond legal requirements. They take into account the strengthening of regional economic cycles in cooperation with all relevant actors work towards a common good regional solidarity economy.</description></code>
  <code><value>USDA</value><name></name><description>US Department of Agriculture</description></code>
  <code><value>USDA_GRADE_A</value><name>U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) – Grade A
e.g., eggs</name><description>USDA’s Agricultural Marketing Service, through the Livestock, Poultry, and Seed Program’s Quality Assessment Division, offers a voluntary program which provides for the official grading of eggs in accordance with the U.S. Grade Standards for the Voluntary Grading of Shell Eggs (pdf) (7 CFR Part 56) and the United States Standards, Grades, and Weight Classes for Shell Eggs (pdf) (AMS 56).</description></code>
  <code><value>USDA_GRADE_AA</value><name>USDA Grade - AA</name><description>United States Department of Agriculture Egg Grading</description></code>
  <code><value>USDA_ORGANIC</value><name></name><description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture has put in place a set of national standards that food labelled products must meet, whether it is grown in the United States or imported from other countries. Organic foods are produced without using most conventional pesticides; fertilizers made with synthetic ingredients or sewage sludge; bioengineering; or ionizing radiation. http://www.usda.gov/wps/portal/usda/usdahome .</description></code>
  <code><value>UTZ_CERTIFIED</value><name></name><description>A certification which is intended to assure the social and environmental quality in coffee production. Coffee based products may be marked with this certification.</description></code>
  <code><value>UTZ_CERTIFIED_COCOA</value><name>UTZ Certified Cocoa</name><description>UTZ Certified is one of the largest programs for sustainable farming of coffee and cocoa in the world. This certification means that a product or brand practices sustainable farm management, good agricultural practices and above standard living and social conditions for the environment. </description></code>
  <code><value>VAAD_HOEIR_KOSHER</value><name>Vaad Hoeir Kosher</name><description>Vaad Hoeir Kosher Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>VAELG_FULDKORN_FORST</value><name></name><description>Grain based foods (bread, breakfast products, baking articles etc.) which have got a high content of whole grain will be puffed with a nutritional puff from the beginning of 2009: Please choose whole grain first! Denmark http://www.fuldkorn.dk/</description></code>
  <code><value>VDE</value><name></name><description>VDE stands for "Verband der Elektrotechnik, Elektronik und Informationstechnik". This German Institute tests and certifies electrical equipment, components and systems and is like Dutch KEMA-quality mark.</description></code>
  <code><value>VDS_CERTIFICATE</value><name></name><description>VdS (Vertrauen durch Sicherheit) is an independent and recognized German inspection and certification agency for fire and burglary. Whether it is a safe in a company, a sprinkler system in a production hall or a smoke detector in a house: VdS examines to the smallest detail.</description></code>
  <code><value>VEGAN_AWARENESS_FOUNDATION</value><name></name><description>The Vegan Awareness Foundation (Vegan Action) administers the “Certified Vegan” Logo, an easy-to-recognize trademarked symbol.  The Logo is a registered trademark, similar in nature to the “kosher” mark, for products that do not contain animal products or byproducts and that have not been tested on animals.   Companies must submit and have approved by the Vegan Awareness Foundation that acceptable steps are taken to thoroughly clean and sanitize all surfaces, vessels, utensils and machinery used between vegan and non-vegan production cycles to minimize cross-contamination if shared machinery is used.</description></code>
  <code><value>VEGAN_BY_EARTHKOSHER</value><name>Vegan By Earthkosher</name><description>EarthKosher offers a Vegan Verification program. The standards for the Vegan Verification program are that a product contains no animal products or animal product derivatives whatsoever, i.e. “Zero Tolerance”. </description></code>
  <code><value>VEGAN_NATURAL_FOOD_CERTIFIERS</value><name>Vegan Natural Food Certifiers</name><description>Vegan Natural Food Certifiers attribute includes all products that present a Vegan Natural Food Certifiers logo.</description></code>
  <code><value>VEGAN_SOCIETY_VEGAN_LOGO</value><name></name><description>The Vegan logo is a registered trademark and is a symbol of our Vegan 'Animal-free' Standards . It appears on thousands of animal free products, and is displayed by catering businesses, that have been registered with The Vegan Society.</description></code>
  <code><value>VEGAPLAN</value><name>Vegaplan</name><description>The Vegaplan vzw was founded in 2003 by the members of the Platform for the Transformation and Trading of Raw Materials and Plant Products (PTMV) bringing together the different sectors and by the agricultural associations (Algemeen Boerensyndicaat, Boerenbond and Walloon Federation of 'Agriculture).
Vegaplan vzw is intended primarily for farms and agricultural entrepreneurs who wish to obtain certification based on the 'Standard Vegaplan' specifications and / or the 'Sector Guide' recommended by the FASFC (Federal Agency for Safety of the food chain). The Vegaplan vzw also targets buyers of raw materials from the plant sector, namely companies in the "trade and transformation of plant products" link, with a view to optimizing quality within the plant sector.</description></code>
  <code><value>VEGATARIAN_SOCIETY_V_LOGO</value><name>Vegetarian Society - Vegetarian</name><description>The Vegetarian Society influences, inspires and supports people to embrace and maintain a vegetarian lifestyle. We work constructively with businesses, government agencies, policy makers and professionals, whilst always remaining independent. We rely on membership subscriptions and donations to carry out this vital work. Established in 1847, we are the oldest vegetarian organisation in the world.</description></code>
  <code><value>VEGECERT</value><name>Vegan - VegeCert</name><description>VegeCert is a non-profit organization that certifies vegan and vegetarian food products. Vegans and Vegetarians represent approximately 5% of American and Canadian consumers, and VegeCert helps this key demographic make informed decisions about the food that they eat. VegeCert is unique in that we make physical inspections of our certified food manufacturing facilities to ensure that they conform to VegeCert's high standards.</description></code>
  <code><value>VEILIG_WONEN_POLITIE_KEURMERK</value><name></name><description>The Dutch "Politie Keurmerk Veilig Wonen" quality mark  focuses on the prevention of intrusion in homes or buildings. The quality mark is given to locks by means of stars in which the burglar resistance is specified in minutes. Incidentally this label covers not only locks but also mirrors, smoke detectors and lighting fixtures.</description></code>
  <code><value>VERBUND_OEKOHOEFE</value><name>Verbund Ökohöfe</name><description>The label certifies that the guidelines of Verbund Ökohöfe e.V. are met. These guidelines are stronger than the legal requirements of the EU for organic farming (EC-Eco-Basis Ordinance (EC) No. 834/2007). 
For example, the following rules apply to the producers: 
- In cattle keeping: no dehorning, no tethering, pasture (at least 100 days) 
- CMS hybrids from protoplast fusion (horticultural cultures) and rye, wheat, triticale, barley, flower and herbal hybrids are not permitted. In addition, different restrictions apply to vegetable hybrids. - Conventional dung GMO (genetically modified organism) fed mammals is not permitted.
- Copper preparations may only be used in fruit, wine and potato cultivation (maximum copper quantity 3kg / ha and year, calculated on the basis of the five-year average of rotation). 
- For horticultural crops, a 100 m distance to the motorway and 30 m to other busy roads must be observed.
- settlecomposts - also from quality-tested systems - are not permissible, since the GMO is not guaranteed in the process.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDE_AGNEAU_FRANCAIS</value><name>Viande Agneau Francais</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case lamb: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France". 

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDE_BOVINE_FRANCAISE</value><name>Viande Bovine Francaise</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France". This identifies French cattle products.

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDE_CHEVALINE_FRANCAISE</value><name>Viande Chevaline Francaise</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case chevaline products: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France". 
Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.  Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:
Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDE_DE_CHEVRE_FRANCAISE</value><name>Viande de Chevre Francaise</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case meat from goats: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDE_DE_CHEVREAU_FRANCAISE</value><name>Viande de Chevreau Francaise</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case meat products from young goats: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France". 

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDE_DE_VEAU_FRANCAISE</value><name>Viande de Veau Francaise</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case veal products: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDES_DE_FRANCE</value><name>Viandes de France</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case meat products: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VIANDE_OVINE_FRANCAISE</value><name>Viande Ovine Francaise</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case meat products from sheep: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>VINHO_VERDE</value><name>Product of the Vinho Verde Region</name><description>The Seal of Guarantee certifies the authenticity and genuineness of Vinho Verde, assuring its origin and strict controls carried out at all stages of the production process, from the vineyard to the glass. Each stamp is unique, with coding both unique and traceable.</description></code>
  <code><value>VOLAILLE_FRANCAISE</value><name>Volaille Francaise</name><description>The French agricultural organizations have created a common visual identity in order to highlight the French origin of agricultural products in this case poultry products: the signatures "Agricultural Products of France".

Remarkable to their elegant silhouette in a tricolor pentagon that is available for each family of products, these signatures reflect the commitment of the professionals of the sectors to value the know-how, the territories and the French jobs.

Covering a variety of productions, these signatures all have a common basis, which consists of four criteria:

Origin France of the products concerned,
The existence of specifications or regulations governing the use of the logo,
A formal commitment from the operators of the sectors concerned wishing to use these logos,
Controls performed by a third party.</description></code>
  <code><value>WARRANT_HOLDER_OF_THE_COURT_OF_BELGIUM</value><name>Warrant holder of the court of Belgium</name><description>"Becoming an official supplier to the Belgian Court is a source of particular pride for a craftsman or company to seeing their talent and professionalism rightly recognized by His Majesty the King.



"</description></code>
  <code><value>WEIDEMELK</value><name></name><description>A certification given in the Netherlands to dairy products made from milk produced by cattle (bovine) that is allowed to roam free in the pasture for at least a minimum of 120 days in a year.</description></code>
  <code><value>WEIGHT_WATCHERS_ENDORSED</value><name>Weight Watchers Endorsed</name><description>Foods and meals in the Weight Watchers program are assigned points, and you're allotted a certain number of points daily depending on your initial body weight and weight loss goals. Some packaged food brands and even certain restaurants have teamed up with Weight Watchers to promote this healthy point-based weight-loss program.</description></code>
  <code><value>WESTERN_KOSHER</value><name>Kosher Western Kosher (WK)</name><description>Western Kosher provides assistance with Kashruth supervision by certifying bakeries, butcher shops, caterers, restaurants, hotels, manufacturers or processors involved in producing Kosher food products for year-round use for Canada and the United States. 

Western Kosher, formerly the Vaad Ha'ir of Winnipeg, provides its 120 licensees with the North American standard of kashruth – a standard adhered to throughout all of Canada and the U.S. 
</description></code>
  <code><value>WHOLE_GRAIN_100_PERCENT_STAMP</value><name>Whole Grain 100 Percent Stamp</name><description>The Whole Grain 100 Percent Stamp is a program of The Whole Grain Council. The Whole Grains Council helps consumers find whole grain foods and understand their health benefits; helps manufacturers and restaurants create delicious whole grain foods; and helps the media write accurate, compelling stories about whole grains. If a product bears the 100% Stamp, then all its grain ingredients are whole grains. There is a minimum requirement of 16g (16 grams) – a full serving – of whole grain per labelled serving, for products using the 100% Stamp.</description></code>
  <code><value>WHOLE_GRAIN_BASIC_STAMP</value><name>Whole Grain Basic Stamp</name><description>The Whole Grain Basic Stamp is a program of The Whole Grain Council. The Whole Grains Council helps consumers find whole grain foods and understand their health benefits; helps manufacturers and restaurants create delicious whole grain foods; and helps the media write accurate, compelling stories about whole grains. If a product bears the Basic Stamp, it contains at least 8g (8 grams) – a half serving – of whole grain, but may also contain some refined grain. Even if a product contains large amounts of whole grain (23g, 37g, 41g, etc.), it will use the Basic Stamp if it also contains extra bran, germ, or refined flour.</description></code>
  <code><value>WHOLE_GRAIN_COUNCIL_STAMP</value><name></name><description>Canadian products must contain at least 8 g of whole grain per serving to bear the Whole Grain Stamp. All requirements for using the Basic Stamp are the same in the U.S. and in Canada.</description></code>
  <code><value>WHOLE_GRAINS_50_PERCENT_STAMP</value><name>Whole grains 50 percent Stamp </name><description>If a product bears the 50%+ Stamp, then at least half of its grain ingredients are whole grain. There is a minimum requirement of 8 grams– a half serving – of whole grain per labelled serving, for products using the 50%+ Stamp. 
</description></code>
  <code><value>WISCONSIN_K</value><name>Kosher Supervisors of Wisconsin Certification </name><description>Kosher Supervisors of Wisconsin Certification </description></code>
  <code><value>WQA_TESTED_CERTIFIED_WATER</value><name>Water Quality Association (WQA's)- Tested and Certified </name><description>WQA's Certified Product Listings are available to help connect consumers with water treatment products that have been tested and certified to industry standards. WQA's Gold Seal Product Certification Program ensures that the product is constructed or formulated from safe materials, the claims listed on the packaging are backed by test data, and the product will hold up under normal usage conditions.</description></code>
  <code><value>WSDA</value><name></name><description>Washington State Department of Agriculture Organic Food Program, Washington State Department of Agriculture Organic Food Program (WSDA) Organic Food Program  The WSDA Organic Food Program, a USDA-accredited certifier, upholds the integrity of the organic label through certification and inspection of organic crop and livestock producers, processors, handlers and retailers. Whether you are looking to market your organic product at home or abroad, WSDA offers certification services to meet your needs. Please browse below to find out how WSDA can put your business on the path to certification.</description></code>
  <code><value>WWF_PANDA_LABEL</value><name></name><description>Products that support the WWF http://www.worldwildlife.org/</description></code>
  <code><value>ZELDZAAM_LEKKER</value><name></name><description>This label is awarded to companies that support (through their products or services) the preservation of rare or uncommon cattle and animal sorts. 




</description></code>
  <code><value>ZERO_WASTE_BUSINESS_COUNCIL_CERTIFIED</value><name>Zero Waste Business Council Certified</name><description>U.S. Zero Waste Business Council Certification Program is created by U.S. Zero Waste Business Council. It is the first third-party Zero Waste Facility Certification program for facilities that meet the requests of Zero Waste Business for a valid, comprehensive verification of their Zero Waste achievements. </description></code>
</codeList>